al
al
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Sparkle Oh
Sparkle Oh
[Music]
[Música]
wow
wow
he ye
he ye
[Music]
[Música]
B
B
ye
ye
ha
ha
[Music]
[Música]
P
P
ber
ber
[Music]
[Música]
good evening how are you
buenísimas noches qué tal estáis me
luares just sent me he just sent me some
luares me acaba de mandar un par de
curious gossip eh he explodes
chismes así curiosos eh explota en
live with Javi's physique and Setup
directo con el físico y el Setup de Javi
what What the [ __ ] [ __ ] What's wrong with
qué What the fuck fuck Qué le pasa a
this man What's wrong Alé gorgeous
este hombre Pero qué cosa Ale guapísimo
how is he Hey but this man what is it what did he have for
cómo está Oye pero este hombre qué es lo
breakfast because it
que qué es lo que ha desayunado porque
seems like he had some strange substance for breakfast I mean he
parece que ha desayunado una sustancia
's Every
un poco extraña o sea está Todos los
[ __ ] day every [ __ ] day
[__] días todos los [__] días
completely crazy
completamente ido de la olla
eh but everything is clear the
eh pero está todo claro es que el
problem is that I don't pay
problema es que yo no le voy haciendo
attention to him because I go through my day
caso porque yo voy echando mi día
doing my normal life but I
haciendo mi vida normal y corriente pero
have this crazy guy all [ __ ] day long okay Cool okay
tengo a este loquito todo el [__] día e
Cool  luare we see him we see him
vale Guay vale Guay luare lo vemos lo
too eh he's there all day Javi
vemos también eh está todo el día Javi
you're going to have to sue him they just
vas a tener que demandarlo me acaban de
told me I'm not going to tell you who but
decir no os voy a decir quién pero me
someone just wrote to me and said
acaba de escribir alguien y me ha dicho
Javi has posted things on Twitter that are
Javi ha puesto en Twitter cosas que son
reportable in the United States So
denunciables en Estados Unidos Entonces
if that's how it is We'll see
si eso es así Ya vamos a verlo a ver
how far he's super obsessed but he
hasta dónde está super obsesionado pero
goes alone I mean every now and then
es que va solo o sea yo de vez en cuando
every but I think he's a person who is
cada pero yo creo que es una persona que
not well let's not see if we're going to
no está bien no sea ver si lo vamos a
report him and he's going to be able to claim problems of
denunciar y va a poder alegar problemas
course man I don't know doesn't he realize he
claro hombre no sé no se da cuenta que
's making a fool of himself I mean gibel went
está haciendo el ridículo o sea gibel ha
out to slap him three or four
salido a pegarle tres o cuatro
times and he's making a fool of himself
cachetadas y está haciendo el ridículo
sir he's 50 months old 50 no 500
señor que tiene 50 meses 50 no 500
months there are several people who are not
meses hay varias personas que no están
well What's going on fay What's going on F eh but the thing is
bien Qué pasa fay Qué pasa F eh pero es
that this guy I don't know The Movida he had
que este señor no sé La Movida la tuvo
with dasas and with you it took it much more
con dasas y contigo la tomó mucho más
but the thing is no no I don't understand what's wrong with this guy
pero es que no no yo de este tío no no
What's
entiendo que es lo que le pasa Cuál es
his problem is that from time to
su problema es que de vez en
time from time to time I run into him I run into him
cuando de vez en cuando me lo encuentro
there Look what's
me lo encuentro ahí Mirad lo que ha
post but he only
puesto pero él solo se
eats the logic of this [ __ ] old man
papea la lógica del viejo [__] este
@ javioliveira
@ javioliveira
gigachat
gigachat
contetas he has only eaten himself here and
contetas él solo se ha papeado aquí y
puts the couples in the middle that I do not
mete a las parejas por medio que no
understand the
entiendo
sense or rather this no no he got really burned
el el sentido o sea este no no se ardió
because d mentioned them about the
muchísimo porque d las mencionó lo de la
mother the One who formed is that d said them
madre la Que formó es que d las ha dicho
about my mother I do not know what I do not know
lo de mi madre no sé qué no sé
how much But what What happens that you
cuánto Pero qué Qué pasa que te
burn desperate for attention it is not that
ardes desesperación por atención no es
I think he is going he is going Burning more by
que yo creo que se va se va Ardiendo más
himself because he wants to be based and you do not
el solo porque quiere ir de basado y no
know how to be based r you are going to end up in
sabes ser basado r vas a acabar en la
[ __ ] jail because they just wrote to me
[__] cárcel porque me acaban de escribir
while I was in gossip they
mientras que estaba ent salseo me han
told me that you have posted things that are
dicho que has puesto cosas que son
criminal in the United States and if it is like
delictivas en Estados Unidos y como sea
that from here right now I am going to make
así desde aquí ahora mismo voy a hacer
an appeal to any lawyer who
un llamamiento a cualquier abogado que
follows me who can practice in the United
me siga que pueda ejercer en los Estados
States and wants to
Unidos y quiera
take it without further I mean I do not have
llevarlo sin más O sea yo no tengo
any kind of problem for me you are
ningún tipo de problema para mí no eres
nobody important to me you are zero to
nadie importante para mí eres cero para
me you are a guy who is there
mí eres una un tipo que está ahí
screaming alone at the
gritando solo con la
wall for me it is from time to time
pared por para mí es de vez en cuando lo
I see it as a joke as a joke
veo yo como un chiste como una gracia
Well of  from time to time I answer him it's
Pues de vez en cuando le contesto es
like those but worse he's being really
como delos pero peor está siendo mucho
ridiculous he's being really ridiculous I
ridículo está siendo mucho el ridículo o
mean here why the [ __ ] is he eating himself Right now
sea aquí por qué [__] se papea Así mismo
okay And look at what I put eh
vale Y fijaros lo que yo he puesto eh
simply jaj well You
simplemente jaj pues Tú solito te has
answered yourself inmate okay ratio No HM mega
contestado recluso vale ratio No HM mega
ratio I mean ratio not hyper mega ratio
ratio O sea ratio no hiper mega ratio
but like that Every time that I mean I
pero así Cada vez que o sea yo
simply put three words like this I move I
simplemente pongo tres palabras así
move my finger a little and it and and and
muevo muevo el dedo un poco y lo y y y y
and I sink it I leave it very clear and it
y lo hundo lo dejo fatal claro y se va
burns more and it burns more And
Ardiendo más y se va Ardiendo más Y va
the level goes up Look in the end you
subiendo el nivel Mira al final le
ate the mouths of the 13 year olds who
comiste la boca a las de 13 años que se
stay up all night on discord talking to you
trasnocha en discord hablando contigo
[ __ ] disgusting sadist and Just like your
[__] sádico asqueroso y Igualito a tu
owner couple of sick people who get wet for
dueño par de enfermo que se mojan por
schoolgirls and Look at what I
colegialas y Fíjate lo que le he
answered him Look at what I answered him
contestado yo Fíjate lo que le he
eh Look what Look at what I
eh Fíjate lo que Fíjate lo que le he
answered him and it burns more Hahaha he answers
contestado y se arde más Jajaja responde
am morpho did you eat his face or didn't you  were
am morfo le comiste la cara o no te la
you able to escape that catfish that you have
pudiste escapar al bagre ese que tienes
for a wife clown here starts
por esposa payaso aquí se pone a
insulting Lorena I mean it's not going to
insultar a Lorena O sea no se me va a
occur to me to mess with the girlfriend eh
ocurrir a mí meterme con la novia eh
absolutely not I saw that there
absolutamente para nada He visto que
were a lot of people there saying
había mucha gente por ahí diciéndole a
things to the girl and so on the girl is
la chica cosas y demás la chica está
with him I mean she has a lot of
está con él o sea bastante tiene
connection with him you know I mean I'm not going I do
conectar con él sabes o sea yo no me voy
n't know what's going through my head but it's that I
no sé me pasa por la cabeza pero es que
would look bad if now I start
quedaría mal yo si ahora yo me pongo a
messing with the girlfriend like he does I would
meterme con la novia como hace él yo
look like him completely ridiculous you
quedaría como él en completo ridículo me
understand me and everyone is telling him
entienden y se lo está diciendo todo el
everyone what does
mundo todo el mundo qué tenía que ver
Lorena have to do with it that he's crazy I mean it seems like he
Lorena que está desquiciado o sea parece
had cocaine for breakfast no I don't
que ha desayunado cocaína no no lo
understand it's that I see him all day
entiendo es que lo veo todo el día lo
I see him all day screaming to himself like a
veo todo el día gritando solo como un
crazy person Screaming to himself like a crazy person and every
loco Así gritando solo como un loco y yo
now and then as it turns out as it's
de vez en cuando como me sale como está
verified I appear there from
verificado me aparece por ahí pues de
time to time I do like this I put three
vez en cuando le hago así le pongo tres
words and simply with three words
palabras y simplemente con tres palabras
okay it always looks terrible I mean
vale queda siempre fatal o sea se lo
everyone is telling him but but I
está diciendo todo el mundo pero pero
think that yes I think that we're going to have to
creo que sí creo que vamos a tener que
report him or  sea ​​he already has a problem
denunciarle o sea tiene ya un problema
in the United States because they just
en Estados Unidos porque lo acabaron de
put him in jail for threatening to
meter en la cárcel por amenazar de
kill a person okay well
muerte a una persona vale que bueno
according to his version his version is that he
según él su versión su versión es que él
went to report a person because he
fue a denunciar a una persona porque le
owed him money and the police made a mistake and
debía dinero y la policía se equivocó y
put him in jail okay according to
lo metió a él en la cárcel vale según
according to his version then RAE I'm
según la versión de él entonces RAE te
telling you from here like you told me a
lo digo desde aquí como me contaste un
lawyer like you told me a lawyer from the
abogado como me contaste un abogado de
United States that I don't know any
Estados Unidos que no conozco ninguno
right now I don't have any like you
ahora mismo no tengo ninguno como me
told me a lawyer from the United States
contaste un abogado de Estados Unidos
who wants to report you can do it or I mean that thing that
que te quiera denunciar se puede hacer o
people think that
sea eso eso de que la gente se piensa
when you are in one country or another
que cuando tú estás en un país o en otro
that you can't report it is as
que tú no puedes denunciar sí es tan
simple as hiring a lawyer and
sencillo como que contrates un abogado y
a solicitor in that country you know what I mean
un procurador en ese país me entiendes
So if there are things here that constitute
Entonces si hay aquí cosas constitutivas
crimes in the United States raed I'm going
de delitos en Estados Unidos raed te voy
to report you And you're making a complete
a denunciar Y estás haciendo el completo
fool of yourself you're not being based nor
ridículo ni estás quedando basado ni
are you making a fool of yourself it's that I don't have to
estás haciendo el ridículo es que yo no
tell you anything because you're
te tengo que decir nada porque te estás
humiliating yourself you
humillando tú
humiliate yourself and on top of that you're going to
solo te humillas tú solo y encima te vas
look for trouble that they're going to throw you
a buscar un problema que te van a ech
out of the United States because  you've already
allá de los Estados Unidos porque ya has
spent a weekend in jail and you
pasado un fin de semana en la cárcel Y
're awaiting
estás a la espera de un
trial you understand Then behave yourself he
juicio me entiendes Entonces compórtate
lives in the United States I don't
que vive en los Estados Unidos que no sé
even know how you are in the United States I'm
ni cómo estás en los Estados Unidos
also telling you
también te digo
Hey what's up mommy You're flirting with me
Eh qué pasa mariaca Me estás piropeando
over there you're pulling my leg
por ahí me está me estáis golfeado
this insistence of r gives me the
esa insistencia de r da como la
feeling that he wants to be on
sensación de que quiere quedar por
top because he doesn't even believe that he's
encima porque ni él se cree que está
doing well anymore but he's getting
quedando bien ya pero es que se está
unhinged and he's getting worse look
desquiciando y está quedando peor mira
what he says no e I
lo que pone no e yo con este pedazo de
don't have and I'm not going to have any
cerdo no tengo ni voy a tener ningún
kind of consideration with this piece of pig The more he
tipo de contemplaciones Mientras más me
names me the more acid I'm going to get let's see
nombre más ácido me voy a poner a ver
who can stand more pressure ra it's not that I
quién aguanta más presión ra que yo no
'm standing up to any pressure
es que estoy aguantando ninguna presión
because to me you
que para mí
're nothing zero So you can
eres nada cero O sea que yo tú puedes
insult Lorena there my father my
insultar ahí a Lorena a mi padre a mi
mother my children are going to say about you about me you're
madre a mis hijos va a decir de ti de mí
not going to say about me I would say that I
no vas a decir de mí diría que yo de
suddenly said something to your girlfriend that I'm not
repente le dijera algo a tu novia que no
going to do it I don't know her You're welcome do you
lo voy a hacer no la conozco De nada me
understand me and I ask everyone from here that It's
entiendes y le pido desde aquí a todo el
good that I don't even believe that they
mundo que Que bueno que ni siquiera creo
are  doing you know whether it's that it's
que lo estén haciendo sabes sea que que
not about whether you should or should
que no es que se trate de que aguantar o
n't endure it, the one who can't
no aguantar que el que no está
endure it is you That your
aguantando eres tú Que te va a explotar
brain cell is going to explode, the one you have out there floating around,
una neurona la que tienes por ahí dando
don't sue him for that, that's why they
vueltas no lo demandes por eso en
're terrible in the United States and they'll put you in a
Estados Unidos están fatal y te meten la
life sentence. I think he's already said several
perpetua yo creo que ya ha dicho varias
things that are actionable eh, I mean, I
cosas que son demanda bles eh o sea yo
think from what I understand
creo que por lo que tengo yo entendido
about how the issue
de cómo funciona el el el tema en
of lawsuits and
Estados Unidos de las demandas y de las
complaints works in the United States, I see things around here that are
denuncias yo veo por aquí cosas demanda
actionable and reportable, both things is that I do
bles y denunciables las dos cosas es que
n't know, I don't have a lawyer in
no conozco no tengo ningún abogado en a
Oh, I've never fought with anyone from the
Ay Nunca me he peleado con nadie de
United States, but I'm sure that
Estados Unidos Pero estoy seguro que
someone is going to contact me and we're going to take him in
alguien me va a contactar y lo vamos a
because he's spouting
llevar porque es que está soltando aquí
some
Unas
outrageous things here, but but he's the only one, nobody's
barbaridades pero Pero él solo nadie le
answering him, and from time to time I
está contestando yo de vez en cuando
tell him what a prisoner is, but it
pues le digo lo que es un recluso pero
's not defamation, nor
es que no es ninguna difamación Ni
any
Ningún
insult, what the news that I've given is
insulto lo que la noticia que yo he dado
that they've put her in jail, no,
que que la han metido en la cárcel no si
the file is there, they've put you in
está ahí la ficha te han metido en la
jail, but it's nothing more that there is to
cárcel pero si es que nada más que hay
see how you behave on
que verte cómo te comportas en
social media, I mean look, look how you behave
redes o sea mira mira cómo te comportas
on social media, what are you
en redes qué es lo que estás
saying?
diciendo
Look, Gel comes and says, why are you
Mira viene gel y le dice Por qué
insulting his wife who has nothing to do with it?
insultas a su mujer que no tiene nada
You're looking really bad and he says,
que ver estás quedando muy mal y dice
ret, I don't give a damn if he comes back today
ret me chupa tres huevos que vuelva hoy
to lie about me on his filthy Stream. I'm
a mentir sobre mí en su cochino Stream
going after the rest of his family. I didn't
voy a por el resto de su familia no te
see you so angry when Dallas called
vi tan ardido cuando Dallas le dijo [__]
my girlfriend a [ __ ]. You haven't seen anything yet. This guy
a mi novia no has visto nada aún este
wants to be a bully on the internet. Let him
quiere ir de buly en internet que se
put up with it. Pa, it's that I'm not putting up with
aguante Pa es que yo no estoy aguantando
anything, they're getting you in
nada que te están metiendo en un
trouble. You
problema tú
say that I'm not putting up with anything, they're
raet que yo no estoy aguantando nada que
going to kick you out of the United States and
te van a echar de los estados Unidos y
you're going to be even more
vas a ser más el
ridiculous. This is totally reportable. Javi,
ridículo esto es denunciable total Javi
I think so, but oh well. I'm going
yo creo que sí pero bueno Igualmente voy
to wait and see if I can get
a esperar a ver si puedo conseguir
someone to
alguien que lo
take it. I'm going to go, someone who's a
lleve Igualmente voy voy alguien que sea
professional, someone who I find out about, who has
profesional que yo me entere que tenga
a good track record, okay, and who understands the
un buen recorrido vale Y que entienda el
issue well because I think there are
tema bien porque yo creo que aquí hay
threats here and I think there are slander, okay.
amenazas y creo que hay e calumnias vale
What happens is that I don't know there. How it
Lo que pasa que no sé allí Cómo
will work. I've seen lawsuits for
funcionará yo he visto demandas por
much
mucho
less, okay. I've seen  there you sue for
menos vale Yo he visto allí demandas por
much less So expect him to
mucho menos Entonces esperar que
contact you and for me to find out about this,
contacte y que yo me entere bien de Esto
okay, eh And we
vale eh Y lo y lo
report it Well, it's just that we have to
denunciamos Pues es que nada más que hay
see it clearly It's that then he comes to tell us that
que verlo claro Es que luego nos viene a
no, that he comes to tell us
contar que no que que nos viene a contar
that no, that it's a lie that they
que no que es que es mentira que a él lo
put him in jail because they got the
metieron en la cárcel porque se
wrong person but guys if we
equivocaron de persona pero chicos si te
're seeing you on Twitter how you
estamos viendo en Twitter cómo te
behave
comportas
okay if I criticized him for messing with
vale si yo critiqué que se metiera con
your girlfriend you're really skinny it's not okay It's
tu novia estás bien flaco no está bien
okay when skinny because I only
Está bien cuando flaco porque yo solo te
see you here sucking this
veo aquí chupándosela de nuevo a este
slanderer again then you go around crying too, you're
difamador después anda llorando también
not going to be a bully because I bet you that this big
no van de buly pues te apuesto a que el
mouth isn't going to say anything about the
bocón este no va a decir nada de la
filthy song that his master just released
canción inmunda que acaba de sacar su
which is that I just found out
amo que es que me me acabo de enterar
that you're interested in Dallas and me
que tú estás pendiente de Dallas y de mí
And all of us who are famous and you're
Y de todos los que somos famosos y tú
not but that I'm just that I'm not
no pero que yo me acabo que yo no estoy
interested in the song that Dallas releases
pendiente de la canción que saque Dallas
well we'll see it we'll react now
pues la veremos la reaccionaremos ahora
Of course but why am I not going to say
Claro que sí pero por qué no voy a decir
anything about the song Because it's good
nada de la canción Porque es buena
because it is  bad boy calm down
porque es mala chico que te calmes que
take something to
te tomes algo que te
calm you down you don't have it you don't have a
tranquilice no tienes no tienes a una
person by your side who loves you and
persona al lado que te que te quiera y
tells you you're making a fool of yourself You
te diga estás haciendo el ridículo Me
're
estás dando
embarrassing me you're
vergüenza estás dando
embarrassing you have too many people and very little
vergüenza tienen mucha gente y muy poco
stamina you guys that no no no it's not about
aguante ustedes que que no no no se
stamina that the one who has little
trata de aguante que el que tiene poco
stamina is
aguante eres
you says I only told you that you messed with
tú dice solo te dije que te metiste con
the woman and that's wrong Besides
la mujer y eso está mal Además de que
saying that you would mess with the rest of his
decí que te meterías con el resto de su
family his son I think is 5 years old
familia su hijo creo que tiene 5 años
friend You need treatment for
amigo Necesitas tratamiento contra la
anger he's not well as he is it's going to be
ira no está bien como está te va a ha
bad for you your opinion is worthless tomorrow you'll
ser mal tu opinión no vale nada mañana
change it
la cambias
weather vane it's that there isn't a single [ __ ]
veleta es que no hay ni un [__]
comment in favor of raed but just like you would
comentario a favor de raed pero al igual
n't have any kind of
que no tendrías ningún tipo de
comment in a trial that you're
comentario en un juicio que estás
threatening Excuse me Lord of
amenazando Discúlpame Señor de los
principles who is the one who is in that
principios quién es el que está en ese
live with Dallas and liis a lawsuit in the
directo con Dallas y liis una demanda en
USA is very expensive you will lose
USA sale muy cara perderás
money but very expensive what is it and
dinero pero muy cara qué es lo que es y
how much is it and how does it work Or rather to me you
cuánto es y cómo va O sea a mí que me
told someone who knows how to do it well
contaste a alguien que sepa hacerlo bien
and it is done Of course it is done without any
y se hace Claro que se hace sin ningún
kind of problem without any kind  or a
tipo de problema sin ningún tipo o una
complaint surely a complaint
denuncia seguramente una denuncia sí se
can be made maybe a lawsuit no
puede hacer a lo mejor una demanda no
but a complaint Yes there are threats here they are
pero una denuncia Sí hay amenazas aquí
not messing with a woman and
no se está metiendo con con una mujer y
a
con un
minor you
menor
understand those two robbed me and
entiendes a mí esos dos me robaron Y
defamed you what do they do to you to make you
difamaron a ti qué te hacen para que
change your mind dressing in a different
cambies de opinión vestirte de otro
color he is
color está
being he is being ridiculous okay I
siendo está siendo el ridículo vale o
mean here he has eaten himself he has put his
sea aquí se ha papeado el solo ha puesto
girlfriend alone what is this cowardly old man going to debate
a la novia el solo qué va a debatir este
if he always shits himself
viejo cobarde si siempre se caga encima
and calls his owner to take care of him and
y Llama a su dueño para que lo cuide y
starts yelling over my voice RAE you made a
empieza a gritar encima de mi voz RAE
fool of yourself here with
que hiciste aquí el ridículo con el
Dallas but you made a fool of yourself here with
Dallas pero hiciste aquí el ridículo con
him
el
and you did it in the
y lo hiciste en el
space you started saying that you would
space que te pusiste a decir que no
never speak to delox in your life
hablarías con el delox nunca en la vida
because he was a scammer and you went to
porque era un estafador y te fuiste a
tell him one of those stories that you
contarle una historia de estas que tú te
make up that Dallas had told you
inventas de que Dallas te había dicho
that he had hitmen with whom he was going to
que tenía sicarios con los que iba a
kill delo that he was going to dress him up
matar a delo que lo iba a disfrazar
as a balloon he was going to go dressed up as a
delde globo iba ir disfrazado delde
balloon to send him a hamburger and he was
Globo A mandarle una hamburguesa y se
going to break into his house that he had
iba a meter en su casa que le había
explained to him what the hallways were like  from his
explicado como eran los pasillos de su
house and everything so that he would
casa y todo para que le para que lo
kill him the pity of those who gave you the ball
matara la pena de los que te dieron bola
the pity of those who saw you as a ball Because
la pena de los que te vieron bola Porque
from the first moment gibel for
yo desde el primer momento gibel por
example who is now arguing there you
ejemplo que ahora está discutiendo ahí
gave balls to this crazy hot old man it cracks
le disteis bolas a este loco viejo
me up how raed says that
caliente me da gracia como raed dice que
Dallas insulted his girlfriend that you are
Dallas insultó a su novia que tú eres
Dallas what does Dallas have to do with it here
Dallas qué tiene que ver Dallas aquí
and But what does it have to do with it that I have to
e Pero qué tiene que ver que tengo que
do with it not even with this man this
ver yo ni siquiera con este hombre que
man is not part of our
este hombre no forma parte de nuestras
lives and he is every day every
vidas y está todos todos los días todos
day every day crazy just
los días todos los días desquiciado solo
talking to the walls yelling at
hablando con las paredes gritando
us from time to time well we
nosotros de vez en cuando pues le
put a tweet like this I
ponemos un tweet así
mean if you see the twe with which I
O sea si veis los twe con los que yo le
respond they are like four words and he gets
respondo son así cuatro palabras y se
hotter and he gets more ignited I mean what did he
arde más y se enciende más O sea qué es
put Someone has to place it in
puso Alguien tiene que ubicarlo en
time and space that you are not
tiempo y espacio que tú no estás
placing anyone RAE that you are making a
ubicando a nadie RAE que estás haciendo
fool of yourself there is no one next to you who
el ridículo no hay nadie al lado que te
loves you and says man you are making me
quiera y diga tío que me estás dando
ashamed man that you are writing here
vergüenza tío que estás escribiendo aquí
with just a like look how the dog
con puro un like mira como el perro se
tries to bite its tail these adquin
trata de morder la cola estos adquin no
can't cover  what are em you
pueden tapar lo que son
know that dalan himself told me that
em sabes que dalan mismo me dijo que
this old jerk is a tremendous flirt
este viejo [__] es tremendo coquetín
that I am very flirtatious that I have
que sí que soy muy coqueto que le he
hooked up with everyone who is here
echo la caña a todos los que están aquí
in the chat
en el chat
[Music]
[Música]
there was one that I
había uno que
quoted here that answered me with a
cité aquí que me ha contestado con un
fish Ah, he's messing with
pes Ah es que se está metiendo con
Lorena he's telling him that he's a
Lorena le está diciendo que es un
fish I don't understand that very well Ah okay
pescado No entiendo muy bien eso Ah vale
look what it
mira
was Look at my answer What was it he got
ha sido Mirad mi respuesta Cuál ha sido
burned
se ha ardido
Look you're really burning up You're really burning up
Mira te ardes mucho Te ardes
[Laughter]
[Risas]
really [ __ ] But how
mucho [__] Pero qué
ridiculous and he's telling me place
ridiculo y me está diciendo lugare que
look at this that's
mire esto que está
exploding I saw your reaction of the
explotando he visto tu reacción del
lawyer saying Panchito to the other one I tell you
abogado diciendo [__] al otro te loo
that I laugh when you go crazy with the
que me río cuando te vuelves loco con el
level of the enemies that you've touched
nivel de los enemigos que te han tocado
not touched the best Mario the best
no tocado los mejores Mario los mejores
enemies in life pure [ __ ]
enemigos de la vida huevón puro
lolc Why are you so flirtatious my love
lolc Por qué eres tan coqueta mi amor
Gorgeous kisses Hey we have to
Besos guapísimos Oye tenemos que
recover the monetization of the rewind eh
recuperar la monetización del rewind eh
now I'll set a goal for you I'm going to
ahora os pongo un un objetivo lo voy a
set it while we listen to it you wouldn't
poniendo mientras que lo escuchamos no
understand it  Why I mean if you're mine
lo entenderías Por qué O sea si eres mía
skylar I have no problem if you're
skylar yo no tengo problema si eres
trans kisses Julio problem is bad to m I
trans besos Julio problema es mal a m
like skylar I think she has
skylar me cae bien
I don't think there's
creo que tiene yo yo no creo que haya
anyone on Twitter who has more stamina
persona en Twitter que tenga más aguante
than mine skylar what a jerk
que que mía skylar una huevonada
Poor thing jerk Ugh how they throw [ __ ]
Pobrecita huevón Uf cómo le tiran [__]
and hate at her she also throws a left-handed one
y hate también ella se tira una de zurda
that they are horrible be there She went over
que que son horribles sea ahí Se tiró
there She tweeted based But she
por ahí Se tiró un tuito basado Pero
had to put that the far right was
tenía que meter que la ultraderecha la
attacking her what does the
que la atacaba qué tiene que ver la
far right have to do with him the old man from Los
ultraderecha e el el viejo de Los
Panchitos incredible jerk incredible the
Panchitos increíble huevón increíble el
guy from Los
vio de Los
Panchitos
Panchitos asos
Latin American asos I got into a fight with a [ __ ]
latinoamericanos me pele con un maldito
40 year old gossip I got into a fight with
viejo de 40 años chismoso me peleé con
a [ __ ] 40
un maldito viejo de 40
year old man and he's three or whatever years older than
años y tiene tres o cu años más que
me but if he gets it if the
yo pero si le llega si te llega la
entry gets here to the crown
entrada aquí a la coronilla
RAE Put something on your balls with the money
RAE Ponte algo [__] con el dinero que
you take from people this guy who spends his time
te llevas de la gente este que se la
uploading my photos
pasa que se la pasa Subiendo fotos mías
on his damn Streams I got into a fight with a
en sus malditos Stream me peleé con un
[ __ ]
maldito enano
pedophile dwarf  this is good with the girlfriend of the
pedófilo este bueno con la novia del
pedophile dwarf With what girlfriend with everyone I
enano pedófilo Con qué novia con todo el
fought Well with what girlfriend he
mundo me peleé Pues con qué novia se ha
fought with the girlfriend of
peleado con la novia de
what with the penguin to of Penguin of
qué con el pingüino a de Penguin de
Penguin and the bug I offended sim he started to
Penguin y el [__] ofendí simo se puso a
upload to mount photos of me and I saw the
subir a montar fotos mías y yo veía las
photos that he uploaded mine it is more he uploads like the
fotos que subía mía es más sube como el
idiot he uploads like a clip of a video in
idiota sube como un clip de un video en
which I am making fun of his
el que yo me estoy burlando de sus
followers I am like that we have
seguidores Yo me estoy que que hemos
mounted photos of him or rather at what moment at what
montado fotos suy o sea en qué momento
moment these photos are mounted
en qué momento estas fotos son montadas
are you
eres
so we have mounted this but where
así que hemos montado esto pero dónde
is this mounted
está montado esto
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Where is it
Dónde está
mounted I am making fun of his
montado Yo me estoy burlando de sus
followers and the idiot uploads the clip and he doesn't
seguidores y el idiota sube el clip y no
know that it was in a Stream I am I
sabe que eso fue en un Stream yo me Yo
am making fun of his followers and the
me estoy burlando de sus seguidores y el
idiot guy Look at the recent searches he
idiota tío Mirad las búsquedas recientes
has eh he uploads the clip and he doesn't know that
que tiene eh sube el clip y no sabe que
it was in a Stream with me putting the face
eso fue en un Stream yo poniendo la cara
of his followers Look over here over here it
de sus seguidores Mira por aquí por aquí
makes me look at being published look here
me pone mir estar publicado mira aquí
Here I am here I am doing
Aquí yo estoy aquí yo estoy haciendo
Bravo bravo jav oliveira bravo bravo and
Bravo bravo jav oliveira bravo bravo y
the idiot puts that to say that I am
el idiota pone eso para decir que yo soy
uglier than him he is trying to say
más feo que él él está tratando de decir
that I am
que yo soy
ugly that no man that you are very
feo que no hombre que eres muy
handsome here what I put is the truth it makes me
guapo aquí lo que pongo es la verdad me
very envious in jail it had to
da mucha envidia en la cárcel tuvo que
be a
ser todo un
candy where I said to be ugly
caramelito donde he dicho que sea feo al
next to him that he is very handsome that he
lado de él que él es un guapísimo que él
is very handsome this [ __ ] look at this
es guapísimo esta [__] mire esta
[ __ ] please Penguin [ __ ] they are
[__] por favor de Penguin [__] le
going to close his twit too eh they are going to
van a cerrar el twit también eh le van a
close his twit too Penguin I mean
cerrar el twit también Penguin o sea él
in his mind in his mind he thinks that he
en su mente en su mente él cree que él
is a giga chat and I am the boyfriend of and
es un giga chat y yo soy el novio de y
Irene I am the boyfriend I Irene what happened
Irene yo soy el novio yo Irene qué pasó
with crypt because he went to
con crypt porque se fue a la
[ __ ] that paddle of jumping at the
[__] la paletada esa de saltar en el
airport Ah yeah no no
aeropuerto Ah sí
seriously seriously seriously he thinks
no no en serio en serio en serio él cree
that he is a giga chat right mandibulín
que él es un giga chat verdad mandibulín
is a gig chat and I am and I
es un gig chat y yo soy y yo
supposedly am here he grabs me Here
supuestamente soy aquí me agarra Aquí
this photo with it is not my best
esta foto con tampoco no es mi mejor
photo but well the photo that you have
foto pero bueno la foto que tú has
uploaded Javi changes his Cologne because wow
subido Javi cambia de Colonia porque
eh he came to play pad he was
vaya tela eh venía a jugar pad estaba
all sweaty all red all
estaba todo sudado todo rojo todo
swollen he says  here and this photo how good
hinchado pone aquí y esta foto que bueno
the photo that I that I that I that the
la foto que me que me que me que la
jail the photo of your police record from
cárcel la foto de tu ficha policial de
the jail RAE the photo of the
la cárcel RAE la foto de la
jail because you threatened a guy just like you're already
cárcel porque amenazaste un tío igual
starting to threaten
que ya me estás empezando a amenazar a
me and I'm going to report you I'm going to
mí y te voy a denunciar te voy a
report you got me mach where I was
denunciar me agarró maco donde estuve
less than 12 hours in a in a
menos de 12 horas en una en una
police station and these mongoloids say
comisaría y los mongólicos estos dicen
that they gave me a life sentence
que a mí me tieron cadena perpetua el
this idiot Look at this [ __ ] this
estúpido este Mira esta [__] esta
[ __ ] this [ __ ] this [ __ ] that
[__] esta [__] esta [__] que
CR this [ __ ] sea the
CR esta [__] mar el
penguin My God
pingüino Dios mío
sick but well he's cute so much [ __ ]
malito pero bueno está mico tanta [__]
that he's a giga chat This is his wife
que él es un giga chat Esta es la mujer
I reserve the comments about his
de él me reservo los comentarios acerca
wife not him
de la mujer de él no él
Supposedly if he hasn't reserved it for you if you
Supuestamente si no te la ha reservado
haven't reserved it winner in
si no te la has reservado ganador en la
life the
vida la
[Music]
[Música]
woman I don't understand What is it that he is I don't
mujer No entiendo Cuál es lo que está no
understand what is it that he is watching he
entiendo que es lo que está viendo le ha
liked the
gustado el
video he is the winner he is the supposed
vídeo él es el ganador él es el supuesto
winner
ganador
and and I I am The loser I am The
y y yo yo soy El perdedor yo soy El
loser in life I reserve the
perdedor en la vida me reservo los
comments ra I'm not going to comment on  your
comentarios ra no voy a opinar de tu
girlfriend didn't even see your girlfriend suffer or the
novia ni vio penar de tu novia ni de las
photos she uploads or what you're
fotos que sube ni de lo que tú estás
doing with her and Dallas also uploaded
haciendo con ella y Dallas también subi
a video of her saying buy buy
un vídeo de ella diciendo compren compr
and I'm not going to I'm not going to say anything about your
y yo no voy a no voy a decir nada de tu
girlfriend when my uncle the least sexist
novia cuando mi tío el menos machista
speaks at Christmas dinner xdd but it's
habla en la cena de Navidad xdd pero es
how ridiculous he's making a fool of himself I'm not going to
que qué ridículo está haciendo no voy a
do the same stop exposing the
hacer lo mismo deja de exponer a la
girl who will not be guilty I imagine
chavala que no tendrá culpa imagino de
what you're doing let's see is
lo que tú estés haciendo a ver está
with you I don't
contigo No lo
know I
sé yo
lost Oh no boy No no how I would
perdí Ay no muchacho No no cómo me
like to have his life change
gustaría tener la vida de él cambiar la
my wife for his
mujer mía por la de él
no but what is he
no pero qué está
talking about The loser no no we lost we
hablando El perdedor no no perdimos
lost
perdimos
dude we lost no no I don't want to be a
maco perdimos no no no quiero ser un
giga chat like
giga chat como
him I want to be a giga chat like him I
él yo quiero ser un giga chat como él o
mean according to him he won he won in life
sea según él é gano el gano en la vida
I don't I haven't said anything about your girlfriend or
yo no yo no he dicho nada de tu novia ni
you Well about you yes she is about you I'm
de ti Bueno de ti sí está de ti me estoy
laughing because you're making a
riendo porque estás haciendo tú el
fool of yourself but I haven't said any of that I mean
ridículo pero yo no he dicho nada de eso
I'm not going to start saying look
o sea yo no me voy a poner a decir mira
this is my girlfriend This is yours Look  my
esta es mi novia Esta es la tuya Mira mi
girlfriend is prettier than yours what do
novia es más guapa que la tuya que
you have account and so many clothes
tienes cuent y tantos panos
man that you probably have some
tío que seguramente tengas algún
problem with the things you eat for breakfast
problemilla con las cosas que desayunas
and the behavior you have
y el comportamiento que tienes
surely at 4 and something stop you
seguramente ya con 4 y pico paro te
start to have problems for you to be
empieces a salir los problemillas para
doing this he wins in
que estés haciendo esto el gano en la
life I am a
vida Yo Soy un
loser That is the That is the level of
perdedor Esa es la Ese es el nivel de la
people that I am with that you have been
gente con la que me estoy que has estado
in jail for threatening that you are
en la cárcel por amenazar que estás
threatening now what the [ __ ] do I care what
amenazando ahora qué [__] me da igual
dress your girlfriend wears or how
el bestido que se ponga tu novia o lo
pretty your girlfriend is according to you
guapa que sea tu novia según tú
fighting crypto Circus that level that
peleando cripto Circo ese el nivel ese
level no it doesn't make any kind of sense
nivel no no tiene ningún tipo de sentido
But well it doesn't make any kind of
Pero bueno no tiene ningún tipo de
sense supposedly he won dude
sentido supuestamente el ganó huevón
supposedly won but if I win every time I
supuestamente ganó pero si gano cada vez
tweet you I
que te pongo un
post two tweets I post two tweets and I
tweet pongo dos tweet pongo dos tweet y
already beat you And now they're going to close your
ya te gané Y ahora te van a cerrar la
Twitch account
cuenta de Twitch
too man you're not very successful
también hombre muy triunfador no eres
when you have to be kicking around
cuando tienes que estar pateando casito
no no but he's not successful at all
no no pero triunfador no es para nada
but he doesn't even have a
pero es que no tiene ni siquiera una
person by his side who loves him and says
persona al lado que le quiera y diga
churra leave the Twitter account a few
churra deja la cuenta de Twitter unos
days don't go live today because you
días no te pongas en directo hoy que no
're not up for going live Well he
estás para ponerte en directo Bueno ya
wasn't on the day of the space day
no lo estuvo el día del el día del space
for
por
God's sake the
Dios el día del
space day the ridiculous thing he
space el día del space el ridículo que
made with the bmar and shouting no no no no he's not
hizo con lo del bmar y gritando no no no
a person you remember Well yes
no es una persona que te acuerda Bueno
yes you won you won Javi it's okay it's okay it's okay it's okay
sí sí ganaste ganaste Javi está bien
what do you think
está bien está bien está bien qué opinas
the sect of Uh I saw the video he
la secta de Uh yo vi el video que le
made but the problem with believing
hizo pero es que el problema de creerle
the problem with believing this
a el problema de creerle a a
professor mager is that
este al profesor mager que es que el
professor Mag puts a lot of pickle in all
profesor Mag mete mucho piquete en todos
the videos So no no there's a
los videos Entonces no no hay un video
serious video out there the one I think the one I saw
serio por ahí el que creo que el que vi
was the turbo plan Turbo is
fue el turbo plan Turbo se un
a serious video
un video serio
of but dude But how are you going to clean up a
del pero tío Pero cómo vas a lavar un
turboplane video serious videos no no the one who
turboplane vídeos serios no no el que lo
makes it serious Turbo plan but don't you see that
hace serio Turbo plan pero no te ves que
no raed starts taking pictures of
no raed se pone a sacarle fotos a
women in the pool it's a Cos if he
mujeres en la piscina es una Cos si
has his girlfriend who has to go
tiene a su novia que tiene que ir de
green tail exactly RAE If you
rabo verde exactamente RAE Si tan
're so successful don't go taking pictures of
triunfador eres no vayas haciéndo fotos
the
a las
good ones that magu trust me if I didn't want to  come
buena esa magu fíate si no he querido
in look at you if I didn't want to come in I haven't even
entrar fíjate tú si no he querido entrar
thought about that it's true guy you're
que no he pensado ni eso es verdad tío
such a winner what are you doing
tan triunfador que eres que haces
taking pictures in the pool without
haciéndole fotos en la piscina sin
the neighbors' consent they're going to
consentimiento a las vecinas que te van
put you in jail again Turbo plan fan come on you're going to
a meter preso otra vez fan de Turbo plan
end up in jail I'm telling you
vamos vas a acabar preso ya te lo digo
if you have all the tickets
yo si es que llevas todas las papeletas
if you're buying tickets every
si es que estás comprando papeletas cada
half hour from Colorado East not from
media hora del Colorado Este no del
Colorado says wings that you did
Colorado dice alas que tú le hiciste
a lot of harm to him
mucho daño
Dallas Dallas What harm is that
Dallas Dallas Qué daño va a sufrir ese
son of a [ __ ] going to suffer that guy is heartless no he doesn't
hijo de [__] ese tipo es un desalmado no
have any kind of it's true
no tiene ningún tipo de de es verdad
But if turboplane that this is a
Pero si turboplane que este es un
scammer sentim doesn't say that having children
estafador sentim no dice que tener hijos
is a mistake that relationships that
es un error que las relaciones que las
relationships don't exist and that
relaciones de pareja no existen y que
everyone has to be promiscuous
todo el mundo tiene que ser un promiscuo
making ships with everyone because they
hacer buques con todo el mundo porque no
can't stay faithful to not even
puede mantenerse fiel a ni siquiera
mention this guy eh I mean Dallas this
menciona este tío eh o sea Dallas este
guy doesn't even mention it eh his girlfriend he doesn't
tipo ni lo menciona eh a su novia no
say that friends don't exist come on a
dice que los amigos no existen dale a un
heartless person is a person who has no
desalmado es una persona que no tiene
soul no he can't feel any kind of
alma no no puede sentir ningún tipo de
regret or pain or empathy anything he doesn't have
pesar o dolor o empatía nada no tiene
any kind of feeling he doesn't want  not even
ningún tipo de sentimiento no quiere ni
his family he doesn't love his own
a su familia no quiere ni a su propia
family because you were sucking his dick with both
familia pues le comías el rabo a dos
cheeks aarse two newscasts to the
carrillos aarse dos telediarios al
unarmed totally totally [ __ ]
desarmado totalmente totalmente [__]
Well go on, he didn't say he's the best
Pues anda que no decía es la mejor
person I've ever met he wrote a
persona que he conocido escribió un
book to throw [ __ ] at his own
libro para tirarle [__] a sus propios
parents Oh Ray how lazy I mean I wrote
padres Ay Ray qué pereza o sea escribi
a
un
schizophrenic book
libro esquizofrénico
Dallas this guy is crazy a psychopath he's
Dallas este tipo es un loco un psicópata
like he's to tie him up they don't tie him up
es tipo está de amarrar no lo amarran
because they don't know where to
porque no saben dónde
get him but the guy is totally
conseguirlo pero el tipo está tot
absolutely crazy him and Javi Oliveira
absolutamente loco él y Javi oliveira
also have
también tien problemas
mental problems what do I do Olira has
mentales yo qué hago olira tiene
problems mental problems I mean the
problemas problemas mentales o sea las
people who think that Ja Oliveira is a
personas que crean que Ja oliveira un
normal guy look at the people
tipo normal vean ustedes a las personas
who are his contemporaries or I know we are
que son contemporáneas con él o se que
40 years old Let's see which of us
tenemos 40 años A ver cuál de nosotros
behaves like that guy behaves none none none r
se comporta como se comporta ese tipo
there I agree with you
ninguno ninguno ninguno r ahí te doy la
normal man no no but there he
razón hombre normal no no pero ahí sí
is right eh No they don't behave like
tiene razón eh No no se comportan como
me he eats himself I mean the
yo se papea solo o sea el
guy the guy is totally and absolutely
tipo el tipo está total y absolutamente
out of place for his
desubicado de su
age just look at the guy's serop I
edad solamente vean el serop del tipo o
mean the guy has a bit of a
sea el tipo tiene un serop un poco de
doll's serop  he got a shitty Disney tattoo 40 years old the
muñeco se tatuó [__] Disney 40 años la
baby I mean eh it's not in line with his
guagüita O sea eh no está acorde a su
mentality he's not 40 years old mentally he's 20 years old
mentalmente no tiene 40 años mentalmente
he thinks he's 20 years old
tiene 20 años él cree que tiene 20 años
and that he is this that he is Sprint the
y que é le es este que él es Sprint el
dream I think he had a
sueño Yo creo que él tenía un sueño
frustrated dream of being a streamer of
frustrado de ser de ser streamer de
these games and just like
estos de juegos y tal y como
[Laughs]
[Risas]
no I wanted to be a gamer dude I wanted to be a
no yo quería ser Gamer tío yo quería ser
gamer [ __ ] and you have condemned me this
Gamer [__] y me habéis condenado esta
[ __ ] [ __ ] of
[__] [__] de aguant
crazy people not like you Ray who looks very
locos no como tú Ray que se te ve muy
mature to be 15 years old could have
maduro para tener 15 años pudo pues se
dedicated himself to defamation he took the
dedicó a la difamación tomó el camino
easy way he took the path of prostitutes
fácil tomó el camino de las prostitutas
the one of messing with people defaming people and
el de meterse con gente difamar gente y
going to invent stories about people
va inventarse historia de la gente
getting into the private lives of
meterse en la vida Privada de los
famous people [ __ ] is the easy way to
famosos [__] es el camino camino fácil
bring him and get
de para traerle y llamar la
exclusive attention ra he throws Jai for
atención exclusiva ra le tira Jai por
having Disney things it
tener cosas de Disney
's not weird Marshall doesn't it seem a little
no es raro Marshall no te parece un poco
strange to you it seems to me that no to me it does
raro a mí me parece que que no a mí si
seem strange men to me it didn't seem
me parece raro men a m no te pareció
strange when you were sucking our [ __ ]
raro cuando nos comías la [__]
RAE but  if you came that you treated us like we were
RAE pero si venías que nos tratabas como
you say you saw Leonardo
si fuéramos tú dices que viste Leonardo
and Caprio at a party Well to me in
y caprio en una fiesta Pues a mí al
Dallas he treated us like we were
Dallas nos trataba como si fuéramos
Leonardo
Leonardo
DiCaprio, no, not the screw-up all
DiCaprio sea no la rosca todo el [__]
day long he appeared here on the Stream every
día aparecía aquí en los Stream todos
day begging for attention it seemed like you
los días rogando atención parecía que
were talking to a fan with an idol I
estabas hablando con un fan con un ídolo
find it weird the
me parece raro se ardió la
little girl got burned now if he dedicated himself to doing
nenita ahora si él se dedicara a hacer
reviews of toys and Disney things it
reviews de juguetes y de cosas de Disney
's perfect it's perfect if his channel
está perfecto está perfecto si su canal
was Look, I'm going to do reviews of
fuera Mira voy a hacer reviews de
Disney movies or I'm going to do
películas de Disney o voy a hacer
reviews of Disney toys I'm going to
reviews de de los juguetes Disney voy a
show the premieres the latest
mostrar los estrenos los últimos
toys the latest Legos and things that
juguetes los últimos Legos y vainas que
came out with all the Disney themes
salieron con toda la temática de Disney
excellent dude what better serop than that
excelente huevón qué mejor serop que ese
but you can't go talking about old women
pero no puedes ir a hablar de viejas de
65 years old and older gossip about the
65 años en adelante chismes de de de la
world with some dolls
farándula con un poco de muñecos ahí
back there [ __ ] that don't fit Ah okay okay
atrás huevones que no pegan Ah vale vale
family We have to change the scenery
familia Tenemos que cambiar el escenario
eh that doesn't fit even with gum it's true
eh que no pega ni con chicle es verdad
oh I think my girlfriend arrived I think
ay creo que llegó mi novia creo que
my princess arrived I have those things and I
llegó mi princesa Yo tengo esas cosas y
don't like them but for me not  it's weird
no me gustan pero para mí no es raro
well you're weird Marshall you know you
bueno Tú eres raro Marshall Tú sabes que
're
eres
weird he's going to applaud maduro because s the
raro va aplaudir a maduro porque s el
maduro comic also fused with
cómic de maduro además fusionado con
delox creating the
delox creando el
dalel he's going to applaud
dalel va a aplaudir a
maduro a tvh there
maduro un tvh
will be there the canine these fascists do not
habr habr el canino estos fascistas no
give up in their assault against Venezuela
se rinden en su asalto contra Venezuela
this is real he's going to applaud
esto es real va a aplaudir a
maduro this is real [ __ ] this is real I mean this is
maduro esto es real [__] esto es real
for real the real
o sea esto es de verdad el verdadero
comic I don't believe this stuff is real
cómic yo no creo que esta vaina sea real
this is
esto es
real [ __ ] [ __ ] what is
real la putísima madre [__] Qué es
this [ __ ] dude this can't be
esta [__] huevón Esto no puede ser
real [ __ ] this has to be me or so we're we're
real [__] Esto me tien que estar o sea
talking take that
que estamos estamos hablando toma de que
the one who writes the maduro comic is
el que escribe el cómic de maduro está
aware of the world of gossip of course and
pendiente del mundo del salseo claro y
of the famous people the gossip of the
de de los famosos del salseo de los
important ones the gossip
importantes el salseo
Gallego we're talking also the one who
Gallego estamos hablando además el que
made the comic eh about maduro I don't know
ha hecho el cómic eh de maduro yo no sé
who it will be okay it will be someone he
quién será vale será una persona de su
trusts but he has joined heads if you
confianza pero ha unido las cabezas si
notice between people who have
os dais cuenta entre personas que han
had the problems between them dal
tenido los los problemas entre ellos dal
lelo or in other words Dallas with delox and Ricky with
lelo o sea Dallas con delox y Ricky con
Javi I mean he did it conscientiously  you
Javi o sea lo ha hecho a conciencia
know, I mean, it's someone who is into
sabes o sea es alguien que está metido
Lore at that level, I mean, the one who
en el Lore de ese nivel o sea el que
writes the Maduro comic is always
escribe el cómic de maduro está todos
aware of the gossip. Well,
los días pendiente del del salseo Pues
like you, the moment I uploaded
como tú que tú al instante de yo subir
every photo that I've been uploading during
cada foto que he estado subiendo durante
my vacation you immediately knew what
mis vacaciones sabías inmediatamente Qué
photo I had
foto había
uploaded like a fan, he can't really be a [ __ ], he really ca
subido como un fan no puede ser [__]
n't be an
de verdad de verdad ya no puede ser
idiot anymore, he can't be a [ __ ] anymore, he ca
huevón es que ya no puede ser [__] es
n't be all the things that he
que ya no puede ser todas las cosas que
follows the account Why dasas is
sigue a la cuenta Por qué dasas es
trending RAE you follow the account Why
tendencia RAE sigues a la cuenta Por qué
dasas is trending, I don't even follow it
dasas es tendencia no la sigo ni yo
ra and you do to stay informed
ra y tú sí para estar informad
look there you
dito mira ahí lo
have it ra the dog is saying right now
tenéis ra el perro está diciendo ahora
that he's going to report me, report me, report me
mismo que te me va a denunciar que me
Why Because I
denuncie que me denuncie Por qué Porque
told him that the woman was a vagrant, he didn't
le dije que la mujer era un vagre no
know that was a crime, it's a crime to
sabía que eso era un delito es un delito
tell him that the woman was a vagrant, he got
decirle que la mujer era un vagre se
so angry and yes, he can say about me that
ardió tanto é si puede decir de mí que
supposedly I was annoying my
supuestamente yo le caía [__] a mi
landlord and a bunch of nonsense that
casero y un montón de barbaridades que
I don't say about you ra that she says
yo no lo digo de ti ra que lo dice la
police page that I'm not saying it raet that
policía que yo no lo digo raet que lo
the police page says your
dice la página de la policía que tu
version is that you went to report a
versión es que fuiste a denunciar a un
guy who owed you money and they made a mistake
tío que te debía dinero y se equivocaron
but the police's plan is to put you in
pero que la de la policía es meterte en
jail for the weekend and keep you there
la cárcel el fin de semana y tenerte ahí
and you're awaiting trial that I'm not
y estás a la espera de juicio que yo no
saying about me and I respond with a
digo sobre mí y yo le respondo con una
dig and she starts crying with a dig
pullita y sale a llorar con una
ra you're literally threatening
pullita ra literalmente estás amenazando
saying until you're going to mess with a
diciendo hasta que te vas a meter con un
5 year old child Of course I'm going to
niño de 5 años Claro que te voy a
report you as soon as you told me today a
denunciar en cuanto me contaste hoy un
lawyer from the United States tells me we
abogado de Estados Unido que me diga le
can do this we can do that
podemos hacer esto le podemos hacer lo
other I'm going to do it Well they're
otro lo voy a hacer Bueno la cuenta de
going to take down your twitter account for sure with the
twit te la van a tirar seguro con las
atrocities they're saying you can't
barbaridades que están diciendo no
and of course I'm going to report you if you
puedes y claro que te voy a denunciar si
already have a legal problem or whatever you
ya tienes un problema legal o los que
have is that you're looking to be
tengas es que te estás buscando que te
kicked out of the United States Of course
echen de los Estados Unidos Claro que
yes the dig threatening an entire
sí la pullita amenazar a toda una
family of course but it's been going on for a lot of
familia claro pero lleva ya un montón de
days Pin Pin and every now and then I
días Pin Pin y yo de vez en cuando pues
mark a response So funny to
marco una una respuesta Así graciosa a
with four words or we see it here but of
con cuatro palabras o lo vemos aquí pero
course  He's
claro ya es que está
crazy now he's going to report me,
loco de una vez que me va a denunciar
report me where he's going to report me
que me denuncie dónde me va a denunciar
here in the United States come Sure,
aquí en Estados Unidos que venga Claro
sure where am I going to report you In
claro dónde te voy a denunciar En
Chipiona where you live in the United
chipiona dónde vives tú en Estados
States where you commit your crimes in the United
Unidos dónde cometes tus delitos en
States Well of course it
Estados Unidos Pues claro que sí se
can be done you haven't thought of that do
puede hacer es que no has caído en eso
you think that because we're in another country I ca
te crees que porque estamos en otro país
n't report you Of course I
No te puedo denunciar Claro que
can so let him come come and report me
puedo pues que venga venga y me denuncie
but let him bring Dallas right now let him
pero que se traiga de una vez a Dallas
bring Dallas right now what let him
que se traiga de una vez a Dallas qué qu
bring Dala to me let him leave Dala have you
me traiga dala que que deje a dala la
seen the [ __ ] Dala Or what's
has vicho la [__] dala O qué es lo que
wrong with you that I'm
te pasa con
not going to take
que no me voy a llevar a
Dallas let him report you but let him take me
Dallas que te denuncie pero que me lleve
to Dallas What are you talking about what the
a Dallas Pero qué estás hablando qué
[ __ ] does this guy have for breakfast What
[__] es lo que Desayuna este tío Qué
substance does he take
sustancia toma
Oh well let him report me but let him
Ah bueno que me denuncie pero que me
bring Dallas I'm not going to take you
traiga Dallas que que no te voy a llevar
to Dallas Dallas no, he hasn't mentioned you for I do
a Dallas que Dallas no no te menciona de
n't even know how many months I still
hace no sé ni los meses que yo todavía
answer him on some tweets but let Dallas
algún twit le respondo pero que Dallas
not come to Dallas for  here I have
no de una se traiga a Dallas para acá
some text messages some nice little
que tenga unos mensajitos de texto un
text messages, very
mensajitos de texto este bonitos muy
nice that if they took me
lindos que si a mí me llevaron 12 horas
to the police station for 12 hours they call it back
a la comisaría d se lo llan palc atrás
with the messages that he sent me
con los mensajes que me mandó a mí
because in no message did I threaten to
porque yo en ningún mensaje amené de
kill anyone in any message I threatened to
muerte a nadie en ningún mensaje amenac
kill anyone and with everything and it's that they
de muerte a nadie y con todo y es que a
put you in jail RAE for
ti te han metido en la cárcel RAE por
threats the police page says it
amenazas lo pone la página de la
to Dalas No to you yes you
policía que a Dalas No a ti sí es que no
are not understanding it really that they
lo estás entendiendo de verdad
tried to screw me here with the law and
eso intentaron joderme aquí con la ley y
no and Here I am sitting so let him
no y Aquí estoy sentadito entonces que
report me come here make
me denuncie venga para acá que se eche
the trip here to Miami bring
el viaje para acá para Miami se traiga
one to Daniel to Daniel to uranet he
una a Daniel a Daniel a uranet se lo
can bring him because he doesn't even have a visa he is
puede traer porque ni visa tiene está
angry because he yes I have to measure my
picado porque él sí yo tengo que medirme
words with them I have to
con las palabras para con ellos yo tengo
be a very respectful person
que ser una persona demasiado respetuosa
and I have to measure my words
y tengo que medirme con las palabras que
with that damn bastard
tengo hacia el maldito desgraciado ese
But he can mess with me
Pero él sí se puede meter conmigo
call me a convict inmate tell me that you are
decirme convicto recluso decirme qu eres
a
un
inmate I'm not telling you anything
recluso que yo no te estoy diciendo nada
nor am I messing with your girlfriend or
ni me estoy metiendo con tu novia ni con
your children or your father or your
tus hijos ni con tu padre ni con tu
anyone I'm telling you that he's in
nadie te estoy diciendo que está en la
jail that you've been in jail period
cárcel que has estado en la cárcel punto
and you spend all [ __ ] day
y te pegas todo el [__] día poniendo
tweeting Of course you do they do
tweet Claro que
n't understand the difference I piss
sí es que no entienden la diferencia meo
what his lining is coming out I give him one little
lo que le sale el [__] yo le meto una
dig that piece of clown and he
sola pullita el pedazo de payaso ese y
starts crying right away suck
se pone a llorar de una vez que chupe
Because I'm still starting mind you I
Porque todavía estoy empezando ojo que
'm only just starting I
es que sola ente estoy empezando se lo
told him today and I [ __ ] myself laughing I
dije hoy y me cagado en la risa se los
told them I told him he posts a baby on his
dije le dije llega a publicar en su
Instagram And he says the baby is
Instagram un bebé Y dice que el bebé es
his and I'm going to [ __ ] I'm going to make fun
de él y me voy a venir me voy a burlar
of the [ __ ] baby and it feels like [ __ ] to me and I
del [__] bebé y me sabe a [__] y me
but it's not that you're stupid it's that you're
pero es que no eres vasado es que estás
making a fool of yourself you know so much
haciendo el el ridículo sabea muchísima
[ __ ] they know [ __ ] about everything them
[__] a ellos les saa [__] todo ellos
not all Venezuelans are like that Javi
no todos los venezolanos somos así Javi
sorry Hahaha man I imagine I
perdón Jajaja hombre imagino
imagine he thinks it's funny he thinks it's
imagino cree que es chistosito él cree
funny Oh how funny no Oh how
que es chistosito Ay qué risa no Ay qué
funny to go laugh there with a mapará  of
risa ir a reírme allá con un mapará de
mentally [ __ ] people who are the ones who
retrasados mentales que son los que lo
see him who don't have the brains for this they
ven a él que no tienen cerebro para esto
don't have the brains for this it's
no tienen cerebro para esto no les da
impossible for them it's impossible impossible Ah yes he
imposible es imposible imposible Ah sí
can say whatever he wants about
puede decir lo que le dé la gana sobre
me then they all come out to cry Oh But
mí entonces salen todos a llorar Ay Pero
why do you mess with the family Ah my
por qué te metes con la familia Ah mi
family has my family yes they have to
familia tiene mi familia sí tiene que
hear that I am an inmate a
escuchar que yo soy un recluso un
convict don't threaten people so they
convicto no amenaces a la gente para que
don't put you in jail and your family won't
no te metan en la cárcel y tu familia no
have to hear it but nobody is
tendrá que escucharlo pero nadie se está
messing with the family they are
metiendo con la familia se están
messing with you because you don't stop All
metiendo contigo porque no paras Todos
the [ __ ] days of making things up that
los [__] días de inventarte cosas que
you made up a story about some
te inventaste una historia de unos
hitmen to talk to you with the uncle
sicarios para hablarte con el delo tío
What a
Qué
shame my nephews Yes they have to
vergüenza mis sobrinos Sí tienen que
hear that I am a swindler that I
escuchar que yo soy un estafador que yo
am this and that I am that I mean my
soy esto y que soy lo otro o sea mis
nephews Yes they have to put up with everything that
sobrinos Sí tienen que calarse todo lo
that piece of
que diga ese pedazo de fracasado
marginal failure slanderer and slanderer says my
marginal difamador y calumniador mi
nephew yes they have to put up with it and what
sobrino sí se lo tienen que calar y yo
am I telling him I am telling
que le estoy diciendo a yo se lo estoy
the woman I am telling him
diciendo a la mujer estoy diciendo a él
directly I am telling him damn
directamente estoy diciendo a él maldito
failure in his [ __ ] life in his [ __ ]
fracasado en su [__] vida en su [__]
life I could not get close nor to a dude nor
vida pude acercarse ni ni a huevón ni a
kilometers from having a jeeva like
kilómetros de tener una jeeva como
Agustina in her [ __ ] vi neither you of your
Agustina en su [__] vi ni tú de tus
neighbors RAE nor you to your neighbors you
vecinas RAE ni tú a tus vecinas le
have to take pictures of her without
tienes que hacer fotos sin
consent to your neighbors
consentimiento a tus vecinas
RAE takes pictures of her in a
RAE le hace fotos en
bikini without
bikini sin
consent that I'm going to report you
consentimiento que te voy a denunciar
RAE that I'm going to report you Do not
RAE que te voy a denunciar No te
worry that I will inform myself of everything
preocupes que me voy a informar de todo
that can be done life and that is the
lo que se puede hacer vida y esa es la
frustration that those envious clowns have
frustración que tienen esos payasos
envious pieces of [ __ ] I mean
envidiosos envidiosos de [__] o sea de
suddenly the story is that I am
repente la historia es que yo tengo
envious of his girlfriend but RAE idiot what is he
envidia de su novia pero RAE idioso qué
going to say that it is V said that I do not know that he
va a decir que es V decía que no sé qué
has more money That all those pieces
tiene más plata Que todos esos pedazos
of youtubers together do not have to do
de youtubers juntos no tiene que hacer
anything in their life has his life figured out has his
nada en su vida tiene la vida resuelta
[ __ ] life figured out people with
tiene la [__] vida resuelta gente de
money what are they going to say has traveled
billete qué van a decir ha viajado
traveled all over the world city that I
recorrido todo el mundo ciudad que le
call him city that she has gone to and has not
nom ciudad a la que ha ido y no ha
had to go with men or be
tenido que ir con hombres ni que le
paid by boyfriends or [ __ ] her family
paguen novios ni una [__] su familia
her dad and her mom what is that
su papá y su mamá qué va a decir ese
piece of failure of my girlfriend going to say he who
pedazo de fracasado de mi novia él quién
is saying anything  of the girlfriend who is
está diciendo nada de la novia que está
crazy the other damn sadist who
loco el otro maldito sádico que lo que
did was sadize her on Instagram every
hacía era sadar la por Instagram todas
night while she was lying next to
las noches estando ella acostada al lado
me in in in France and the other loser
mío en en en Francia y el otro fracasado
stalks jerking off every night for
stalkea pajeándose todas las noches por
Agustina what are those sons of [ __ ] going to say about
Agustina qué van a decir esos hijos de
me what were they going to say brother that they can
[__] de mí qué iban a decir brother que
handle pressure facts that he can handle
aguanten presión factos que aguante
pressure he likes to be funny with
presión le gusta ir de chistoso con un
some people that you don't see the
poco de gente que ustedes no ven las
disgusting things that those people say to
asquerosidades que me dice esa gente a
me on Twitter and I have to put
mí en Twitter y yo me las tengo que
up
calar yo me cago de la risa yo hice el
with them I'm laughing my ass off I made the tweet and they all came out Ah ah they didn't even understand the tweet I said it's not real look look at the tweet let's see the tweet let's see who those are I just arrived in one
esos Acabo de llegar en uno uno que se
called Javi Oliveira look at the tweet I
llama Javi oliveira Miren el tweet les
give you the logic of this [ __ ] old man
pongo la lógica del viejo [__] este
and I say that they are some gig chat and
y pongo que ellos son unos gig chat y
that Agustina and I are the ugly ones according to
que Agustina y yo somos los feos según
him look at this [ __ ] please this
él miren está esta [__] por favor esta
[ __ ] Look at this [ __ ] bro and in the
[__] Mira esta [__] bro y en los
comments the followers of osti
comentarios Los Seguidores de osti le
go to him  to close the Twitch eh that really
van a cerrar el Twitch eh que de verdad
in his dissociated mind in his mind in his
en su mente disociada en su mente en su
mind totally dissociated with
mente disociada totalmente con la
reality completely and absolutely
realidad completa y absolutamente
distorted they are the gigachat and
distorsionada ellos son los gigachat y
we are the ugly ones dude it's like that I mean
nosotros somos los feos huevón es así O
that guy really thinks I mean
sea ese tipo cree que de verdad O sea
Agustina and I are catfish and he is
Agustina y yo somos unos bagres y él es
beautiful with his wife he is a beauty
hermoso con la mujer él es una hermosura
this [ __ ] [ __ ] I don't understand
esta [__] [__] yo no entiendo por
why he hasn't taken Bradley
qué no le ha quitado el trabajo a bradle
Cooper's job [ __ ] Brad Pit he
Cooper [__] a Brad Pit él
supposedly he He is the gigachat and I
supuestamente él Él es el gigachat y yo
do it here and still the
lo hago aquí y todavía los retrasados
mentally [ __ ] people who follow him the
mentales que lo siguen a él los
mentally [ __ ] people who follow him
retrasados mentales que lo siguen a él
believe that he says ha Well you
creen que dice ja Pues Tú solito te has
answered yourself inmate Well I am an inmate
contestado recluso Bueno yo soy recluso
because his wife is a [ __ ] vagre Ah I am
pues su mujer es un [__] vagre Ah yo soy
an inmate Ah I am an inmate I am in
un recluso Ah yo soy recluso yo estoy
prison right now well his wife
recluido en este momento bueno su mujer
is a [ __ ] catfish next to mine his
es un maldito bagre al lado de la mía su
wife is a [ __ ] catfish And what's going on and
mujer es un maldito bagre Y qué pasa y
what's he going to say cry to me she looks like a
qué va a decir llore a mí me parece un
catfish I wouldn't touch her even with a
bagre yo no la toco ni con un puntero
laser pointer or with  a laser pointer ae but it's
láser ni con un puntero láser ae pero es
that your neighbors either what a shame
que a tus vecinas tampoco qué vergüenza
dude in the [ __ ] would have a chance to even
tío en la [__] tendría chance ni
approach me by my standards
acercarse a mí por mis estándares
Unfortunately for me by their
Lamentablemente para mí por sus
standards man of course son a
estándares hombre claro hijo un
mental hospital is not going to come near my girlfriend will
manicomio no se va a acercar mi novia
never hook up this girlfriend his wife his
nunca ligar esta novia su mujer suya
wife his a [ __ ] catfish and with the
esposa suya un maldito bagre y con la
distorted reality says the one who
realidad distorsionada lo dice el que
says he went to report but in
dice que fue a denunciar pero en
reality he threatened me with another person and
realidad amenazo de m otra persona y por
that's why they put him in jail XD clo the
eso lo metieron preso XD clo la cuenta
Twitch account we are going to report it eh I
de Twitch se la vamos a reportar eh o
mean you have to tell me send me the
sea me tenéis que decir mandarme el
link there in the chat because
enlace por ahí en en el chat porque
obviously I am going to report this I
evidentemente esto sí lo voy a reportar
never usually report eh you know I never
nunca suelo reportar eh sabéis que nunca
report for fun And such But of course this This we are
reporto a coña Y tal Pero claro esto
going to report I think it is
Esto sí lo vamos a reportar creo que es
logical and what if someone tells me where it is because I have
lógico y Y si si alguien me dice dónde
never known where the Twitch thing is
es que nunca he sabido dónde es lo del
eh put the link there in the chat
Twitch eh poner ahí el enlace en el chat
okay I think he takes drugs my taking
vale Yo creo que se droga a mí que se
drugs is his problem okay but I think we
drogue es su problema vale pero yo creo
are going to report this Eh This
que esto sí lo vamos a reportar Eh Esto
yes I mean I never report eh I think you
sí O sea nunca reporto eh creo que me
know me  enough but I think we
conocéis de sobra pero creo que aquí
can agree here that we are
estaremos de acuerdo en que esto lo
going to report this on both Twitter and
vamos a reportar tanto el Twitter como
Twitch okay already out of the way I
el como el Twitch vale Ya fuera parte lo
leave it here said any lawyer you
dejo aquí dicho cualquier abogado que
know from the United States okay
conozcáis de Estados Unidos vale
tell me because we are going there for him he
decírmelo porque vamos allá por él él
wants legal problems Well he's going to have them he's going to have them
quiere problemas legales Pues los va a
buying tickets he's going to have them I
tener va comprando papeletas los va a
think we can
tener yo creo que aquí estaremos de
agree here that it has to be done no
acuerdo en que sí hay que hacerlo no
family and Dallas should report him on
familia y Dallas debería reportarle el
Twitch I think Dallas is not even
Twitch yo creo que Dallas ni se está
aware of this but oh but yes
enterando de esto pero e pero sí
obviously this man is crazy
evidentemente sí está loco este hombre
I don't know what he has for breakfast What substance do you
Yo no sé qué Desayuna Qué sustancia
take okay Okay well if you could put
tomas vale Vale pues si me podéis poner
the link please in the chat and tell me
el enlace por favor en el chat y decirme
where to report it someone who knows we
dónde se reporta alguien que sepa lo
report it because this person is going too far he's
reportamos porque este persona se está
going too far and we have to
pasando se está pasando y y hay que
put a control on him okay I'm not going
ponerle un un controlo vale yo no me voy
to mess with the girlfriend I'm not going to give my opinion if she
a meter con la novia no voy a opinar si
's pretty if she's ugly I have my thoughts
es guapa si es fea tengo mi pensamiento
obviously he's just exposing her
evidentemente él solo la está exponiendo
okay I think there's no need to even
vale Yo creo que no hace falta ni ni ni
talk about it No but not about that but he
hablar No pero ya no de eso sino que él
himself is not happy with his relationship
mismo no está contento con su relación
when when he's  harassing his
cuando cuando está acosando a sus
neighbors and taking pictures of them you know he's
vecinas y haciéndoles fotos me entiendes
harassing women eh in the pool
está acosando a mujeres eh en la piscina
of the Urbanization and taking pictures and
de la Urbanización y haciéndole fotos y
sending them to his friends you know So they're
mandándose elas a su amigos me entiendes
going to put you in jail
O sea que te van a meter en la cárcel
buddy they're going to put you in jail you
colega que te van a meter en la cárcel
know But well for now we'll
me entiendes Pero bueno de momento eso
fix that okay but for now on
lo arreglaremos vale pero de momento el
Twitch if you could please give me
Twitch si me podéis poner porfa
the link where the [ __ ] we have to go
e el enlace dónde [__] nos tenemos que
Well I have no [ __ ] idea
meter Pues yo no tengo ni [__] idea
eh And what is he going to say he's going to
eh Y qué va a decir qué me va a
report me for saying he's a catfish he's
denunciar por decir que es un bagre es
a catfish horrible it's horrible what is he going to
un bagre espantosa es espantosa qué va a
say report report report for saying that he
decir denuncia denunci denunciar por
's a catfish if I say
decir que está un bagre si a m yo digo
whatever the hell the lining of my ass comes out
lo que a mí me salga el [__] del culo
of this [ __ ] [ __ ] who should
de este maldito desgraciado que debería
disappear from the internet The disgusting
desaparecer de internet El asqueroso
old disgusting wanker wanker [ __ ]
viejo asqueroso [__] [__] huevón
talking says Carlos I already reported him on
hablando dice Carlos ya le reporté el
Twitch but give me the link please
Twitch pero ponerme el enlace porfa
give me the link because I don't know where the
ponerme el enlace que yo no sé dónde
[ __ ] he does it give me the link because yes you're
[__] se hace ponerme el enlace porque sí
going to allow me But this
esto sí me vais a permitir Pero esto
yes the  5 and 6 7 10 in the morning talking
sí las 5 y 6 7 10 de la mañana hablando
to 13 year old girls damn sadist [ __ ]
con niñas de 13 años maldito sádico [__]
old sadist I am a sucker for ass you have
viejo sádico Yo soy chupac culo t tiene
an alert on Twitch Look at the alert he
una alerta en Twitch Mirad la alerta que
has on Twitch he is completely gone
tiene en Twitch está completamente ido
eh he
eh
says if he has a traitor he should treat them
dice al si tiene traita que se los trate
but you are taking too long to report it I
pero ya estás tardando en reportarlo yo
think so eh you know that I do not report and
creo que sí eh sabéis que no reporto y
that I do not care but of course I think that
que me da igual pero claro yo creo que
this is already
esto ya sí
eh apart from looking for whatever is
eh aparte de buscar la lo que sea
reportable of the threats that he has made
denunciable de las amenazas que ha hecho
here on Twitter apart from that we are
aquí en Twitter aparte de eso vamos a
going to report the account and then let them
vamos a reportar la cuenta y ya luego
tell the police station when they put him in
que cuenten comisaría cuando lo metan en
jail that they have the wrong
la cárcel que se han equivocado de
person yes Anica if you give me the link we
persona sí Anica si me ponéis el enlace
report it of course sucker for ass part
lo reportamos claro chupa culo parte
sucker for ass from Dallas this old sadist
chupac culo de Dallas est viejo sádico
talking until 10 in the morning with
hablando hasta las 10 de la mañana con
13 year old girls on discord and
niñas de 13 años por discord y
telling them that he is going to eat their face
diciéndole que les va a comer la cara
tey I will eat your face if I see you he would say I will eat your face
tey te como la cara si te veo les decía
to him I look for the tweet
te como la cara a le Busco el tweet
where it says I will eat your face or look for yourself
donde dice te como la cara o buscarse
Where  look look at this I do have to
Dónde está miren miren esto yo sí me lo
put up with it but I tell him that the
tengo que calar pero yo le digo que la
woman is a catfish crying Oh you attacked
mujer es un bagre llora Ay atacaste a
Lorena Oh no oh no You attacked her Oh I don't care Hey
Lorena Ay no ay no La atacaste Ay me la
gibel came out there
me la pela Ey por ahí salió gibel por
gibel came out too Where is he Where is he gibel
ahí también salió gibel Dónde está Dónde
where is he
está gibel dónde está
mutually says over here Where is he the [ __ ] I
mutuamente dice por aquí Dónde está [__]
want to get Where is he I think it's
Quiero conseguir Dónde está creo que es
in the answer that the clown gives this
en la respuesta que da el payaso este
old [ __ ] let's see where is
viejo [__] a ver dónde
God you take a long time and I the le poo what is
Dios tardes mucho y yo el le poo que qué
this old man going to debate no and start
va a debatir este viejo no y empieza
here with that you get really burned Where is he the
aquí con que te ardes mucho Dónde está
[ __ ] Where is he brother he's
[__] Dónde está brother está
completely crazy Imagine
completamente loco Es que imagínate
Imagine this man the day they
Imagínate este hombre cl el día que lo
put him in jail if he is like that
metieron en la cárcel si es así
publicly Imagine what he wouldn't do to that
públicamente Imagínate lo que que no le
man eh who reported him
haría al hombre ese eh que lo denunció
eh Imagine
eh Imagínate
eh they deleted my answer it can't be it can't
eh borraron mi respuesta no puede ser no
be Ah look at the other one they feel
puede ser Ah mire la otra se sienten
proud because he says and that ratio bro
orgullosos porque dice y ese ratio bro
that I don't have a YouTube channel that
que yo no tengo un canal de YouTube que
I have a minimum Twitch channel of
yo tengo un mínimo canal de Twitch de
cryptos that to me  I don't give a [ __ ] if
criptos que a mí me importa un culo que
he's followed by more [ __ ]
a él lo sigan más retrasados obviamente
people, obviously there are more [ __ ] people in the world.
en el mundo hay más gente retrasada
Obviously there are more people in the world,
Obviamente que hay más gente en el mundo
rich millionaires or poor people, there are very
gente rica millonaria o pobres hay muy
few millionaires, right? And there are very few
pocos millonarios verdad y Hay muy poca
intelligent people, what's left over?
gente inteligente qué es lo que sobra
Trash Like the ones who follow him,
basura Como la que sigue a él retrasados
mentally [ __ ], that's what's left over. Uh, like rice,
mentales eso lo que sobra Uh como arroz
like rice, [ __ ] people who believe an
como arroz retrasados que le crean a un
idiot like this old man, damn it. Uh, that's
idiota como este viejo maldito Uh eso
left over, left over, left over. Where is he, dude? I
sobran sobra sobra Dónde está [__]
want to see the answer, let's see, [ __ ]
Quiero ver la respuesta que que a ver
brother, where is it? It can't be that I ca
[__] brother dónde está No puede ser que
n't get the answer somewhere.
no consiga la respuesta en algún lugar
Javi talks to Juan Go Ospina, he has an
Javi habla con Juan Go ospina tiene un
agreement with a very good law firm in Miami.
acuerdo con un despacho de Miami muy
Don't [ __ ] with him. Juango has an agreement
bueno no joda el juango tiene un acuerdo
with a law firm in Miami, precisely,
con un despacho de Miami precisamente
seriously. I didn't know that, damn, well, we're
en serio No sabía yo eso [__] pues lo
going to see. Yes, yes, for sure, 100% there are
vamos a ver sí sí fijo 100% que hay
things here, eh, reportable, man, I mean, I've
cosas aquí eh denunciables tío o sea he
seen a lot of things when we've
visto un montón de cosas cuando hemos
dealt with the issue of famous people in the United
tratado tema de los famosos de Estados
States and so on. For much less, eh, For
Unidos y demás Por mucho menos eh Por
much less, big problems in the
mucho menos marrones gordos de los
courts, eh, I mean, this guy
juzgados eh o sea este tipo le
says Anica, I'm sure, go to the but
dice Anica lo tengo claro ir al pero
put  the link please is disgusting that he has to
ponerme el enlace porfi es asqueroso que
mess with Lorena, what a
se tenga que meter con la Lorena que
little man the one who messes with a woman
poco hombre el que se mete con una mujer
and more her who doesn't say anything Lorena up we
y más ella que no dice nada Lorena up te
love you car that it doesn't make any sense
queremos car que no tiene ningún sentido
Even if I had a horrible wife which
Aunque yo tuviera una mujer horrible que
is not the case ra Because she is 10
no es el caso ra Porque le da 10
million times around I'm not going to say
millones de vueltas ya no voy a decir a
yours anymore, any of the ones who take
la tuya a cualquiera de las que les hace
pictures of them and things in the pool it is already
foto y a cosas en la piscina ya es
shameful to have conflicts between
vergonzoso tener conflictos entre
you is one thing but this guy,
ustedes es una cosa pero este tipejo de
everything he says 90% are insults, they
todo lo que dice el 90 por son insultos
should ban the minimum No, that's for sure they are
deberían banear lo mínimo No eso seguro
going to ban him but surely
que lo van a banear pero seguro que le
something is going to happen to him legally too but e
va a pasar algo legalmente también pero
Even if I had a horrible wife,
e Aunque yo tuviera una mujer horrorosa
a horrible son and a terrible mother it doesn't
un hijo horroroso y una madre malísima
matter, they are not doing anything to you
da igual no te están haciendo nada a ti
You argue with me what happens is that you ca
Tú Argumenta conmigo lo que pasa es que
n't because you are very
no puedes porque eres muy corto
mentally short and that is what I am telling you, the
mentalmente y es lo que te digo te va a
same thing is going to happen to you that happened to you with him with the
pasar lo mismo que te pasó con el con el
landlord, I mean, you started threatening
casero o sea te has puesto a amenazar
here on live on your Twitter, I am going
aquí en el directo en tu Twitter te voy
to report you and I am going to go after you in everything
a denunciar y voy a ir a por ti a todo
that is, in everything  what is legal, I do
lo que sea a todo lo que se pueda legal
n't care It's okay if you're wrong, then
igual No pasa nada si tú estás mal pues
treat yourself RAE I can't do anything else it's that you
trátate RAE yo no puedo hacer otra
're not even looking good
cosa es que ni estás quedando bien
because you're making a fool of yourself or
porque estás haciendo el ridículo ni
anything like that, the [ __ ]
nada por el
where is it? It can't be, I can't
estilo está [__] dónde está No puede ser
get it, hon, it has to be around
no lo consigo hón tiene que estar por
here where gubel answered me Oh or
aquí por donde me respondió gubel Ah o
here I knew, give your opinion, lawyer arrives in Miami
aquí sabía opina abogado llega a Miami
with the signature of an
con la firma de una alianza
international alliance, damn it, I didn't know Well, of course we're
internacional [__] pues no lo sabía
going to report it, obviously Of course, of course, I
Pues pues claro que lo vamos a denunciar
'm absolutely sure, absolutely
Claro que sí claro que sí es que estoy
sure that he's gotten himself into something
segurísimo segurísimo de que aquí se ha
bad here, I'm absolutely sure that he's gotten himself into something
marrón estoy segurísimo de que aquí se
bad here, what else has
ha metido un marrón qué más ha
happened, how are you going to mess with the woman,
seguido cómo te vas a meter con la mujer
the trauma is evident, he's like the child who
se nota el trauma es como al niño que
never got attention, now he needs to be
nunca le daban atención ahora Necesita
told that his car and wife are
que le digan que su carro y mujer son
beautiful, otherwise he won't sleep well He
hermosos si no no duermen bien Es que
's putting the woman as if she were
está poniendo a la mujer como si fuera
the car, literally, whether she's prettier or
el coche literalmente sea más guapa o
uglier, he
más fea
's putting the woman as if she were
e está poniendo a la mujer como si fuera
a car, look, look at the car that I have
un coche mira mira el coche que yo tengo
and the car that you have, damn it, he
y el coche que tienes tú [__] es que
's making a fool of himself but it's
está haciendo el ridículo pero
totally not at all  that's looking
totalmente que no tiene nada que ver
really bad I don't give
está quedando muy mal a mí me importa
a [ __ ] [ __ ] how I look in front of you you
una [__] [__] como quedar delante tuyo
damn failure what do I care about
maldito fracasado mi que me importa
looking good in front of this damn
quedar bien delante de este maldito
failure Porto [ __ ] and I put
fracasado Porto una [__] y le puse
Look I suck three balls That I'm
Mira me chupa tres huevos Que vuelvo a
lying about myself again your filthy Stream vo for
mentir sobre mí su cochino Stream vo por
the rest of his family here they burned
el resto de su familia aquí se ardieron
his wife and his children have more to do
más tiene que ver su esposa y sus hijos
with what
con lo que haya dicho
Dalas said since when Javi and Dalas are the
Dalas desde cuánd Javi y Dalas Son la
same person you are threatening a
misma persona estás amenazando una
family Ray what I put you is the
familia Ray yo loo de te pongo es la
same [ __ ] Dallas or oliveira is the
misma [__] Dallas o oliveira es la
same [ __ ] disgusting mangy dog ​​ass liar hypocrite slanderer
misma [__] perro asqueroso sarnoso
defamer ball licker of a
calumniador difamador lame bolas de un
[ __ ] sadistic grummer pedophile of
maldito sádico grummer pedófilo de
[ __ ] what is he going to do what is he going to do
[__] qué va a hacer qué va a hacer
jira what is he going to do
jira qué va a hacer
failure then put me
fracasado entonces me pone
here for you some innocent children are the
aquí para ti unos niños inocentes son
same [ __ ] I am saying here that
misma [__] yo estoy diciendo aquí que
the children are the same [ __ ] this chick ca
los niños son la misma [__] esta tipa
n't even read I understand why you
ni siquiera sabe leer entiendo por qué
put some minors and threaten
metes a unos menores y los amenazas que
them publish them publish the minors publish
los publique publique a los menores
my girlfriend is this and that that I
publos mi novia es esto y lo otro que yo
I'm an inmate publish the child
soy un recluso publique el niño
publish with that son of a [ __ ] If the
publíquese con eso hijo de [__] Si el
child is ugly which obviously he's going to be ugly
niño es feo que obviamente va a ser feo
Or ugly I don't know if it's a boy or a girl I'm going to make fun of it I'm
O fea no sé si es niño o niña me voy a
going to make
burlar Me voy a
fun of it I don't give a [ __ ] about these
burlar Me importa una [__] con estos
[ __ ] wretches like jav oliveira you
malditos desgraciados como jav oliveira
can't have
no se puede tener contemplaciones de
any kind of consideration of any
ningún tipo de ningún
kind don't pay attention to him he stopped being coherent a long time ago
tipo no le den bola hace mucho que dejó
the gentleman acts like
de ser coherente el señor actúa como
those 15 year old kids who fight in
esos niños de 15 que se pelean en el
high school he says I don't think the best
instituto dice no creo que las mejores
way is to insult a person who's not
formas sea insultar a una persona que no
involved in your fight man you've
está metida en vuestra gresca tío te has
gone too far look I'm telling him I'm telling him
pasado mir yo se lo digo yo se lo digo
with this piece of pig I don't have and I'm not
yo con este pedazo de cerdo no tengo ni
going to have any kind of
voy a tener ningún tipo de
consideration The more he names me
contemplaciones Mientras más me nombre
the more acid I'm going to get and it's the
más ácido me voy a poner y es la
reality the worse I'm going to get the more he messes
realidad peor me voy a poner más se mete
with me the more sadistic I'm going to get worse
conmigo más sádico me voy a poner peor
worse every day every day you're sick pa I
peor cada día cada día estás enfermo pa
'm not healthy thank God look at him
no estoy sano gracias a Dios mira mete
with your old lady's face when you see how
con la cara de tu vieja cuando ves cómo
you fight like a schizophrenic on Twitter
te peleas como esquizofrénico en Twitter
that face Agustina all the time me
esa cara Agustina todo el tiempo yo
when I fight  all the time Agustina
cuando me peleo todo el tiempo Agustina
if she's
si está
bored this face Agustina
aburrida esta la cara Agustina
always has this [ __ ] I want to look for the
siempre este [__] Quiero buscar el el
tweet when they push you aside and cry
tweet cuándo te hacen a un lado y llorar
about it Ugh it's terrible eh this guy has
por eso Uf está fatal eh este tío tiene
problems eh I tell him Don they're going to
problemillas eh le digo Don lo van a
kick him out of the United States 100% I say to the
echar de los Estados Unidos 100% digo al
piece of failure this this [ __ ]
pedazo fracasado este este maldito
virolo with a charro drip all carried
virolo con gote de charro todo llevado
by the [ __ ] bastard he looks like a
por la [__] malparidez que parece un
[ __ ] homeless person a homeless person in New
maldito indigente un indigente en Nueva
York This is difficult easy easy to
York Este sí es difícil fácil fácil de
look at this is easy to look at and
mirar esto es fácil de mirar y
listen to him He doesn't even know how to speak Spanish he can't even speak
escucharlo No sabe ni hablar ni español
his own
ni siquiera puede hablar su propio
language well he doesn't even know how to speak Spanish he didn't
idioma bien no sabe ni hablar español no
graduate from absolutely anything a [ __ ]
se graduó de absolutamente nada un [__]
ignorant who turned on a camera and makes
ignorante que prendió una cámara y hace
content on YouTube That's all
contenido en YouTube Eso es todo lo que
this clown is defaming the whole [ __ ]
es este payaso difamando a todo el [__]
world So let him endure he turned on the
mundo Entonces que aguante prendió la
camera to defame let him endure he says he says
cámara para difamar que aguante dice
he and all his followers say that
dice él y todos sus seguidores dicen que
they are the pretty ones and we are
ellos son los bonitos y nosotros somos
the vagres at that level we
los vagres a ese nivel
are RAE you are at the level that you
estamos RAE tú estás al nivel de que
harass your neighbors by taking photos
acosas a tus vecinas haciéndole fotos
without
sin
consent and at the level that now you
consentimiento y al nivel de que ahora
are threatening What  I upload a picture of
estás amenazando Que suba yo una foto de
my 5 year old son that you are going to mess with
mi hijo de 5 años que te vas a meter con
him that is your level that is why you are going to end up
él ese es tu nivel por eso vas a acabar
in
en la
jail where you belong you should
cárcel donde debes
be where you should be You shouldn't have gone
estar debes estar de donde No debiste
out that weekend because we are
salir ese fin de semana porque estamos
seeing or a baby or if it is a baby it is a baby Yes yes yes yes
viendo o un bebé o si es un bebé es un
or if it is a baby a baby Yes yes yes
bebé Sí sí sí sí o si es un bebé un bebé
you are a criminal raet and you
Sí sí sí sí eres un delincuente raet y
have to be in jail because you
tienes que estar en la cárcel porque no
are not well but it is that you are not well and you do not
estás bien pero es que ni estás bien ni
love your girlfriend because you start
quieres a tu novia porque te pones a
taking pictures of women without
hacerle fotografías a mujeres sin
consent in the pool it is worth
consentimiento en la piscina vale para
scoring lasas and you do not have anyone by your side
puntuar lasas ni tienes a nadie al lado
who loves you because you are making a
que te quiera porque estás haciendo el
fool of yourself you
ridículo
are making a fool of yourself and nobody
estás haciendo el ridículo y nadie te
stops you honey please why am I
frena cariño por favor para que me da
ashamed of what you are
vergüenza lo que estás
doing that level we are we are the
haciendo ese nivel estamos nosotros
horrible ones and he who seems like a
somos los horribles y él que parece una
damn who is amorphous
[__] que es amorfo
right an amalgam of pieces Ah you are not going to
verdad una amalgama de pedazos Ah no vas
compare no yes yes yes yes his
a comparar no sí sí sí sí sí los
followers say yes Look he
seguidores de él dice que sí Mira él
says well You have answered yourself
dice pues Tú solito te has contestado
inmate or rather he really look he sees
recluso o sea él de verdad mire él ve
this photo and sees this photo and he really
esta foto y ve esta foto y él de verdad
believes that the catfish woman of  he and he are
cree que el bagre mujer de él y él son
much more beautiful, graceful, pretty
mucho más más bonitos agraciados bonitos
and are physically better than us, he
y son mejores físicamente que nosotros
believes it and also has a gang of
se lo cree y aparte tiene una banda de
mentally [ __ ] people who tell him yes
retrasados mentales que le dicen que sí
and here I answered him in the end you
y aquí yo le respondí al final le
ate his mouth, the 13 year old with whom
comiste la boca la de 13 años con la que
you stay up all night on discord
con la que te trasnocha en discord
talking to you, [ __ ] disgusting Saico
hablando contigo [__] Saico asqueroso
Just like your owner a couple of sick people who get
Igualito a tu dueño par de enfermos que
wet for schoolgirls The
se mojan por colegialas La verdad la
truth is that these guys like
verdad que a Estos tipos les gustan las
schoolgirls is what this guy likes the guy
colegialas es lo que le gusta este tipo
likes schoolgirls it's
tipo le gusta las colegialas está
proven Wow
comprobado Wow
impressive we are the ugly ones
impresionante nosotros somos los feos
Hit it in the snout through Juan goos
Dale en el hocico a través de Juan goos
Pina face throwing a kiss car a kiss
Pina cara lanzando un beso car un beso
face throwing a
cara lanzando un
kiss that I noticed a lot like this in streamers or
beso que noté mucho así en streamers o
content creators it's not like I know if
creadores de contenido es no s si es que
fame goes to his head or but
la fama se le suba la cabeza o pero de
suddenly they think they are Brad
repente se creen que son Brad
Pit, let's see we all have defects he
Pit cre a ver todos tenemos defect le
is asking his girlfriend You think he
está preguntando a la novia Tú crees que
is more handsome than
es más guapo que
me Poor thing get out of there girl get out of there I
yo Pobrecita sal de ahí chica sal de ahí
don't know what your name get out of there Get out of
no sé cómo te llamas sal de ahí Sal de
there because this is not going  to end well
ahí porque esto no va a acabar bien
seeing seeing the audios that
viendo viendo los audios que ha
he published the other girlfriend the
publicado él la otra novia la novia
previous girlfriend published some audios of Ray
anterior publicó unos audios de Ray
yelling at them jidos seeing what he's
gritándoles jidos viendo lo que está
doing here that he's threatening
haciendo aquí que está amenazando has
even a baby get out of there girl get out of
hasta un bebé sal de ahí chica sal de
there look at what's happening to him You think he
ahí fíjate tú lo que le está Tú crees
's more handsome than me if the girl
que es más guapo que yo si a la chavala
decides to say yes to him Imagine what he
se le ocurre decirle que sí Imagínate la
can do to all of us we all have
que puede formar to todos todos tenemos
things there are people who are more beautiful and uglier
cosas hay gente más linda como más fea
than us but from there to having an ego
que nosotros pero de ahí a tener un ego
through the roof and believing that you have
por las por las nubes y creer que tenés
the nerve to be able to criticize
el tupé de poder criticar a todo el
everyone no like that it's not like that
mundo no así no es o sea bastante errada
the situation is quite wrong no I mean and nothing one hears
la situación no O sea y nada uno escucha
a criticism of a person who is better
una crítica de una persona que es mejor
than you let's see if tomorrow comes and Jennifer
que uno a ver si viene mañana y Jennifer
Lopez Megan Fox they tell me Hey This is
López Megan Fox me dicen Che Esto está
fine they are perfect I keep my
bien son perfectas me quedo callada la
mouth shut they are right but that a person
boca tienen razón pero que una persona
a catfish one and the truth is that a vagre I
un bagre uno y la verdad que un vagre me
laugh a vagre like this like this
río un vagre como este como este
guy release him on the street well let's go
tipo suéltenlo en la calle pues vamos
to a bar so he goes with the woman and let's
para un bar que vaya él con la mujer y
go Agustín And I who don't even
vayamos Agustín Y yo que ni se dan
realize when  we go out to restaurants
cuenta de cuando salimos a restaurantes
when we go out to eat out what they
cuando salimos a a comer por ahí lo que
tell us Ah you're prettier than
nos dicen Ah vos sos más linda que
and man are you listening to this who is in his
y tío estáis escuchando esto que tiene
40s and the guy is
40 y pico años y el tío está
arguing but at what point did this
argumentando pero esto en qué momento se
become a beauty pageant in a
convirtió en un desfile de belleza en un
beauty contest I
concurso de de belleza
mean the guy
o sea el tipo de
suddenly is saying that they say things
repente está diciendo que le dicen cosas
to him the girlfriend is
a él la novia está
freaking out J I hope it's let's see what it is let's
flipando J Ojalá este a ver qué es lo
see what it is in the photo
que es a ver qué es lo que es en la foto
it's more the photo of the 31st the photo of the 31st is
es más la foto del 31 la foto del 31 es
magical this [ __ ] brut on top of that
mágica esta [__] brut encima para
the lighting wasn't the best no
colmo la iluminación no fue la mejor no
I come out all yellow and you know what
yo salgo todo amarillo y sabes que hacen
those clowns followers of his do they zoom in on me
los payasos seguidores de él me dan zoom
until I'm more pixelated than
hasta que ya yo estoy más pixelado que
anything to say that I am me I
nada para decir que yo soy
am hideous I am a catfish already that
yo soy espantoso soy un bagre yas que
measures 30 cm and it doesn't even have a shape
mide 30 cm y é que no tiene ni forma
[ __ ] that looks like a popcorn it looks like a
[__] que parece una cotufa parece un
Popcorn it has no shape hon damn ping
Popcorn no tiene forma hón maldito ping
but it doesn't matter Even if you were handsome that you are
pero que da igual Aunque fueras guapo
not handsome inside that even if I were
que no eres guapo por dentro que aunque
handsome ra even if it were that no that
fuera guapo ra aunque fuera que no que
you are a person who is not well okay but even
eres una persona que no está bien vale
though  you were you're not handsome
pero aunque lo fueras no eres guapo por
inside you're a criminal you
dentro eres un delincuente
should be in
tienes que estar en la
jail he believes he believes that for real he
cárcel é se cre cree que de verdad é
believes in his stupid mind he really believes
cree en su mente estúpida él cree de
that he's a gig chat and I'm a
verdad que él es un gig chat y yo soy un
Bag he believes it please the old man the
Bag él lo cree por favor el viejoo el
ass no sir literally
culo no sir literal
literally you with your neighbors
literal tú con tus vecinas
r you with your
r tú con tus
neighbors betrayed him
vecinas lo delató
Eh and also I don't know how to mess with his
Eh y además no sé como meterse con con
partner and give your
la pareja de y
opinion to his followers and him and everything Oh that
opinar sus seguidores y él y todo Ah que
the girlfriend is laughing at him for messing
la novia le está riendo a él por meterse
with
con la pareja
my partner I read messages because I don't use
mía yo leí mensajes porque yo no uso
Twitter for Wait what's she talking to me
Twitter para Espera que me está hablando
Fran the girlfriend told you off
Fran la novia te ha echado la bronca en
live that you don't realize you have to
directo que no te enteras que tienes que
watch her live streams because if not you don't
ver sus directos porque si no no lo
understand it she only talks about you but the girlfriend
entiendes solo habla de ti pero la novia
is giving in to him Fran Look, the
le está rindiendo a él Fran Mira la
girlfriend just told him man mess
novia le acaba de decir hombre meterte
with his partner Look it's like messing with his
con la pareja Mira es como meterse con
partner and giving your
con la pareja de y
opinion clo of
opinar clo
course followers and him and everyone I read
claro seguidores y él y todos yo leí
messages because I don't use Twitter for
mensajes porque yo no uso Twitter para
that honestly eh but I saw
eso sinceramente eh pero vi vi
comments and he said he has this he has that
comentarios y decía tiene esto tiene lo
guys and if I could  have the money
otro chicos y si pude tener la plata
to do what I wanted to do to get
para hacerme lo que me quise hacer para
rid of my insecurities what the [ __ ] does the
sacarme las inseguridades qué [__] le
other person care if I have 1000 2000 3000
importa al otro si tengo 1000 2000 3000
invested in me what does my money
invertidos en mí qué le importa mi plata
my life my body my choices matter to them and
mi vida mi cuerpo mis elecciones y
tomorrow I want to do it up to my ears I'm
mañana me quiero hacer hasta las orejas
going to do it and whoever wants to
me lo voy a hacer y el que me quiera
criticize me is the one who can't because they're either
criticar es el que no puede porque o es
poor or ugly or don't dare to
pobre o es feo o no se anima a
face the reality that sometimes
enfrentarse la realidad de que a veces
not everyone is pretty and not everyone has
no todos son lindos y no todos tenemos
all the nice things and have the courage of
todas las cosas lindas y tener coraje de
bancs Elo because going to get something done
de bancs Elo porque ir a hacerse algo
isn't easy either I mean fatale the girlfriend does
tampoco es fácil O sea fatale la novia
n't know where to put kisses andr Well
no sabe dónde meterse besos andr Bueno
let her let her express herself it's a
dejarla dejarla que se exprese es es un
well operation it's a lot of things
poz operatorio es un montón de cosas
but what is that piece of [ __ ] going to talk
pero qué va a hablar ese pedazo de
about operations and d he has operations every
[__] de operaciones y d se opera cada
week who told him but I don't
semana quién le ha dicho pero es que no
know he's arguing with someone who
sé está discutiendo con alguien que le
told the girl if he had operations or
ha dicho a la chavala si se ha operado o
not if I'm not giving
no se ha operado si es que yo no estoy
my opinion on her
opinando de ella
dates with him with the
citas con el con el
but  dates with lizy to go out to eat he
peroo que citas con lizy para ir a comer
sees the surgeon more than the woman who is going
ve más al cirujano que a la mujer qu va
to talk about
a hablar é de
surgeries Oh and besides he got hair
cirugías Ah y aparte é se puso pelo
Exactly it was left it was left So criticism
Exacto le quedó le quedó Entonces crtica
I don't call him bald He doesn't have it he has a a
yo no le digo pelado No tiene él tiene
spot he has a spot he has a spot
una una mota tiene una mota tiene una
there that he got there he got hair
mota ahí que se puso ahí se puso pelo
My God My God My God I'm going to
Dios mío Dios mío Dios mío yo me voy a
get hair Well I don't have the
poner pelo Bueno yo no tengo todavía
need to get hair yet I guess no if he
necesidad ponerme pelo seg no si la
has it RAE Yes he has it what happens is that I do
tiene RAE Si la tiene lo que pasa que yo
n't know if yes yes It should be good to
no sé si si si Debería ser bueno
touch yourself a lot up there Eh
toquetear mucho tú por ahí arriba Eh
but yes yes he has it if he has ra if you need it I
pero sí sí tiene si tiene ra si te hace
'm bagasse first of all I'm not
falta Yo soy bagazo primero que no estoy
fat Starting from there he has to go
gordo Empezando por ahí él tiene que ir
to the gym Dad this him He looks at this
para gimnasio Papá este él Él mira esta
[ __ ] [ __ ] that this I mean let
[__] [__] que esto O sea que venga
this piece of Bag [ __ ] come along I'm all for
este pedazo de Bag [__] yo todo para
me is braver the one who says Hey I don't
mí es más corajudo el que dice Che no me
like that I'll go and change it than the one who
gusta eso voy y lo cambio que el que
criticizes the darkness knowing that it is
critica de la oscuridad sabiendo que es
a reflex action because of their piras
un es un acto reflejo por sus prias
insecurities I mean there's always the
inseguridades o sea siempre está la
person who is bad milk that says oh
persona mal leche que dice ay se hizo
this was done, that other thing was done right that  you
esto se hizo lo otro bien que vos
had the money you would do it too
estuvieras la plata también te lo harías
but he and his wife have had some work done
pero él y su mujer se han retocado de
that is going well and he is very conceited about
que le va bien y él es muy de presumir
having surgeries Well dude he should
hacer de hacerse cirugías Pues [__]
sue the surgeon because look how he
que demande al cirujano porque mire como
looks he had surgery I don't know where the [ __ ] he had
quedó se hizo cirugía no sé dónde
surgery he is a son of a [ __ ]
[__] hizo cirugía está hijo de [__]
idiot he is a son of a [ __ ] it was with a
huevón está hijo de [__] más fue con un
car underneath him dude he is horrible
carro por debajo [__] es espantoso
look here he spends his time messing with me
mira aquí se la pasa metiéndose conmigo
and I respond to him and I tell him that
y yo le respondo y le digo que la mujer
his wife is a catfish and he starts crying and look
de él es un bagre y sale a llorar y mira
how he has me here defam send me
como me tiene aquí difam mándame
telling him that telling me what defaming
diciéndole que diciéndome qué difamando
you RAE this
te RAE esta es tu foto policial de la
is your mugshot from jail what are you Ray let it be clear to you that you can go as crazy as you want that The crazier they make you today they will close your Twitch tomorrow they will close your Twitter and I will put you in jail with a complaint
meter en la cárcel con una denuncia
because you are threatening dude you are
porque estás amenazando tío estás
threatening you are slandering me You are going to have to
amenazando estás difamando Me vas a
pay me okay go as
tener que pagar vale tú vuélvete todo lo
crazy as you want but never anything that
loco que tú quieras pero que nunca nada
you do  and the ridiculous thing that you
de lo que tú hagas y del ridículo que
do will take away that you are
hagas va a quitar que eres un
just an inmate that I
recluso sin
hit him that I was a prisoner that I
más que yo le pegué que yo fui preso que
was he hit the landlord and a
fui le caía coñazos al casero y un
lot of atrocities spa they had
montón de barbaridades espa tuvieran
the policies that they have here the rules they have here I
las políticas que tienen acá las reglas
wish if I were in Spain
tienen acá Ojalá si en España estuviera
Ah there are more he is sending me to more
Ah que hay más me está mandando más
places but the rules don't stop them from
lugares pero no paran las reglas que
being here This guy could never go
estuvieran acá Este tipo no pudiera
out and do his filthy
salir a hacer Su contenido cochino de
[ __ ] content ever in his [ __ ] life because he would
[__] jamás en la [__] vida porque
have 400 lawsuits open cases he would
tendría 400 demandas procesos abiertos
spend all the money that the
gastaría toda la plata Que le donan los
mentally [ __ ] donate to him on lawyers because
retrasados mentales en abogados porque
he doesn't here to this government in Spain here
él no aquí a est gobierno en España aquí
in the United States you can't do the
en Estados Unidos no se pueden hacer las
clowning that this one does and Dallas and Dallas
payasas que hace este y Dallas y Dallas
threatening death and all that
amenazando de muerte y todas esas
[ __ ] here exactly for that reason you are
[__] aquí exactamente por eso tú a ti
going to be kicked out you are going to be kicked out raet you
te van a echar a ti te van a echar raet
are buying tickets here bro she
estás comprando papeleta aquí hermano se
got her eyes and nose done supposedly
hizo en los ojos y en la nariz se supone
for health but she got a touch up
que por salud pero se dio un retoque
apart from her hair Oh well Then she
aparte del pelo Ah bueno Después me
criticizes me that I have criticized
critica a mí que yo la he criticado a
her but this girl this girl
ella pero que esta chica esta chica de
where does she get that from that I  I have criticized
dónde saca eso que yo la he criticado a
her for having
ella por
surgery yes And this is the result
operarse sí Y est este es el resultado
of operations of this type
de la de las operaciones de este tipo
these are the results of the type
estos son los resultados del tipo a
sometimes All that remains is to be born again my love
veces Solo queda volver a nacer mi amor
the coffee and the coffee you forgot it right
el café y el café lo olvidaste verdad
here It already smells like a debate grandpa aelo [ __ ]
aquí Ya huele a debate abuelo aelo merda
n we are going to report it Hey it goes to me are you going
n lo vamos a denunciar Oye me va me vais
to send me the link to report it
a mandar el enlace para reportarlo
Ah
Ah
this well yes Imagine having to put up with
este pues sí Imagínese tener que calarse
a [ __ ] failure
todos los días que un [__] fracasado
like this piece of old [ __ ] lazy guy
como este pedazo de viejo [__] huevón
every day pending on
esté todos los días pendiente de la vida
our lives when when I am
nosotros cuando cuando yo estoy
pending on the ballast and see and see
pendiente del balastro y ver y de ver en
how much the unicorn is rising, I mean
cuánto está subiendo el unicornio o sea
I am here publishing my stuff about the
yo estoy aquí publico mis vainas del
unicorn Ah apart from another big lie Oh
unicornio Ah aparte otra gran mentira Ay
if you don't talk about them you have no
si no hablas de ellos no tienes nada de
repercussion repercussion of the unicorn
repercusión repercusión del unicornio
145 likes 25 move away Willy move away Willy you have
145 likes 25 aparta Willy
had 100 likes on
aparta Willy que has tenido 100 likes en
a tweet move away Willy eh apart from what else is luar
un twit aparta Willy eh aparte qué más
going to send me Put next to pid
me va a mandar luar Pon al lado de pid
of course and Daniel Sancho and a
claro por supuesto y Daniel Sancho y un
few people  dude who is in prison right
poco de gente huevón que está presa en
now, really convicted,
este momento convictos de verdad me pone
this [ __ ] slanderer, pathetic,
este [__] difamador calumniador patético
disgusting brother, standing next to these people
asqueroso brother al lado de esta gente
as if I had really committed a
como si yo de verdad hubiese cometido un
serious crime, had done something. I mean, this guy
delito grave hubiese hecho algo O sea no
has no face, this guy is a
tiene cara este tipo este tipo es un
slanderer, a slanderer, everything that I
difamador un calumniador todo lo que yo
have to say to this guy, I'm
yo tenga para decirle a este tipo se lo
going to say it to his face. Now Oliveira, if you
voy a decir en la cara ahora oliveira si
're reacting here to this, you're going to
estás reaccionando aquí a esto vas a
deny your discord conversations with the
negar tus conversaciones de discord con
13-year-old girls, you're going
la con las carajitas de 13 años las vas
to deny them because they're even on video. You're going
a negar porque están hasta en video vas
to deny that you talk to 13-year-old girls
a negar que hablas con gitas de 13 años
until 10 in the morning on discord and
hasta las 10 de la mañana por discord y
that you told one of them that you ate her
que le dijiste a una que le comías la
face or I don't know how I eat your face, you're
cara o no te como te recomo la cara lo
going to deny it now it's a lie it's a lie
vas a negar ahora es mentira es mentira
that you told her, being 35, 36 years old, you
que le dijiste teniendo 35 36 años le
told a 13-year-old girl that
dijiste una a una gevita de 13 años que
a person who on Twitter wrote to me
a a una persona que Twitter me escribió
that I don't even know who she is or how old she is or or or or or or how
que yo no sé ni quién es ni la edad que
I talk to her
tiene ni ni ni ni o sea como yo le hablo
lovingly to everyone who is here
cariñosamente a todos los que están aquí
in the chat and maybe suddenly one is
en el chat y a lo mejor de repente uno
14 but in private I don't talk to
tiene 14 pero en privado yo no hablo con
anyone underage she is a person who was
nadie menor es una persona a la que
also harassed by the gossip forum members
además acosaron las foreras de cotillo
that comes from there what they are saying
que viene de ahí lo que están diciendo
that girl you ate her face with kisses it's a
esa chica le comías la cara a beso es
lie that that is true you know it's a
mentira eso eso sí es verdad sabes que
lie you know it's a lie that
es mentira sabes que es mentira que
supposedly I attacked my landlord That is a
supuestamente yo agredí a mi casero Eso
lie it's not a lie ra it's on
sí es mentira no es mentira ra está en
the police page and you know what is
la página de la policía y sabes lo que
not a lie because the
tampoco es mentira porque están las
conversations are published that you harassed
conversaciones publicadas que tú acosaba
your neighbors and took photos without
a tus vecinas y le hacía fotos sin
consent RAE that I talk in the
consentimiento RAE que yo hable en el
group with my followers until late
grupo con mis seguidores hasta las
at night it's not a problem that's why I
tantas de la noche no pasa nada por eso
'm commenting on it in public okay
lo estoy comentando en público vale que
you are overwhelmed that you are crazy
tú estás agobiado que tú estás rayado
because of the ridiculous thing you are doing
por el ridículo que estás haciendo
Because they are going to kick you out of the United States
Porque te van a echar de Estados Unidos
because you have been in jail Whatever you
porque has estado en la cárcel Lo que tú
want but what there is proven with
quieras pero que lo que hay probado con
conversations and we are going to report you is
conversaciones y te vamos a denunciar es
that you harass your neighbors So you
que tú acosas a tus vecinas Así que
won't like your girlfriend so much you harass
tanto no te gustará tu novia tú acosas a
your neighbors the photos are there
tus vecinas están ahí las fotos están
the conversations are there guys  punat
ahí las conversaciones chicos punat
Wait I'm going to try to take a
Espera que le voy a intentar hacer una
better picture of things to women and he takes
foto mejor a cosas a mujeres y le hace
pictures of them in bikinis without
fotos en bikini sin
consent there are the
consentimiento ahí están las
conversations Take out
conversaciones Saca las conversaciones
my conversations with minors that you are saying
mías con menores que tú estás diciendo
well you are going to have to prove them you've
bueno las vas a tener que demostrar
been another idea that you are going to have to
ve sidado otra la idea que lo vas a
prove take it out take it out right
tener que demostrar sácalo sácalo right
okay We are going to report you they are
vale Te vamos a denunciar me están
telling me that Juan Go Pina has an
diciendo que Juan Go Pina tiene un
agreement with a law firm in Miami we are going
acuerdo con un bufete de Miami te vamos
to report you raet And they are going to kick you out of the
a denunciar raet Y te van a echar de
United States because you already have
Estados Unidos porque ya tienes
problems and you repeat it Every
problemas y tú la repites Todos los
[ __ ] day of your life every day of
[__] días de tu vida todos los días de
your life you piece of failed cowardly
tu vida pedazo de fracasado cobarde
slanderer and slanderer like all of
difamador y calumniador como todos
you By the way they are telling me they
ustedes Por cierto me están diciendo me
are telling me that some bombshells
están diciendo que vienen unos bombazos
of this type are coming some bombshells of this type
de este tipo unos bombazos de este tipo
unbelievable unbelievable here they are
increíble increíble aquí me están
telling me I can only say that they are
diciendo Yo solo puedo decir que andan
saying that your girlfriend is with you for
diciendo que tu novia anda con voos por
money I mean my girlfriend has more money
la plata o sea mi novia tiene más dinero
than me much more something more ridiculous What
que yo mucho más cosa más ridícula Cuál
is your channel RAE we are not even going to
es su canal RAE ni siquiera le vamos a
do it we are not even going to
hacer ni siquiera le vamos a hacer
promote it but only the fact
promoción pero solamente el hecho
magiito the fact that the guy I  with
maguito el hecho de que el tipo yo con
88 viewers I make his
88 viewers le pongo a temblar a su su
Stream tremble with 1,500 people applauding
Stream con mil 500 personas que aplauden
like seals that the guy is
allá como focas que el tipo esté
defaming people Every day every
difamando gente Todos los días todos los
day like that applauding him there and he's
días así aplaudiendolo allá y tiene
afraid that I with 89 viewers say the
miedo que yo con 89 viewers diga la un
kiss Mauro truth that gives a lot to
beso Mauro verdad eso da mucho que
think about I don't think I think that
pensar No creo que creo que eso
shows Who is the one who is lying And who
demuestra Quién es el que miente Y quién
is the one who is telling the truth that shows
es el que dice la verdad eso demuestra
Who is the one who is lying And who is the one who is
Quién es el que miente Y quién es el que
telling the truth Because if he's trying to
dice la verdad Porque si está intentando
close my Twitch channel it's because he doesn't
cerrarme mi canal de Twitch es porque no
want anyone to hear me and why doesn't he
quiere que nadie me escuche y por qué no
want anyone But if we're
quiere que nadie Pero si te estamos
putting you here creature
poniendo aquí criatura
but if you're making a
pero si estás haciendo un ridículo
tremendous fool of yourself all
tremendo todo el
day long to hear me What's the fear oliveira
día me escuche Cuál es el miedo oliveira
why are you scared What's the fear
por qué estás cagado Cuál es el miedo
are you wrapped up with those suitcases no
estás embolatada con esas maletas no
but Look listen to me if it's really
pero Mira escúchame si de verdad es
too much too much luggage I'll
demasiado demasiado equipaje Yo te
lend you a Carrión or I'll lend you one I'll
presto un Carrión o te presto una te
send you Let's put him in his place Look
mande Vamos a ponerle en su lugar Mira
donkey you know what I'm not even interested
burrillo sabes qué a mí ni me interesa
I don't even respond to  these
yo ni siquiera yo le respondo a esta
people and I don't even go around spamming
gente y yo ni siquiera ando spameando
the tweets that I make so that the people
los tweets que yo hago para que la gente
who see me here on Stream the FES that
que me ve aquí en Stream los FES que
are here every day so that
están aquí todos los días para que la
people don't even go and respond to
gente ni siquiera vaya y le responda a
these guys and this guy really believes
estos tipo y a este tipo de verdad crea
that what he's responding to here is
que lo que él está respondiendo aquí es
the truth. In other words, so that he continues
la verdad O sea para que él siga
believing in his world in his mind
creyéndose en su mundo en su mente
Absurd and in his fantasy world created
Absurda y en su mundo de fantasía creado
by idiots who respond to him in a
por por huevones que le responden en un
chat yes yes yes yes you're right oliveira
chat sí sí sí sí tienes razón oliveira
Yes yes yes yes you're right to all the
Sí sí sí sí tienes razón a todas las
defamations Yes yes yes brother
difamaciones Sí sí sí brother se
projects himself with absolutely everything why did he
proyecta con absolutamente todo por qué
insult you he has he has since
te insultó tiene tiene tiene desde que
his master defamed me and I defended myself by insulting me he
su amo me difamó y yo me defendí
took a
insultando insultándome se metió un
space on Twitter he said he was going to talk
espacio de Twitter dijo que iba a hablar
to me and what he did was bring the
conmigo y lo que hizo fue traerse al
other one from Dallas to
otro de mente del Dallas a pegar puros
scream what he did was repeat in Lu
gritos que lo que hizo fue repetir en Lu
words and words and words and
palabras y palabras y palabras y
words and
palabras y
repeat something important something important
repetir algo importante algo importante
Lu Find me the link please for the
Lu Búscame el enlace porfi para el
report the best drainer roars but of course
reporte el mejor drainer ruga pero claro
of course
por supuesto
[Music]
[Música]
Lu that says
Lu que diga
here continues in  loop up to this point is
aquí sigue en bucle hasta este momento
not going to stop okay a person who is not
no va a parar vale una persona que no
here I think it's clear how it
está está Yo creo que está claro cómo
is and I'll tell you okay okay Please find me the
está y ya te digo vale vale Búscame el
link for the report raet we're
enlace porfa para el reporte raet nos
going to see each other because I'm going to report you
vamos a ver porque te voy a denunciar
Okay You are obviously a criminal
Vale Eres un delincuente evidentemente
okay that's why they put you in jail let it be
vale por eso te metieron en la cárcel
clear to you okay We are going to
que te quede claro vale Te vamos a
report you on Twitch we are going to report you on
reportar el Twitch te vamos a reportar
Twitter OK And of course I'm going to Look
el Twitter OK Y por supuesto voy a Mira
here we have the link to
por aquí tenemos el enlace para
report it okay This is the link for
reportarlo vale Este es el enlace del
today's live okay But let's
directo de hoy vale Pero vamos voy a
talk to Juan Goina so that they
hablar con Juan goina para que te
report you there in Miami and and I think that and I
denuncien allí en Miami y y creo que y
think it's very clear what's going to
creo que es muy claro lo que te va a
happen to you is that you're going to have to leave the United
pasar que te vas a tener que ir de los
States I have put incitement to hatred
Unidos yo he puesto incitación al odio
man but I think it's that look I
hombre pero yo creo que es que mira que
never report eh I mean I never report
nunca reporto eh o sea nunca reporto a
anyone
nad
anything like that Because apart from The guy it
nada por el estilo Porque aparte El tipo
seems like he's a person who is not
se ve que es una persona que no está
well but man boy you are already threatening
bien pero hombre chico estás amenazando
small children dude it's awful I do
ya a niños pequeños colega está fatal Yo
n't know what substance you take or what you
no sé qué sustancia toma o es lo que
have for breakfast but you're not well your
Desayuna pero no estás bien tu
behavior on the internet is not right
comportamiento en internet no está bien
but not only on the internet not
pero no solamente en internet no
only on the internet your ex already
solamente en internet ya tu expareja
published some audios where you were yelling at him
publicó unos audios donde le gritabas
for stupid things you were screaming like crazy
por chorradas te ponías como un loco a
okay you're there fooling around your girlfriend
gritar vale estás ahí vacilando tu novia
as if she were a car the poor thing okay You
como si fuera un coche la pobre vale Te
go to the pool and you start taking
vas a la piscina y te pones a hacerle
pictures of girls without consent
fotos a chicas sin consentimiento
a person in love doesn't do that
ra una persona enamorada no hace eso
okay send her pictures of girls the
vale mandarle fotografías de chicas lo
first thing is to photograph girls there that
primero es fotografiar a chicas ahí que
could be Imagine that you have a
podrían ser Imagínate que tenéis una
sister, a cousin or something and there's an
hermana una prima o algo y hay un
inmate taking pictures of them without
recluso haciéndole fotos sin
consent
consentimiento
then what's going to happen to you is going to happen to you is that they're
pues te va a pasar lo que te va a pasar
going to kick you out of the United States I have no
que te van a echar de Estados Unidos no
doubt eh Also I have no
tengo ninguna duda eh Además no tengo
doubt I mean look at you eh
ninguna duda o sea fíjate tú eh Te lo
Everyone is telling you eh But
está diciendo todo el mundo eh Pero
well now the consequences will come to
bueno ahora vendrán las consecuencias a
me me I'm telling you I mean it doesn't mean
mí me me ya te digo O sea no me supone
anything to me eh what else luar Ah delox what delos
nada eh qué más luar Ah delox que delos
has said about the food let's see also
ha opinado del comi a ver también
Javi if you're going to take legal action
Javi si vas a tomar acciones legales
just do it Eh well that will have to
solo Hazlo Eh bueno eso tendrá que
decide I will search and they will have to
decidir Buscaré y me tendrán que
advise me if it is possible How is it done and
aconsejar si se puede Cómo se hace y
all that Roo  you understand me I mean
todo el Roo ese me entendéis O sea no lo
I didn't decide in the end I would put dal elox on him
decido yo al final yo le ponía dal elox
before I prefer that they call me nutel I'm
antes Prefiero que me llamen nutel esta
not going to forgive you for this super mustache and it's that
no te la pienso perdonar super bigote y
maduro there you can see him maduro
es que maduro ahí lo podéis ver maduro
in this comic that he publishes in
en el cómic este que saca él en
Venezuela Well I'm here This is
Venezuela Pues he salido yo aquí Este
me a kiss Mauro Thank you very much handsome
soy yo un beso Mauro Muchísimas gracias
here I am this This is me this one
guapo aquí estoy este Este soy yo este
here you know eh And he puts me dal elox like
aquí sabes eh Y me pone dal elox como
a fusion of Dalas and delox and then they
una fusión de Dalas y delox y luego han
put jabrik the canine and he put
puesto el jabrik el canino y ha puesto
like Javi oliveira Who is obviously
como a Javi oliveira Que obviamente es
a dog they have made him quite
un perro a él lo han puesto bastante
well in his line eh but they have made him
bien en su línea eh pero lo han puesto
like a two-headed dog with Ricky did that
como perro de dos cabezas con Ricky did
rickyedit has been drawn quite
que a rickyedit le han dibujado bastante
Chernobyl eh But
chernóbil eh Pero
well Ricky Ricky they haven't drawn him
bueno Ricky Ricky no le han dibujado
well delox another clown I mean I have to
bien delox otro payaso o sea yo tengo
change perfume eh I have to
que cambiar de perfume eh yo tengo que
change perfume delox you know who
cambiar de perfume delox tú sabes quién
this gibel has been that today Was
ha sido un este gibel que hoy Estaba
unworthy with r This is the same gibel I
indignos con r Esto es lo mismo gibel
already told you this this is a disgusting
esto ya os lo dije este es un asco de
person a very bad person and  Ricky
persona malísima persona y Ricky Lo
Same here Ricky Same here they are bad people they
mismo Ricky Lo mismo son malas personas
are filthy people okay they are filthy and
son gente [__] vale son gente [__] y
bad people delox has not spoken out again
mala delox no ha vuelto a pronunciarse
regarding the Cristo Spain issue Why
respecto al tema de Cristo Spain Por qué
delox What happened with CR Spain Why did you
delox Qué ha pasado con CR Spain Por qué
delete your entire channel all the
borraste todo tu canal todas las
collaborations he had because there is
colaboración que tenía porque hay por
a kid out there with an interview
ahí un chaval con una entrevista
saying that Crist Pain paid him 1%
diciendo que crist Pain le pagaba un 1%
of what people made from those who
de lo que le sacaba la peña a los que lo
promoted him Why don't you go out and
promocionaban Por qué no no sales a
criticize that delox I want to see you
criticar eso delox yo quiero verte a ti
The righteous objective the one that came out is to
El objetivo justiciero el que salió es
put it as pambi delox if you are not a
ponerlo de pambi delox si no eres un
dog you are Cristo Spain's dog and you
perro eres el perro de Cristo Spain y tú
are not a dog no Or yes no
no eres ningún perro no O sí no
delox Why did you delete your entire channel
delox Por qué borraste todo tu canal Por
Why did you delete your entire channel all of a
qué borraste todo tu canal entero de
sudden because you didn't like the
repente porque no te gustaban las
[Laughs]
[Risas]
thumbnails delo is Will's dog no
miniaturas delo es el perro de Will no
but apart from being Willy Rex's dog I
pero aparte de ser el perro de Willy Rex
want to know I am
Yo quiero saber me interesa
very interested even maduro knows that sinas he does
muchísimo hasta maduro sabe que sinas de
n't eat Haha And well grandpa it doesn't have
no come Jaja Y bueno abuelo no tiene
much to do with it but a friend of pambi from
mucho que ver pero una amiga pambi de
Twitter is going to retire from Twitter her
Twitter se va a retirar de Twitter se
name is minami can you send her a
llama minami le puedes mandar un mensaje
nice message  Well a kiss minami don't leave
bonito Pues un beso minami no te retires
Twitter Oh we recently had to
de Twitter Ay hace poco lo tuvimos que
publish it because the guy has no
publicar porque el tío es que no tiene
shame whatsoever he has no shame
vergüenza ninguna no tiene vergüenza
whatsoever
ninguna
and he started
e que se puso a
saying
decir
Oh very far it wasn't
Ay muy lejos no
very far this wasn't done done
estaba muy lejos no
look who consumes it Listen to this delo
mira quien consuma ser Escucha esto delo
that you haven't put this on your
que esto no lo has sacado en tu canal de
cryptocurrency channel delo when are you going to talk
criptomonedas delo cuándo vas a hablar
about
de
this the truth is that the
esto la verdad es que las
investigations are advancing at an
investigaciones están avanzando a una
incredible speed and this is very
velocidad increíble y esto es muy
positive for the victims that it is your
positivo para las víctimas que sea tu
community that consumes services in which
comunidad quien consuma servicios en los
we generate a surplus value and
que nosotros generamos una plusvalía y
that part of that generated surplus value is
que parte de esa plusvalía generada
channeled to you we
vehiculizar hacia ti nosotros
would be four and you would be
quedaríamos un cuatro y tú te quedarías
one and if you thought that romillo was
un uno y si pensabas que romillo estaba
alone in this then you are very wrong
solo en esto pues estás muy equivocado
cryptospain Not only did he scam thousands of
cryptospain No solo estafó a miles de
people but he also used
personas sino que además utilizó a
big influencers to make himself known
grandes influencers para darse a conocer
what happened deo In fact you don't talk on
qué ha pasado deo De hecho no hablas en
your channel No man tell it
tu canal No hombre cuéntalo
delo tell it yourself why he promoted CR
delo cuenta tú por qué promocionaba a CR
Spain delox on your channel and you had a
Spain delox en tu canal y tenías una
series of videos that you have deleted because
serie de vídeos que has borrado porque
you don't like the thumbnails
no te gustan las miniaturas
why I want you to explain this that
por qué yo quiero que expliques esto que
this kid is saying that this
está diciendo este chaval que este
kid says that Cristo Pain paid him
chaval dice que Cristo Pain le pagaba un
1% of what he earned at least to the Vice
1% de lo que ganaba por lo menos al Vice
at least to the Vice
por lo menos al Vice
delox this comes out And say something
delox esto sale Y di algo
delox No you are already Willy Reed's dog
delox No ya eres el perro de Willy reed
But don't be this guy's dog
Pero no vayas a ser el perro de este
either you tell me delox what it We'll
tampoco tú cuéntame delox qué lo Te te
send you a thumbnail so that you can
te mandamos un miniaturero para que para
republish all the videos
que vuelvas a publicar todos los vídeos
man and so you like the
hombre y que te gusten las
thumbnails you have it or rather so you can
miniaturas lo tenéis o sea para que
see a little bit of the Flow also comes out
veáis un poco el Flow también sale por
here my friend My friend Sergio tvh who in
aquí mi amigo Mi amigo Sergio tvh que de
fact recorded a podcast yesterday with him very
hecho grabamos podcast ayer con él muy
good podcast By the way and Jordi Wild who has
buen podcast Por cierto y Jordi Wild que
given him an onion face Poor guy
le han puesto una cara cebolla Al pobre
with how strong Jordi Wild is and they
con lo fuerte que está Jordi Wild y lo
put him here as if he had a I don't know guy
ponen aquí como si tuviera un no sé tío
a protuberance on his body so bad they
una protuberancia en el cuerpo así
hooked me they hooked me up with a
chunga me engancharon me engancharon a
[ __ ] crazy person next to me they put
un [__] loco al lado me han puesto al
Dallas there and he was already asking me for a
Dallas ahí y ya me estaba pidiendo un
contract you know he was asking me for a
contrato sabes me estaba pidiendo un
contract and I didn't I don't want to sign
contrato y yo no que no quiero firmar
anything You know I don't want to have a threesome
nada Sabes que no quiero hacer un trío
with Lizy please
con lizy por favor
[ __ ] dude They're son  the same eh
ostia tío Son son lo mismo eh
man they are the same they are terrible eh
tío son lo mismo están fatal eh
And well, nothing has become confusing for us it has become
Y bueno pues nada se nos ha liado se nos
confusing for us the afternoon has become confusing for us and well, well,
ha liado se nos ha liado la tarde y pues
in the end we have had to, we have had to
bueno Pues al final hemos tenido hemos
succumb not to the to the
tenido que que sucumbir no al al al
power of Super
poder de Super
bigote God of my life eh they are
bigote Dios de mi vida eh
each one is worse eh
están está cada un cu peor eh
of We
del Nosotros te mandamos un miniaturero
are sending you a miniature, damn We are sending you a miniature that I am very I am very interested in your series with CR Pain How he promoted his talks How he recruited people so that you hire the service of CR Spain okay delox it's that I don't see you talking about that man on your on your
no te veo hablar de eso tío en tu en tu
daily channel I still see you talking about
canal diario te veo todavía hablando de
pambi we don't know about pambi anymore man
pambi lo de pambi ya no lo sabemos tío
talk about Cristo Pain damn that
habla de lo de Cristo Pain [__] que eso
interests us a lot
nos interesa mucho que me han escrito
a few people from the world of Christ have written to me
unas cuantas personas del mundo cristo
to say a few
para decir unas
things and leave it already forget about the
cosillas y deja ya olvídate de los
dogs forget about the dogs delox that I
perros olvídate de los perros delox que
don't know what's wrong with you with the dogs that
no sé qué te pasa con los perros que te
something strange has been left there forget about the
ha quedado ahí algo raro olvídate de los
dogs delox Tell me about CR Pain
perros delo Háblame de CR Pain
Mimi blah blah blah  Mimi Dallas mii
Mimi bla bla bla Mimi Dallas mii
miot restraining order my my By the
miot orden de alejamiento mi mi Por
way they told me that Ricky has been
cierto me dijeron que Ricky ha ido
saying
diciendo
and he does it completely with evil okay he
y lo hace plenamente con con maldad vale
has been saying that he has filed the
ha ido diciendo que me ha puesto el la
complaint on purpose
reclamación a propósito
eh that he is not going to remove it that he asks
eh que no la va a quitar que se lo pide
the kings and blah blah blah and all that
a los reyes y patatín patatán y todo el
stuff okay Ricky I have a
rollo ese vale Ricky yo tengo una
copyright claim that I am going to
reclamación por copyright que la voy a
solve obviously I am going to
solucionar evidentemente la voy a
solve it because it is fair use you know
solucionar porque es uso legítimo sabes
what I don't have
lo que yo no tengo
Ricky a complaint for
Ricky una denuncia por violencia de
gender violence I don't have that at the moment you
género esa no la tengo de momento tú
have any by chance I don't know to
tienes alguna por casualidad no sé para
measure our
medirnos las
[ __ ] and report because maybe maybe
pollas y denunci porque a lo mejor a lo
the kings haven't brought me
mejor los reyes a mí no me han traído
that But they brought you something The
eso Pero a ti te han traído algo Los
Kings
Reyes
okay I'm going
vale voy
member here for the face
miembro aquí por la cara
no gel they realize that we are in the
no gel se dan cuenta que estamos en el
rewind this year the discussion went
rewind este año la tertulia llegó
quite far I don't care about anything
bastante lejos a mí no me importa nada
I suck a whole egg I want my Esla
me chupo todo un huevo Yo quiero mi Esla
nothing more people Did you ever think
nada más gente Alguna vez se pensaron
that there would be a mess just by putting a
que habría quilombo solo por poner un
30 second animatic in a rewind
animatic de 30 segundos en un rewind
well neither do I literally this is the
bueno yo tampoco literalmente es la
third time that I record this  video the
tercera vez que grago este video la
first one was very technical explaining how I
primera fue muy técnica explicando cómo
did everything step by step the second one was the
hice todo paso a paso la segunda fue el
first day that the rewind was launched and today
primer día que se lanzó el rewine y hoy
today I have a couple of things to say
hoy tengo un par de cosas que decir la
people are very crybabies noy posh hope they do
gente es muy llorona noy pija que les
well dude let's go from the beginning it
vaya bien boludo vamos desde el inicio
's Javiera the youtuber who did the
es javiera el youtuber el cual hizo el
rewind this year or at least one of
rewind de este año o por lo menos uno de
the rewinds of all these
los rewind de se hicieron todos estos
rewinds were made damn Seba just gave away another
rewind [__] seba acaba de regalar otro
50 don't start with the madness friend
50 sea no empieces con la locura amigo
A
Un
kiss a kiss friend Thank you so much man
beso un beso amigo Muchísimas gracias
[ __ ]
[__]
[ __ ] How many members are we right now
[__] Cuántos miembros somos ahora mismo
5008 plus the 150 that they just gave away
5008 más los 150 que acaban de regalar
we have enough of your
vamos sobra de te
family says Seba Orellano
familia dice seba orellano
Ortellado that the other two Sebas
ortellado que vengan los otros dos Sebas
of always come and I double them I mean
de siempre y los duplico o sea
this Seba just gave away 150 members
este seba acaba de regalar 150 miembros
but he says that if the other Sebas come
pero dice que si vienen los otros Sebas
what did he say double or
él qué ha dicho duplica o
triple double double again eye
triplica duplica vuelve a duplicar ojo
eh eye
eh ojo
there year youtuber of gossip friend or I don't know
ahí año youtuber de salseo amigo o no sé
what from Dallas review dasas I ca for the
qué de Dallas review dasas me ca para el
ass  literally because of him this year I got
[__] literalmente por él este año me
doxed and I had some kind of
doxearon y tuve unos comentarios un poco
beautiful comments for three days in a row just
hermosos durante tres días seguidos solo
for making a petero meme this we start
por Hacer un meme petero esto partimos
with the fact that he doesn't have a very good reputation let's
con que no tiene muy buena fama que
say or rather he's been getting into kiros
digamos o sea se viene metiendo en kiros
with Stream celebrities and friends of mine I
con Stream famosos y amigos míos estoy
agree with him and the truth is that he didn't do a lot of
de acuerdo con él y la verdad que muchas
things to me something to me no
cosas no me hizo algo a mí no
literally I worked for him a few
literalmente trabajé para él hace unos
years ago I made these logos over it's
años atrás yo hice estos logos over es
true mind you I have a tattoo mind It's true I have this
verdad ojo que yo tengo un tatuaje ojo
tattooed I have a drawing of It's that to me the the
tatuado un dibujo de Es que a mí me el
How Tina draws I love I mean
el Cómo dibuja Tina a mí me encanta O
whenever I can or whenever I
sea yo siempre que pueda o siempre que
need and whenever she wants of
necesite y siempre que ella quiera por
course I'm going to call her okay I mean
supuesto yo la voy a llamar vale O sea
she did this it's true it's true Well
ella hizo esto es verdad es verdad Bueno
in fact I think that the outro is not the
de hecho creo que todavía el outro no la
start window I think not but the
ventana de inicio creo que no pero el
outro I still have it on well
outro sí lo tengo puesto todavía bueno
no what do we have in the other Well I don't know
no qué tenemos en el otro Bueno no lo sé
but it's true man I mean
pero es verdad tío o sea
literally literally
literalmente literalmente estos dibujos
she made these drawings and I think it's wonderful you
lo hizo ella y me parece una maravilla
know that I really like the way she
sabes que a mí me gusta mucho como ella
draws I mean whenever I need
dibuja o sea yo siempre que necesite
some
algo de dibujos
cartoons If she wants  whenever she
animados Si ella quiere siempre que ella
wants, well obviously she has to
quiera pues evidentemente tiene que
want it, I'm going to hire her, I'm
querer la voy a la voy a contratar la
going to call
voy a llamar a
her, even a tattoo, always with you. My
ella hasta un tatuaje siempre ti mi
tattoo, I mean, my tattoo is drawn
tatuaje o sea mi tatuaje está dibujado
by her, eh, look, eh, it's true, it's true,
por ella eh ojo eh es verdad es verdad
a work relationship and she always
una relación de laburo y conmigo siempre
had the best with me, the guy, I mean, we're friends, that's why
tuvo la mejor el chón o sea somos amigos
dude, I don't even know him. It's like
por eso boludo ni lo conozco es como
when they make fun of me just for working with
cuando me bardean solo por trabajar con
x or y streamer, it's noticeable that people
x o y streamer cómo se nota que la gente
on Twitter don't like me, super [ __ ], via.
de Twitter no la buon super perra via ya
With this, we started from the beginning.
con esto partimos desde el inicio vino
Javi came and asked me if I wanted to be there,
Javi me preguntó si tenía ganas de estar
that such streamers were going to be there and since it
que iban a estar tales streamers y como
was a rewind of gossip, I thought it was cool.
era un rewind de salseo me pareció piola
More than anything because it's the world where I
Más que nada porque es el mundo donde me
handle myself and where I work and where I know a
manejo y donde laburo y donde conozco
lot of inmates. Besides, Javi
muchas internas Además de que Javi me
told me that he liked my style, that he
dijo que le gustaba mi estilo que le
liked my. Yes, let's see, I practically
gustaba mi Sí a ver prácticamente me
remembered her too. Because there were
acordé también de ella Porque eran
several scenes that were animated, there
varias escenas que eran de animación
was the one with
estaba la de
em
em
eh frikis and then the other one that did
eh frikis y luego el otro que hacía lo
the AI ​​​​thing and I say,
de la ia y digo
wow, having an animated scene of
[__] que haya una escena animada de
this
esta
girl would be cool, right? I mean, there are several
chica molaría no o seaas hay varios
types of  animations too and so on my
tipos de animaciones también y demás mi
humor and she was going to be another other
humor y ella iba a ser otra otra
animation was going to tell me that there was going to be two
animación iba me dijo que iba a ser dos
one of selling and another of the
una de una de seling y otra de la
chat so it seemed cool to me the
tertulia entonces me pareció Guay la
other one the other one didn't do it in the end I
otra la otra no la hizo al final
understand that due to time someone who
entiendo que por el tiempo alguien que
knows half sure seemed to me to lose the
conoce medio seguro me pareció piera la
idea because the truth is that if it weren't
idea porque la verdad es que si no fuera
one of Javi or any other streamer with
un de Javi o de cualquier streamer con
a horror more so that he sucked my h
un horor más así que le chupaba mi h
everything could not have been
todo no hubiera podido estar
directly this when I was
directamente esto le cuando estaba
asking for the animations I remembered
pidiendo las animaciones me acordé de
Tina because I really like
Tina porque a mí me gusta mucho el
Tina's drawing style the
estilo de dibujo que tiene Tina la
truth is I really like the drawing style
verdad el estilo de dibujar me gusta
and I say hopefully this girl wants to
mucho y digo ojalá esta chica quiera
participate and I asked her and she
quiera participar y se lo pregunté y me
said yes what happens is that I
dijo que sí lo que pasa es que se lo se
asked her very hastily you know I would have
lo pedí muy precipitado sabes a mí me
loved for this to be ment
hubiera encantado que esto fuera amiento
complaint in color okay imagine if he had
denuncia a color vale imagínate hubiera
been in
estado el a
color that the nauter had been
color que hubiera estado el el nauter
with the suit of the one that he wears in these
con el traje del el ese que se pone en
debates no that goes with the
en los debates estos no que va con el
Venom suit t color was to make a
traje de Venom t color era hacer un
sketch between 20 to 30 seconds of  whatever I
sketch de entre 20 a 30 segundos de lo
want free rein there it seemed
que yo quiera vía libre ahí me pareció
cool to me Jai told me do whatever the
repiola Jai me dijo hacé lo que se te
[ __ ] you want And the truth is I'd be
cante el rto Y la verdad es que les
lying if I said my first choice
mentiría si dijera que mi primera opción
was the talk show. The truth is I was going to do
fue la tertulia yo la verdad iba a hacer
a sketch with Celin and Alana, it was Alana.
un sketch de celin y alana era alana
Well I thought she told me it was going to be the
Bueno yo cre me dijo que iba a ser los
two of them. I think I said [ __ ] great, well,
dos creo que yo dije de [__] madre pues
two scenes, you know, but I
dos escenas sabes pero
understand that it wasn't going well with
pero entiendo que era no iba bien de
time, of course I asked her if I would have
tiempo claro es que se lo pedí si se lo
asked her months ago, man, but I
hubiera pedido con meses tío pero es que
was asking on the fly as they were
fui pidiendo sobre la macha conforme se
coming to mind, man,
me iban viniendo a la cabeza tío
stopping the audience that they were going to be
un parando al público que iban a ser
cute, I mean, it was another type of sketch but it was
monos o sea era otro tipo sketch pero
going to be another topic, she wanted to be the one
iba a ser otro tema ella quería ser la
on the talk show and it seemed fine to me,
de la tertulia y me pareció bien la
honestly, well, yes, because that's how
verdad pues s Sí porque así tenía c meo
the talk show had it going. I mean, in the end there will be
la tertulia O sea que al final tenga
better or worse times with them, but
épocas mejores o peores con ellos pero
well, let's see if it's an episode where we're going to
bueno a ver si es un r en donde vamos
make reference to
hacer referencia de de
our world, not that it's the gossip and all
nuestro mundo no que es el salseo y todo
that stuff. Well, yes, I mean, no, we're not going to
el rollo Pues sí O sea no no vamos a
deny that they have a presence, no, let's
negar que tienen presencia no vamos el
Uncle Shur was already out, his cameo I thought about it
tío shur ya salía que su cameo lo pensé
from the beginning and from eh to Ai
desde desde el principio y de eh to Ai
the initial scene came to me
se me ocurrió la escena inicial como
like an intro no and Tommy Tommy was the
como de intro no y Tommy Tommy fue el
first one who sent me the scene I think eh
primero que me mandó la escena creo eh
also okay I had already asked Shur
además vale yo ya le había pedido a shur
eh his scene and there's the mess pu I
eh su escena y ahí está el kilombo pu yo
knew that Javi had some problems
sabía que Javi tenía algunos problemas
with the vast majority of the chat room there was
con la gran mayoría de la tertulia había
a very high probability that they wouldn't even be on
una probabilidad muy grande que ni estén
top of it I knew that they were going to be south
encima yo sabía que iban a estar sur
and in reality I don't have a problem with
y en realidad no tengo problema con
anyone well let's see the taja thing no let's see
nadie bueno a ver lo del taja no a ver
he has it with me I mean I don't have
lo tiene él conmigo o sea yo no tengo
any problem I don't know what I'm telling you he
ningún problema no sé que te digo me me
was insulting me not in a Stream not
estuvo insultando no en en un Stream no
like very strongly I
así como muy fuerte
think he said more about himself than about me
creo que que dijo más de él que de mí
that type of insult And if I criticized him
ese tipo de insulto Y si yo lo criticado
in the past for something well I only
en el pasado por algo pues Solamente le
told him to tell me that it was the criticism in
dije que me dijera que era la crítica en
which I had gone too far with him and such he did
la que yo me había pasado con él y tal
n't know how to tell me And and little else but it's not
no supo decirme Y y poco más pero no es
like he has a problem I mean
como que tenga un problema o sea
no I don't even think he has it
no no creo ni siquiera que él lo tenga
with me I don't know I think it's some heat
conmigo No sé creo que es algún calentón
in  at some specific moment I don't know the truth
en algún momento puntual no sé la verdad
but I don't think we're people who
pero no creo que seamos una persona que
think about each other
pensemos el uno el uno del otro
constantly the
constantemente la
truth I mean ybel well rat Nobel is going
verdad O sea ybel pues va rat Nobel va
to be there for a while tomy that
rato a estar tomy mucho que iban a estar
the others were going to be on top of some for it
los otros encima de alguna for se
ended up being confirmed that if I didn't do
terminó confirmando que si yo no hacía
something like that they were going to be because I spoke to
algo así iban a estar porque les habló a
the others about the
los otros de la
discussion I ask why instead of that you
tertulia pregunto por qué lugar de eso
didn't put
no puso
a part of the discussion wasn't it
un una parte de la tertulia no era
better some of the clips like that kind of
mejor alguno de los clips así medio
funny
divertido
but it's art that they
pero tiene arte que
have to have an animation I mean
tengan que que tenga una animación O sea
that each one appears in a
que cada uno aparezca de una forma
different way also has its grace and
diferente también tiene su gracia y
besides being Tina who is like very
aparte siendo Tina que es como muy
close to them
cercana a ellos
no and what is it dude I mean it's a parody it's
no y qué es tío o sea es una parodia es
an animation I was predisposed to not
una animación venía predispuesto a no
be happy about anything literally
estar contento por nada literalmente los
I put them that I say Yes it seems good to me that they
he puesto que digo Sí me parece bien que
are Of course it is
estén Por supuesto que sí ya había
I had already included tomy and shul who are the ones with whom I
metido yo a tomy y a shul que son con
have contact but I say I spoke
los que tengo contacto pero digo hable
with Tina to do the animation And
con tina para que hiciera la animación Y
she says I would like to do the one of the
ella dice me gustaría hacer la de la
discussion and I say Oh well Cool Yes it seems
tertua y digo Ah pues Guay Sí me parece
good to me that they are cool I mean it was on purpose that it
bien que estén onda O sea fue querendo
gave  disgusting eh I mean he can't even
que daba asco eh o sea no puede ni
talk eh Maybe later it would have
hablar eh A lo mejor luego se me hubiera
occurred to me to ask Guibel something and I would have
ocurrido pedirle algo a guibel y se lo
asked him eh I mean no no no I don't rule out I don't
hubiera pedido eh o sea no no no
rule out that maybe
descarto no descarto que a lo mejor
[ __ ] eh after asking Latina for the
[__] eh después de pedir latina los
drawings there were still people that I
dibujos todavía hubo gente a la que le
asked youtuber to the ones I asked Auron
pedí youtuber a las que le pedí auron me
sent it to me the same day I think eh I mean you
lo mandó el mismo día creo eh o sea lo
can see it by the clothes I think it was
podéis ver por la ropa creo que fue el
his last Stream from Well in fact I think
último Stream de él de Bueno de hecho
Auron sent it to me almost the same day eh
auron me lo mandó casi el mismo día eh
from I mean it doesn't make sense eh I mean I kept
de O sea no tiene sentido eh o sea seguí
asking for things I don't rule out maybe it would have
pidiendo cosas no descarto a lo mejor se
occurred to me to ask Guibel for something I do
me hubiera ocurrido pedirle a gbel algo
n't know
No lo sé la
honestly to do something for people that I really like far away
verdad hacer algo para gente que me cae
Dear [ __ ] or something you must have
muy bien lejos Dear [__] o algo habrán
seen it's not a specific clip
visto no er un clip en concreto ya
tell me how do you review a [ __ ]
díganme ustedes cómo se reseña un [__]
year of content in 20 seconds you
año de contenido en 20 segundos vos
come in one day Random and everything you
entas un día Random y est todo lo que
heard messy noises
escuchabas quilombo ruidos chistes de
dark humor jokes it's an exaggeration
humor negro es una exageración
obviously it's not a specific clip
obviamente no es un clip concreto Así
So nothing once that  I look for clips I
que nada una vez que busco clips los
edit them I do the animation in just two days
edito hago la animación en Solo dos días
this time I only used the iPad like I did with
esta vez solo usé el iPad como hice con
all my other past animatics because I did
todos mis otros animatics pasados porque
n't want to start experimenting and doing
no quería ponerme a experimentar y hacer
other things with time against the clock or
otras cosas con el tiempo contra reloj o
rather I have to stop doing that since
sea tengo que dejar de hacer eso ya que
at least I have 5 years less life
por lo menos tengo 5 años menos de vida
so once the Porto project was finished
así que una vez finalizado el proyecto
and I retouched it in Premier another
Porto y lo retoco en Premier acabó otro
point ended that I saw several who complained that it
punto que vi varios que se quejaron de
was a personal pull there javis
que era una tiradera personal allá javis
if he decided to pass or not or try the
si él decidió pasar o no o probar el
script that I made but yes I will
guion que yo hice pero sí les voy a
tell you let's see is that
decir a ver es que
sincerely There was only one little thing that
sinceramente Solo hubo una cosilla que
from the script that she made for me that was a
del guion que ella me hizo que era un
joke about gibel that I said I know that they are
chiste de gibel que dije yo sé que son
jokes from her channel I know that these jokes are
chistes de su canal Sé que estos chistes
made by the tertulia
los hace la tertulia
em but I can't put this joke in the
em pero no puedo poner este chiste en el
rewind because
rewind porque
suddenly Auron collaborates suddenly
de repente colabora auron de repente
Marta Díaz and Alfa collaborate suddenly
colabora Marta Díaz y Alfa de repente
people collaborate that when they find
colaboran gente que cuando se encuentre
this joke they don't know who this
con este chiste no saben quién es este
guy is they don't know you know La Movida they
tío no saben sabes La Movida se
find this comment it was a
encuentran con este comentario fue un
comment the only thing then the subject is
comentario lo único luego el tema es
obviously I think I think I said something like
evidentemente creo Creo que le dije algo
no  to rebuke anyone I don't know what
así como no increpar a nadie no sé qué
but evidently I understand that we
pero evidentemente entiendo que nosotros
in which we handle ourselves will not
en los que nos manejamos no le va a
offend pan dos cuernitos there be if
ofender a pan dos cuernitos ahí sea si
himself has made fun of that subject you
mismo ha hecho burlas de ese tema me
understand it's like when he called me frikis
entiendes es como cuando me puso frikis
with a Correa I don't think it was in what
en con una Correa No creo que fue en lo
Fran's thing No what I tell you
lo de Fran No qué te digo
be I'm not going to understand I'm not going to get
sea no me voy a entiend no me voy a
angry about it nor am I going to start
enfadar por eso ni me voy poner a
crying I don't care
llorara me da igual
understand my idea put r for
entiend mi idea poner a r por opinar
deliberately giving his opinion on my work
deliberadamente sobre mi laburo
Ricky got involved with Rick
se metió Ricky cona Rick
porin
porin
soo seti with miniature designers and
soo seti con diseñadores miniatur y
Editors well said it's similar to what
Editores bien dicho es parecido a lo que
some people do they take advantage and
hacen algunas personas aprovechan y se
go to other countries to pay less taxes
van a otros países para tributar menos
taking advantage of their situation to get
aprovechando su situación para conseguir
more
más
money defending us in quotes
dinero defendernos entre comillas
making us look like
haciéndonos quedar como retrasados
mentally [ __ ] that we work for two pesos
mentales que trabajamos por dos pesos
because we are from latam what s me calling us
por ser de latam qué s yo tratándonos de
starving and an exploiter and it's
muerto de hambre y aur explotador y es
like and from Mexico Well more of the same
como y de Mex Bueno más de lo mismo la
Tina Tina didn't have a job Lauro
tina tina no tenía laburo el Lauro lo
was doing it for someone else  Tina is from
estaba haciendo otra persona Tina es de
Venezuela no Tina is from Venezuela
Venezuela no Tina es de Venezuela
Argentina feeling very low but I think it's
Argentina senent muy bajo pero yo creo
lower working for him
que es más bajo trabajar para el tí
working is incredible I think what is it that
trabajar en increíble Yo creo que el qué
Tin does to uncle sh
es lo que le hace Tin al tío sh
eh I've seen the the some well the
eh yo he visto la la alguna bueno los
stickers I don't understand no the stickers and
stickers no entiendo no los stickers y
the Well I'm going to ask Tina
la Pues yo le voy a encargar a Tina
things eh I don't know what but I don't know maybe we have to
cosas eh No sé el qué pero no sé a lo
renew the stickers or
mejor hay que renovar los stickers o
something I'm a little embarrassed because I'm like
algo no me da pena un poco porque soy
very lazy for that for that but maybe
como muy vago para esa para eso pero a
we should do things I don't know animations I don't know something I'll think about it is going but working incredible But pure laziness contact pure laziness the same subject Only that directly getting into me on repeated
directamente conmigo en reiteradas
occasions in the year and mind you I'm not
ocasiones en el año y amente yo no
staying behind what time do you go out for the
quedándome atrás a qué hora sales por el
bread Tina so as not to go out at that time
pan tina para para no salir a esa hora
dude What time do you go out for the bread Tina so as not to go out at that time gy for I
güey A qué hora sales por el pan tina
mean
para no salir a esa hora gy para o sea
gey [ __ ] girl with nothing to do gey Don't [ __ ] with
gey [__] morra sin que hacer gey No
me Tina Don't [ __ ] with me what time do you go out for
[__] Tina No [__] qué hora sales por
the bread Tina  so as not to go out at that hour gey
el pan tina para no salir a esa hora gey
my girl to sleep her milk and to cuddle
a mi niña a dormir su lechita y a mimir
Tina no her milk and to cuddle her milk
Tina no su lechita y a mimir su lechita
and to cuddle I don't go with people who act
y a mimir no me van con la gente que va
like martyrs or superiors on the networks So
de martirs o superiores en las redes Así
yeah closing that point a bit the
que sí cerrando un poco ese punto la
idea was mine the people who know my
idea fue mía la gente que conozca mi
channel and my humor and my networks know that I
canal y mi humor y mis redes sabe que
always say caricatures of people
siempre dice caricaturas de la gente
remember how I am
acorda como me
this that illustration was made by Tina no
es esta esa ilustración la hizo Tina no
but well angry angry Tina ge angry
pero bueno ardida ardida Tina ge ardi
Tina the other day I wake up with each
Tina el otro día me levanto con cada
message that to see my Twitter
mensaje que a ver a mi Twitter
was there you have made them look
estuvo los has hecho quedar
bad you have fallen on me dude getting into
mal te me has caído macho metiéndote en
Jabi Oliveira's ruen I did not have almost
el ruen de jabi oliveira no tuve casi
anything bad on these people's channels
nada mal en los canales de esta gente
there is a pure audience that hates me eh but
hay pura audiencia que me odia eh pero
that hates me on a personal level eh I mean
que me odia de nivel personal eh o sea
look at the channels that the
fíjate tú los canales que los
comments that I put out the other day eh they
comentarios que que saqué el otro día eh
were saying that it was okay that
que estaban diciendo que estaba bien que
Ricky gave me a strike that as long
Ricky me pusiera un strike que siempre
as it is Javi eh that it is okay I mean they are
que sea Javi eh que está está bien o sea
people  and I saw 100 messages like that I knew I was
gente y vi 100 mensajes así yo sabía que
going to get hate on reine for being from
iba a tener hate el reine por ser de
Javier Oliveira simple but stupid
Javier oliveira simple pero boludo
literally without more looking
literal sin más viéndolo en
back it wasn't that bad I'm not here
retrospectiva no fue para tanto no vengo
to defend it as if it were a great video
a defender como si fuera un gran video
eh For me it has a lot of these internal ones there
eh Para mí tiene muchos estes internos
are sketches that last quite a while I mean yes they
hay sketches que duran bastante O sea sí
shouldn't last that long More than anything
no deberían durar tanto Más que nada
because year after year we have the most
porque año a año tenemos el cerebro más
rotten brains and if you don't put a sketch with
podrido y si no pones un sketch con
at least three Gameplays of s Surfer the
mínimo tres Gameplays de s Surfer el
eight it doesn't give people the lady
ocho no da de la gente la señora
dancing sex is at least bizarre
bailando sexo es cuanto menos bizarro
the subject ends badly if it would have been good to
mal acaba el tema si hubiera sido bueno
specify type rwi from Javi
que se especificara tipo rwi de Javi
Veira or rwi from the Javi Leira community
veira o rwi de la comunidad Javi leira
Because if you put rin it's only understood that it's
Porque si pones rin solo se so entiende
cool And the truth is that it's
que al molón Y la verdad es que se hab
like precisely because there wasn't a
como que justamente como no había un
budget as such those of us who were there were
presupuesto como tal los que estuvimos
idiots it was because I wanted to
ahí fueron de boludo fue porque quería
make a small tribute to the people who
hacer un pequeño tributo a la gente que
gave me so many funny moments this
me dio tantos momentos graciosos en este
year and people that I appreciate and that I like
año y gente que lo aprecio y que me cae
a lot but oh well Nothing end of the year
muy bien pero bueno Nada fin de año la
people are really hated or something  that they do
gente está muy odiada o sea cosa que
Even if they are something for them it is
hagan Por más que sean algo para ellos
also going to be [ __ ] like the issue of
también va a ser [__] como el tema de
the ia dude I with the issue of the laa I do not get
la ía boludo yo con el tema de laa ni me
involved because I am making a video of
meto porque estoy haciendo un video de
the artists against the ias I am just
los artistas contra las ias Solo que
saying that they complain dude What did they want, for it to
digo que se quejan boludo Qué querían
come out and turn into Hulk, to
que salga y y se convierta en Hulk que
animate it in 3D they know the n they are
lo animen en 3D saben la n están
criticizing pure criticizing I mean the issue
criticando puro criticar o sea el tema
of the I mean yes yes I agree
de la O sea yo sí sí estoy de acuerdo en
that we should have
que teníamos que
summarized a few dozen to have
e haber resumido unas cuantas decenas
summarized to have done everything
haberl resumido haberlo hecho todo como
faster Pin Pin Pin Pin I would have taken
más rápido Pin Pin Pin Pin yo hubiera
out some almost entire scenes eh
sacado algunas escenas casi enteras eh
In fact eh m I can't go back now
De hecho eh m Yo ya no se puede volver
but I should have
atrás pero sí que tenía que haber haber
delayed the premiere a day and have been
[__] el estreno un día y haber
that night reviewing the entire run
estado esa noche repasando el ran entero
and putting it more to my liking the order and
y poniéndolo más a mi gusto el orden y
having put in some transitions from one
haber metido algunas transiciones de una
thing to another but well some little things
cosa a la otra pero bueno alguna cosilla
no But well I think it's not a bad
no Pero bueno creo que no es un mal
video I mean I think it's cinema really I
vídeo o sea creo que es cine realmente
think it's cinema I saw it again after a few
creo que es cine lo volví a ver al cabo
days and I think cinema is a it's
de los días y creo que cine es una es
a [ __ ] marvel So it's true that
una [__] maravilla Así que es verdad que
for people outside of
para la gente de fuera de la comunidad
our community Well maybe there are too many
nuestra Pues a lo mejor demasiados
inside jokes that only we can
e chistes internos que solamente podemos
catch but I also think that in
pillar nosotros pero también creo que en
general the majority of the people who appeared
general la mayoría de gente que aparecía
and Cam understood each other if you more or less
y de Cam se entendían si más o menos
know the entire internet you know what
conoces a todo internet sabes lo que
happens that also these people the
pasa que también e esta gente las
communities of these people do not leave the
comunidades de esta gente no salen del
same circle okay eh And and we already
círculo mismo vale eh Y y nosotros ya
know that we moved through several
sabéis que nos movimos por varias
communities and for several things no no I'm
comunidades y por varias cosas no no yo
not going to do more eh sun air I'm not
no voy a hacer más eh sol aire yo no me
going to get involved in this again I'll
voy a meter más otra vez en esto ya me
invent another mess to get into
inventaré otro marrón en el que meterme
but the AI ​​thing rawai's work is
pero lo de la ia el trabajo de rawai es
[ __ ]
una [__]
wonderful It's [ __ ] wonderful I mean it
maravilla Es una [__] maravilla O sea me
seemed [ __ ] crazy to me This seems
pareció una [__] locura Esto me parece
[ __ ] crazy to me And I work what is that
una [__] locura Y laburo qué es eso
selling Gabi but it's like for
vender a Gabi pero es como para
any streamer for Pedrito 44 I mean
cualquier streamer para Pedrito 44 o sea
this is [ __ ] crazy the [ __ ] I have to
esto es una [__] locura lo de [__] le
send Fran something that he
tengo que mandar a Fran una cosa que me
asked me for man and I forgot man I
pidió tío y se me olvidado tío me
always remember this time you know what it is there were
acuerdo siempre de esta hora saben t qu
some complaining about the
es eso había algunos quejándose de la
voice some of the clips  or of evel and
voz algunos de de los clips o de evel y
the guys from the chat that have
de los chicos de la tertulia que tengan
shitty voices was kind of the joke
voces de [__] era medio el chiste
because I didn't ask everyone to record a
porque no le pedí a todos que graben una
specific scene for the rewi Well
escena específica para el rewi Bueno
nothing the one that was kind of heard for
nada la que sí se escuchó medio para el
[ __ ] was evel's last line like he
[__] fue la última línea de evel como él
said in a clip eh he recorded it being on the
dijo en un clip eh lo grabó estando en
couch I thought it was going to sound a
un sillón pensé que se iba a escuchar un
little better
poco mejor
me To think that Tina told me record this
yo Pensar que Tina me dijo grabame esto
thing with the antlers and the
lo del cornamentas y lo
other thing I recorded lying on that couch
otro se lo grabé acostado en ese sillón
while watching a series and I send him a
mientras veía una serie y le mando un
What's up
Qué pasa
antlers What's up
cornamenta Qué pasa
antlers shitty audio dude
cornamenta [__] de audio cabrón le
sends him [ __ ] the girl asks you for an audio
manda [__] te pide la chavala un audio
and you send it to him like this What's up with
y se lo mandas así Qué pasa con
rameta and ready to send me recorded
rameta y dispuesto a mí me mandó grabado
with his microphone The joke was going to
con su micrófono Es que la gracia iba a
be that something or rather imagine that even
ser que algo o sea imagínense que hasta
when he came I la caca Ah he knows each other in
cuando vino I la caca Ah se conoce en
person I didn't show him anything because I wanted it to
personaa no le mostré nada porque quería
be a surprise for almost everyone only
que sea una sorpresa para casi todos sol
Tom I showed him some
lo Tom le mostré alguna que otra
animation but then the rest didn't know
animación pero después el resto no sabía
anything bu jurn I wanted to bother him that Us the
nada bu jurn lo quise molestar que Us la
ia that uses tior  for the news I
ía que utiliza tior para los noticieros
liked our participation I must
a mí me gustó nuestra participación debo
say our participation because it
decirlo nuestra participación porque
is animated and they did not put a funny scene of
está animada y no pusieron una escena de
the discussion with all the ones there are
la tertulia graciosa con todas las que
Because the
hay Porque el
plan is a funny scene I mean but it
plan es una escena graciosa o sea pero
is not a funny scene a scene that
no es una escena graciosa una escena que
is parodied in cartoons of
está parodiada en dibujos animados de
a person from your circle or rather that
una persona de vuestro círculo o sea que
represents you orig directly
os representa orig directamente
or rather the content of the discussion he did not
o sea lo el contenido de la tertulia no
ask us he asked
nos lo pidió a nosotros se lo pidió a
Tina I know but if he would have taken it from some
Tina ya sé pero hubiera sacado de algún
extreme it would have been much funnier
extremo hubiera sido mucho más gracioso
I took it But then it is from
yo lo tomé Pero entonces tiene de
Uruguay not like gibel like I don't know it seems to me it
Uruguay no como gibel como no sé me pare
seemed like a nice detail at
me pareció un detalle bonito en
first What's up eclipse says man yes
principio Qué pasa eclipse dice tío si
yes it is more special that it is
que si es que es más especial que esté
animated Exactly not
animada Exactamente no más
cooler We were not even going to go out it was
chulo Nosotros ni íbamos a salir fue
Tina's idea and she did it with love Man
idea de Tina y lo hizo con cariño Man
the animation was nice
estuvo guapo la animación
sincere you have a point with with
sincero tienes un punto con con con
all the criticism of rewen but in that
todas las críticas del rewen pero en esa
part in particular for example they
parte en particular a mí por ejemplo me
piss me off I swear I can't stand
cagan no te juro que no soporto la
music made with Artificial Intelligence
música hecha con Inteligencia artificial
I see for example things that are taken from
yo veo por ejemplo cosas que sacan de de
the  I don't like the chat or me with
la tertulia o de mí con Inteligencia
Artificial Intelligence, but I still
artificial no me gustan pero igual
appreciate the detail. I still appreciate
agradezco el detalle Yo igual agradezco
the detail and I consider it a nice
el detalle y lo considero un bonito
post and I'm not going to dedicate an entire part
puesto y no voy a dedicar todo una parte
of a Stream or a video to say Ah well
de un Stream o un video a decir Ah pues
this is crap because
esto es [__] porque la Inteligencia
Artificial Intelligence no, it doesn't have a soul, the detail
artificial no no tiene alma el detalle
is what counts, friend, what I'm not
es lo que cuenta amigo qué no estoy
understanding, I think they don't realize that
entendiendo yo creo que no les cae que
the event is that the chat was born.
el suceso es que nació la tertulia
Man shrugging his
hombre encogido de
shoulders I don't know, but come on, I don't understand the
hombros no sé pero vamos no entiendo la
complaint. Hello old tasty kiss Dark, I don't
queja Hola viejo sabroso beso Dark no
understand the complaint. It seemed to me that
entiendo la queja A mí me pareció que
they were going to like it more, the truth is, it
les iba a gustar más la verdad a mí me
seemed very cool to me because it is a person
pareció muy Guay porque es una persona
close to them
cercana a ellos
and they didn't count on the fact that we would
e ellos no contaban con que les
put them there, they would have a, we were counting on
pondríamos no ahí tendrían un contábamos
putting a scene on it and also a
con ponerle una escena y aparte una
parody that is made with no. I mean, no, no, I don't
parodia que está hecha con no O sea no
understand the complaint. It seemed to me that it was
no no entiendo la queja me pareció que
going to be something that they were going to like
iba a ser una cosa que les iba a gustar
more, not a detail, not a detail, appearing
más no un detalle no un detalle aparecer
in an important video of the year, but oh
en un vídeo importante del año pero
well, anyway. By the way, what
bueno en fin Por cierto muy feo lo que
c did today is very ugly, eh, eh, about the wallpaper, eh, I do
ha hecho c hoy eh eh lo lo del fondo de
n't know.  if it was a joke or what
eh No sé si ha sido una calentada o qué
but I saw on Twitter the
pero he visto por ahí por Twitter el
wallpaper that m put not in
fondo de pantalla que ha puesto m no en
the
el
ugly ugly ugly ugly that eh I don't know at what
croma feo feo feucho eso eh No sé en qué
moment I didn't understand the joke I didn't
momento no he entendido la broma no he
understand making that
entendido hacer esa
joke what is he said understood what
broma qué está di entendió que quiso
tomy meant well because she's your friend also do
tomy bueno porque es tu amiga también
n't be an [ __ ] don't criticize
que no sea [__] que no critiques tanto
Tina's thing so much she's a [ __ ] friend
la esta de Tina que es colega cabrón
but it's that
pero es que
he but he's not criticizing Oh wait he
el pero no está criticando Ah espera me
's sending me
está mandando
places Javi Oliveira's Followers
lugares Los Seguidores de Javi oliveira
are like Pablo Franco and all that they are
Son son como los Pablo Franco y todo eso
very funny they are very
son son muy graciosos son gente muy
weird people very
rarita muy
special I don't know if this is a compliment or
especial no sé si esto es un halago o
because you realize that these
sea porque vos te das cuenta que estos
dolls are Javi's followers
muñecos Son son los seguidores de Javi
They are kind of down Yeah let's see I don't know if it
Son medios down Sí a ver no sé si ha
was a joke But that was ugly
sido una calentada Pero ha estado feucho
The truth is I mean I don't know if it was some
eso La verdad o sea no sé si ha sido un
kind of bet or whatever but
tipo de apuesta o lo que sea pero ya
putting a Dallas chroma doing yoga
ponerte un croma de Dallas haciendo yog
with your sister dude cha
con la hermana tío cha
[ __ ] with respect no
[__] con respeto no
because because they call me uncle gubel it
porque porque a mí me dicen tío gubel
's telling us that we have
nos está diciendo que nosotros tenemos
a community  a little weird is that you have to
una comunidad un poco rarita es que te
laugh eh Hey you're not too
tienes que reír eh Oye no estás muy
old to watch anime skinny fools
grande como para ver anime flaco bobes a
someone who has Disney tattooed on their
alguien que tiene tatuada a Disney en la
hand Disney is also for people in their
mano que Disney también es para gente de
40s no if we put it like that neither can
40 años no si nos ponemos así tampoco
a 40 year old person watch Disney I can't
una persona de 40 años Ver Disney yo no
watch anime But he can't
puedo ver anime Pero él tampoco se puede
watch Simba either Come on let's [ __ ] let's
ver a a Simba Dale quemos [__] dejemos
[ __ ] around they're kind of limited kind of quite
[__] son medio limitados medio bastante
limited
limitados
Not following that logic following that
No siguiendo esa lógica sigiendo es
logic Yes of course of course but what happened have you
lógica Sí claro claro pero qué pasó has
suffered a lot this week with when
sufrido mucho esta semana con cuando
you spoke badly of the
hablaste mal del
rewind no no no I have laughed my ass off
rewind no no no me he cagado de risa
because now I'm in the plan of who
porque ahora estoy en el plan de quién
told him that or rather someone criticized him for
le dijo eso o sea alguien criticó por
watching cartoons you know I don't know they make us they
ver dibujos animados sabes que no sé nos
make us responsible for what they
hacen nos hacen responsables de lo que
say any random person on the internet
le digan cualquier rando de internet
is there to talk about
está el para hablar de comunidades
weird communities No yeah yeah yeah let's see but well
raritas No ya ya ya a ver pero bueno
each one understands their own eh the se pray
cada uno entiende lo suyo eh los se oran
the cucas every time someone puts
los cucas cada vez que alguien me pone
something to me I put losan the cucas and and I laugh at
algo le pongo losan los cucas y y me río
the
del
ru what rating do you give it Ah for me it's
ru qué calificación le das Ah para mí es
a 10 just because I'm in it  Hey
un 10 solo porque yo estoy en él Hola
Tom Dale for you for M it's a one for
Tom Dale para ti para M es un uno para
me it's a
mí es un
one it's an 11 if Javi Oliveira did it it's
uno es un 11 si lo hizo Javi oliveira es
an 11 it's pes a one bro a one is a
un 11 es pés un uno bro un uno es un
video that you upload and it goes crazy and the
vídeo que lo subes y se crasa y está la
screen is black for 10 minutes dude already
pantalla negra 10 minutos cabrón ya
I guess
Supongo
doing some makeup I saw
que haciendo un maquillaje de pas vi
some people I don't know if it was
alguna gente no sé si fue
turboplane the Turbo plan video dude there
turboplane el vídeo de Turbo plan tío
were some things from the Turbo plan video
hubo algunas cosas del vídeo de Turbo
and lipe attacks me in the new rewind
e lipe me ataca en el nuevo rewind
okay there are a lot of people who took it
vale hay mucha gente que se dio por
personally because liy painted herself like a clown
aludido porque liy se pinte de payaso
saying that she was going to put on hater makeup I
diciendo que se va a maquillar de hater
mean let's
o sea vamos a
see they are messing with them that they
ver que se están metiendo con ellos que
were messing with the haters and let's
estaban metiose con los hater y que
see let's
vamos a ver vamos a
see all the communities on YouTube
ver todas las comunidades de de YouTube
we have haters we don't seem like clowns
tenemos haters noos parecen unos payasos
the haters
los haters
always clear it's that each one has taken it
siempre claro es que cada uno se ha dado
personally with what they were referring to
por aludido con que se referían a
it guys well and I already I mean let's see
ello chicos bien y yo ya o sea a ver
cool and Jaime Olivas who is very smart
molón y el Jaime Olivas que es muy
said Come on then I'll take advantage and
avispado ha dicho Venga pues aprovecho y
do this year's rewind it lasts 40
hago yo el rewind de este año dura 40
minutes  a little long maybe for my
minutos un poquito largo quizás para mi
taste even so I have seen it all I
gusto aú así sí lo he visto entero Yo
think we all agree on this Eh yes yes
creo que en esto coincidimos todos Eh sí
eh In order to comment on it and to see
que sí eh Para poder comentarlo y a ver
honestly if this was the rewind
sinceramente si este fuera el rewind
made by Alex molón well
hecho por Alex molón pues pues
obviously I would say that it is crap
evidentemente diría que es una [__]
a very very big crap but of course
una [__] muy muy gorda pero claro
taking into account that it is Jaime
teniendo en cuenta que es el Jaime
Olivares The one who has done the rewind that it
Olivares El que ha hecho el rewind que
is the first time that he has done it I have to
es la primera vez que lo hace yo tengo
say that it has surprised me or rather
que decir que me ha sorprendido o sea
for the better that it is not as much
para bien de que de que no es tanta
crap as I expected I
[__] como me esperaba O sea a ver me
mean let's see and you entertain yourself for a
refiero se puede ver y te entretienes un
while now well things is that gibel
rato ahora bien cosas que es que gibel
has become a very hater very
se ha puesto como muy hater muy
exaggerated I mean the video is cinema the
exagerado o sea el vídeo es cine el
video is cinema [ __ ] cinema that you don't
vídeo es cine [__] cine que tú no
know anyone [ __ ] I [ __ ] on D you
conoces a nadie [__] me cago en D
have [ __ ] Iker Jiménez in the video you have
tienes al [__] Iker Jiménez en el vídeo
the video closing Lauro in play you
tienes el vídeo cerrando Lauro en play
have Marta Díaz and Alfa doing
tienes a Marta Díaz y a Alfa haciendo
a scene that is really nice the
una escena que está s simpática la
scene of polyfacetic that he edited it he did
escena de polifacético que la editó
n't even send it edited to him is the
incluso no la mandó editada a él es la
host I mean the scene of  versatile
[__] O sea la escena de polifacético
I think
Me parece muy buena la actuación de
Nerea's performance with Aaron Mercury is very good, I think it's
nerea con Aaron Mercury me parece
great too, okay, it has mistakes, it has mistakes, it has mistakes
buenísima también vale tiene errores
in the order, it has
tiene errores tiene errores en el orden
mistakes in having summarized a
tiene errores en haber resumido unas
few things, it's worth making it
cuantas de cosas vale haberlo hecho más
shorter, eh And they should have paid more
corto eh Y que me Hubieran hecho más
attention to the instructions, honestly, but it
caso a las indicaciones la verdad pero
's cinema, I mean, it's very good,
es cine o sea está muy bien está
the animated scenes are nice too,
simpático las escenas animadas también
the Marta Riesco scene is s nice, she's
la escena Marta riesco está s simpática
also involved, I mean, what the [ __ ]? No, no, it
metida también o sea qué [__] No no no
's not that bad,
está tan mal
well, there are many, first of all, you can
pues Hay muchísimas lo primero de todo
see a little bit of the whitewashing
que se nota un poquito el blanqueamiento
that they're doing to Dallas, they're
que están haciendo a Dallas
really making fun of me, about the
burlándose de verdad yo lo del
whitewashing of Dallas, Dallas is
blanqueamiento a Dallas a Dallas se le
put in there like a normal person, we made fun of the Pambi thing,
mete ahí como una persona normal hemos
[ __ ],
hecho cachondeo con lo de pambi [__]
we made fun of the Pambi thing, he
hemos hecho cachondeo con lo de pambi él
participated in the scene without any
ha participado en la escena sin ningún
kind of problem with the Pambi thing, what
tipo de problema con lo de pambi qué
whitewashing, of course, maybe for
blanqueamiento claro a lo mejor para
you not that it wasn't whitewashing,
ustedes no que no fuera blanqueamiento
because seeing what we've seen it would be that heo had
pues visto lo visto sería que lo hubiera
said something about the insect or that or that he
dicho heo algo del insecto o que o que
had done a scene about something like a
le hubiera hecho una escena de algo de
pedophile abuser, no  I mean, clear, I
maltratador pedófilo no O sea claro o
mean, to Ricky I can't give Ricky a banana
sea a Ricky No le puedo poner un plátano
No no no Ricky The banana thing
a Ricky No no no Ricky Lo lo del plátano
in El Debate no click on the debate no I mean as far as I
en El Debate no click del debate no O
know I haven't put Ricky a
sea que yo sepa no he puesto a Ricky un
lot of things that would have been
montón de cosas que sí hubieran sido
throwing at him okay In fact here the editor
tirarle vale De hecho aquí el editor
took and planted the photo of Ricky
cogió y le plantó la foto de Ricky
eating Win michu's plate and I
comiéndole El plato a Win michu y le
told him to
dije que la
remove it okay I mean, Dallas should have had
quitara vale O sea a Dallas le tenía que
a whitewashing because I
haber es un blanqueamiento porque lo
treat him like a normal person in the
trato como una persona normal en el
video but I attacked Ricky because
vídeo pero a Ricky lo he atacado porque
I put scenes from the
he puesto escenas del
debate of Ricky edited making fun of Delo
debate de Ricky edit burlándose de delo
making fun of Delos no, Delos is making fun of
burlándose de delos no delos se burla de
himself This is Delos' role be
él mismo Este es el papel de delos sea
out of the scene of wanting to agree with
fuera de la escena de querer darle la
everyone who is against
razón a todo el que se pone en contra de
Dallas, ao has been seen like this people with
Dallas ao se le ha visto así gente con
two fingers in front delox has been
dos dedos de frente a delox se le ha
seen like this raed
visto Así a raed le
gave it to him first he was called a scammer
diola primero se le llamó estafador
when he was with Dallas then he was given the
cuando estaba con Dallas luego se le dio
ball eh gibel was interviewing her on
bola eh gibel estuvo entrevistándola a
her channel what happened Well now we
su canal qué ha pasado Pues que ahora se
see how crazy he is  raet and the person who
ve el loco que es raet y la persona que
is
es
raet has basically said that your rewind
raet básicamente ha dicho que tu rewind
is not [ __ ] but that it is [ __ ]
no es una [__] sino que es una [__]
with a bow Haha a kiss a kiss No man
con lazo Jaja un beso un beso No hombre
that has surprised her because it is well
que la ha sorprendido porque está bien
done but that
hecho pero que
delox gibel and all these people
delox gibel y toda esta gente
delox you will realize that he is a trickster
delox os daréis cuenta que es un trilero
that is bad he is bad he is a
que es malo es malo es una persona
filthy person he is a bad person that
[__] es una persona mala que te la que
puts it in you in case he does not put it in
te la mete por si no te la mete por
front He puts it in you from behind the stick do you
delante Te la mete por detrás el palo me
understand a trickster is a
entiendes una persona liante es un
trickster he is a charlatan But if here I
liante es un charlatán Pero si aquí
am completely exposed here
quedo completamente expuesto aquí me
I got on the talk show to debate with him
subí yo en la tertulia a debatir con él
and he was completely exposed these
y quedó completamente expuesto estos
clips of delos is what there is, it happens that
clips de delos es lo que hay pasa que
you guys are like very denied Ah
ustedes pues estáis como muy negados Ah
Hey, just like I am very in favor
Oye pues igual que yo estoy muy a favor
of Dallas No because I get along with him Well maybe
de Dallas No porque me llevo con él Pues
you are denied to put yourselves
a lo mejor estáis negados a poneros en
against anyone who appears
contra de cualquiera que aparece en
against Dallas and this guy this guy He is
contra de Dallas y este tío este tío Es
bad Ricky He is bad Ricky He is bad Ricky He is bad he
malo Ricky Es malo Ricky Es malo Ricky
is a bad person alianta
Es malo es una persona mala alianta
filthy too He says it to be dirty you
[__] también Él lo dice para guarro tú
filthy I'm bad is bad
guarro yo es malo es malo
also comes out liy And he says Well,
también sale liy Y dice Pues que los
haters are clowns Hello everyone
haters son unos payasos Hola a todos
welcome one more day today I'm going to
bienvenidos un día más hoy os voy a
show you How to do makeup like a hater it's
enseñar Cómo maquillar como un hater es
[Music]
[Música]
super easy there you go have you seen how
superfácil ya está habéis visto que
easy even a fool can do it Oops
fácil hasta un tonto puede hacerlo Ups
even at the beginning of the video it starts It's
incluso al principio del vídeo inicia Es
a joke a superl a super
un chiste una superl un chiste super
white joke the delicious thing is that I don't even
blanco lo delicio sea es que ni siquiera
understand the hype that has been given to the
entiendo el bombo que se le ha dado al
joke
chiste
what do you want me to tell you that haters
qué queréis que os diga que los haters
are good I don't
son buenos no
know with the joke that of course to
sé con la broma de que claro que para
finance the ring what
financiar el rine pues lo que ha hecho
Javi Oliveira has done is steal money from
Javi oliveira es pues robar el dinero a
the Dallas fans with Pambi that was
los fans de Dallas con pambi que fue
literally what happened anyway It's that this
literalmente lo que pasó sea Es que esto
is
es
real if you think that r it cost me
real si tú te crees que r me ha costado
bucks that is literally what happened
pavos que es literalmente lo que pasó
says the
dice la
little creature we financed with Pambi
criaturita hemos financiado con pambi
damn we'll have to do something
[__] habrá que hacer algo
no If I had money If I had
no Si tuviera dinero Si tuviera
money to me it looks it's very
dinero a m está se ve está muy
[Music]
[Música]
cool Let's go
chula Vámonos
Javi What is this about selling Here comes
Javi Qué es eso de vender Aquí se viene
crying  dito de casa here you hold with
llorad dito de casa aquí se holdea con
balls here you don't sell anything until you
[__] aquí no se vende nada hasta que
have millions in your wallet you idiot
no tengas millones en la cartera imbécil
to fold vorde to your cousin from
a foldear vorde a tu prima la de
Mursia I'm Javi Oliveira Look how
mursia soy el Javi oliveira Mira qué
handsome I am Look look look Javi Oliveira
guapo soy Mira mira mira Javi oliveira
was one of the first first of all to
fue de los primeros primeros de todos en
invest in Pambi this you already know what that
invertir en pambi esto ya sabéis lo que
means he was not one of those
significa no era una de esas personas
privileged people who then in the end he
privilegiadas que luego pues al final
ended up selling in the face of the
les terminó vendiendo en la cara a los
fools who came after and who
tontos que vinieron después y que
ended up Oh you plan it really how
acabaron Ay tú lo plan de verdad que
lazy it is that already Look we are going to
pereza es que ya Mira nos vamos a tomar
laugh but come on I was not even one of the first
risa pero vamos ni fui de los primeros
first first privileged because I
primeros primeros privilegiado porque yo
'm not even in the discord group okay
no estoy ni en el grupo de discord vale
I found out through Twitter I didn't even
Yo me enteré por Twitter ni siquiera me
find out through Dallas what's going on with the
enteré por Dallas qu pasa con la
cryptocurrency he had been uploading
criptomoneda él Ya llevaba días subiendo
videos on his channel for days and I didn't
vídeos en su canal de Cristo y yo no ech
notice those things You know
cuenta esas cosas Sabes
and I found out through Twitter because I started to
e me me enteré por Twitter porque empecé
see tweets that Pambi Pam and this and this I
a ver twit que pambi Pam y esto lo otro
asked the editor and he told me I already
le pregunté al editor y me dijo yo ya he
bought a while ago you know and I was not one of the
comprado hace un rato sabes e ni fui de
first nor did I sell to them  in the face it's
los primeros ni les vendí en la cara a
worthless Ah people started
nadie vale Ah la gente se puso a
investigating to see my equal is if how much I had
investigar a ver mi igual es si cuánto
bought And how much I had sold
había comprado Y cuánto había vendido yo
eh If I had wanted to sell suddenly
eh Si hubiera querido vender de repente
and have taken out all my profit my
y haber sacado todo mi beneficio mi
portfolio wasn't worth 10,000 I took out 10,000
cartera no valía 10.000 yo saqué 10,000
little by little because I was selling I was
poco a poco porque iba vendiendo iba
taking out as I saw that there was
sacando conforme iba viendo que había
profit I was collecting profit but
beneficio iba recogiendo beneficio pero
my portfolio ended up being worth almost 30,000 man I
mi cartera llegó a valer casi 30.000 tío
mean if I had known that it was going to
O sea si yo hubiera sabido que se iba a
[ __ ] or that I had
la [__] o que tenía información
privileged information or or or or I would have taken it all out in
privilegiada o o o o lo saco todo en la
people's faces I took out when it was worth
cara de la gente yo saco cuando valía
30,000 whole no that I took out 3000 2000 I went to
30.000 entero no que saqué 3000 2000 fui
take out your mistake was being lukewarm no no no it's
sacar tu error fue ser tibio no no no es
lukewarm it's that no that's like playing the
tibio es que no eso es como jugar un
lottery a little I mean that's a
poco a la a la lotería o sea eso es un
little you know you don't know what can happen
poco sabes no sabes lo que puede pasar
because suddenly if everyone starts
porque de repente si todo el mundo se
selling it falls if a lot of people buy it goes
pone a vender cae si mucha gente compra
up I mean you can't guess the
sube O sea tú no puedes adivinar el
future price if someone knew how to
futuro del precio si alguien supiera
do that a lot of people would be millionaires
hacer eso serían mucha gente millonaria
I was collecting  benefits as
yo fui recogiendo beneficios como me
my editor told me okay let's get a
decía mi editor vale vamos a sacar un
little come on let's get it we don't get it we're going to
poco venga sacamos no sacamos vamos a
get it all No well no well let's
sacarlo todo No pues no pues vamos a
get half and and and out more you know
sacar la mitad y y y fuera más sabes
but I kept half or more of
pero yo me quedé con la mitad o más de
my token when everything fell that fall on the
mi token cuando todo cayó la caída esa
day of the announcement okay Why well I
del día del anuncio vale Por qué pues me
kept it because I would say Well
lo quedé porque yo diría Bueno pues
now it's going to go up again I don't know what the [ __ ] I know I
ahora subirá otra vez yo que sé qué [__]
know losing money like Javier
sabes perdiendo el dinero como Javier
Oliveira that close friend of Dallas
oliveira ese amigo cercano de Dallas
Well of course evidently he was one of the
Pues claro evidentemente eraa uno de los
first to invest in Pambi he
primeros que invirtió en pambi se lo
kept it quiet simo no then he got caught with
tenía callad simo no luego se le pilló
a portfolio that he himself leaked Well that he had
una cartera que él mismo filtró Pues que
taken
se había sacado
00 if I'm not mistaken no then Well
00 si no me equivoco no entonces Bueno
at least he recognizes it no well let you know
al menos lo reconoce no bueno que sepáis
that this rwi is financed I'm
que este rwi está financiado me estoy
laughing turboplane people like you with the
riendo turboplane gente como tú con el
money that the pambiitos lost or
dinero que perdieron los pambisitos o
rather he's literally telling you and he doesn't give a damn
sea literalmente os lo está diciendo y
then the
se la pela completamente luego la
game part did Willy Rex no this
parte de juego hizo Willy Rex no esto
would have to have been lacquer the
tendría que ha sido laca la escena
primordial scene of the R I would have even
primordial del R yo hubiera incluso
being Javi Oliveira I would have called
siendo el Javi oliveira habría llamado a
Dallas to record a  scene from what
Dallas para grabar una escena de qué
game did Willy Rex make in
juego hizo Willy Rex en
conditions, I mean, I mean, the protagonist
condiciones o sea o sea el protagonista
of R had to be
del R tenía que ser
Dallas the protagonist of the rewi had to
Dallas el protagonista del rewi tenía
be d it's not worth it that the
que ser d no vale con que la escena
main scene is that there is no rewine but
principal sea que no hay rewine pero yo
suddenly I earn money in pambi then I
de repente gano dinero en pambi entonces
become a millionaire with the 10000 I have
me hago millonario con los 10000 tengo
a Ferrari so I do a non-
un Ferrari entonces hago un rewind no
main rewind Dallas I have to call him
principal Dallas yo lo tengo que llamar
so he yells at me what game did Wily
para que me grite qué juego hizo wily
Turlan make it was here it was here on my channel the
turlan fue aquí fue aquí en mi canal lo
Willy game was here on the
del juego de Willy fue aquí en el
main gossip channel there is
principal canal de salseo que hay sin
however in the part of the R where
embargo en la parte del R en la que
they honor the Meme of what game did
hacen honor el Meme de qué juego hizo
Willy Rex make Well they do this [ __ ] [ __ ]
Willy Rex Pues hacen esta [__] [__]
What did Willy Rex do what game
Qué hizo Willy Rex qué juego
did you authorize
hizo autorizas
and the game as such is the one you are
y el juego como tal es el que estáis
seeing here the game is totally free
viendo aquí juego es totalmente gratuito
so that everyone can play you do not
para poder jugar todo el mundo no hace
need to have any type of wallet Today I
falta tener ningún tipo de wallet Hoy
come from saying I have smoked three joints it is
vengo de decir me he fumado tres porros
not there
no está
Oh okay [ __ ] I had to see it like
Ah vale [__] lo he tenido que ver como
six times to get it Of course Will
seis veces para pillarlo Claro está Will
Rex reacting to a game but the
Rex reaccionando un juego pero está el
background is black because Willy Rex did not do
fondo en negro porque Willy Rex no hizo
no game clear what game did Dallas make
ningún juego claro qué juego hizo Dallas
good question he said he was going to release 17
buena pregunta dijo que iba a sacar 17
games but they don't talk about those
juegos pero de esos de eso no se hablan
[Music]
[Música]
was going to release 17 games When did he say
iba a sacar 17 juevos Cuándo ha dicho
that I don't know eh I don't know I ask eh that maybe he
eso no lo sé eh No lo sé pregunto eh que
said I have no [ __ ]
a lo mejor ha dicho no tengo ni [__]
idea I know he said he was going to release a
idea Yo sé que dijo que iba a sacar un
game not about I don't know what
juego no de de no sé qué así
like H no yeah no yeah that they also
como H no s no s que también lo
criticized it no no it wasn't a game also about a
criticaron no no era un juego también de
token also they also saw
un token también lo también le veían
some
algún
problem with it curiously yes It should be
problema curiosamente eso sí Hay que
emphasized that Willy Rex no he didn't make any
recalcar que Willy Rex no no hizo ningún
game I don't know the truth is that I would have taken
juego no sé yo la verdad es que a este
out of this meme But what but
meme le hubiera sacado Pero qué pero
joking but let's see or so he's telling me he's
broma pero a ver o sea me está diciendo
telling me that as the main scene he
me está diciendo que de escena principal
had to bring Dallas to shout
tenía que traer a Dallas a que gritara
where is the Willy re game and He
dónde está el juego de Willy re y Se
's complaining that the Willy
está quejando de que el juego de Willy
re game is a black screen no but but
re sea una pantalla negra no pero pero
then what did you want me to mess with
entonces qué querías que me metiera con
Dallas is what you would have liked say
Dallas es lo que te hubiera gustado a ti
it I would have liked him to have
dilo me hubiera gustado que hubiera
put Dallas with his sister doing
puesto a Dallas con la hermana haciendo
yoga and with the other one and  and and and stealing there
yoga y con el otro y y y y robando ahí
as if he were a thief and in jail
como si fuera un ladrón y en la cárcel
say it that's what you would have liked
dilo eso es lo que te hubiera gustado
so that the rigu would have been the [ __ ] damn say it like that
para que el rigu hubiera sido la [__]
much more juice and it is clear it is
así mucho más jugo y se nota claro se
clear that it is done a little because of
nota que está hecho un poco pues por el
Javi Oliveira that well we already know what
Javi oliveira que pues ya sabemos lo que
happens no we already know then also the
pasa no ya se sabe luego también la
joke of Serene no that she is a girl
broma de serene no que sea una chica a
that Dallas threatened to send her
la que Dallas la amenazó con enviarla
hitmen this is true Serene well she is
sicarios esto es verdad serene pues es
a girl who had a
una chica que tenía una cuenta de
Twitter account that talked about gossip and she was
Twitter que hablaba de salseo y se
dedicated to criticizing Dallas a lot the
dedicaba a criticar a Dallas mucho la
truth is that must be said and Dallas well he must have
verdad eso hay que decirlo y Dallas pues
sent her an email threatening her that
la debió enviar un correo amenazándola
some friends were going to see her at her
con que iban a verla unos amigos a su
house or it is [ __ ] crazy no And of
casa o sea una putísima locura no Y
course making this joke that Serene
claro esto hacer un chiste de que serene
died when the girl disappeared from the
ha muerto cuando la chica desapareció de
networks because she was she was scared she
redes porque estaba estaba [__] tenía
was this is a lie but if the
miedo es esto es mentira pero si la
girl said that she had left For
chica dijo que había se había ido Por
another
otro
reason [ __ ] but he is offended by this
tema [__] pero está ofendido con esto
dude I can't with this died when
tío yo con esto no puedo muerto cuando
the girl disappeared from the networks because she was she was
la chica desapareció de redes porque
scared she was
estaba estaba [__] tenía miedo
Spanish she
españoles
died eh what the [ __ ] happened with
ha muerto eh qué [__] ha pasado con
serene where the hell is serene and I've
serene dónde [__] está serene y esto lo
seen this from the comments serene has been
he visto por los comentarios serene
practically two weeks without giving any
lleva dos semanas prácticamente Sin dar
signs of life I feel like this is
señales de vida siento que esto es
too serious to make this
demasiado serio como para hacer esta
joke and act like this is a meme
broma y hacer como si esto fuera un meme
a joke No the truth is that this about
un chiste No la verdad es que esto lo de
serene is a little bit wrong the truth is
serene un poquito mal traído la verdad
I really would have thought of
yo esto la verdad me lo hubiera las
this year's r collaborations Oh I've been
colaboraciones del r de este año Ay que
offended
se me ha ofendido Dios
my God chav s auron Play there's one by des you
mío chav s auron Play hay una de nis vos
saw the
viste la
performance please tell me a little about how you
actuación por favor un poquito de cómo
took the serene joke
os habéis tomado broma lo del serene
guys How you took the serene joke you
chavales Cómo os habéis tomado broma los
have no heart
de serene no tenéis corazón
eh How can you take the
eh Cómo os podéis tomar a broma lo de
serene thing as a joke Maybe you don't have a heart or what's wrong with you
serene Acaso no tenéis corazón o qué os
well it's not a joke eh the
pasa pues no es ninguna broma eh la
girl had a really
chavala lo pasó muy
bad time I should have put like I would have
mal tenía que haber puesto como le
put like the game
hubiera hubiera puesto como el juego
Where is serene Elo saying where
Dónde está serene Elo diciendo dónde
is serene and the black screen
está serene y la pantalla
great
buenísima
shock absorber situation also
amortiguador situción también
no I liked our participation I
no a m me gustó nuestra participación
must say our participation is
debo decirlo nuestra participación está
lively and they didn't put a scene from the
animada y no pusieron una escena de la
discussion  funny with all the ones there are
tertulia graciosa con todas las que
ies
hay ies
t that are taken from video about me at the end
t que de vídeo se sacan sobre mí al cabo
of the day with nonsense
del día con tontería
eh it was it was the the creature that makes me look
eh era era la la la criatura que me pone
like a puppy in the
como un perrito en la
thumbnail live and direct look look at
miniatura en vivo y en directo mira mira
the
la
creature you find it you
criatura te lo encuentras te lo
find it on the street it says come come you who
encuentras en la calle dice ven ven tú
put the thumbnail come I'll
qu me has puesto la miniatura ven te lo
paint it for you with a label I'll
te lo pinto con un rotulado a ti te
paint your nose like this bold and I'll
pinto a ti la naricita así negrita y te
give you a mustache as if you were a
pongo bigotito como si fueras una
little mouse It's that then they are to see it
ratita Es que luego son para verlo
man there are no more opinions of the rig here is
tío no hay más opiniones del rig está
Tina's Ay
Tina Ay de
really from when it was from there on out I mean
verdad del cuando era de ahí en fuera o
let's read miet not
sea vamos a leer miet no
this and if I say that I liked the rewind Ah
esto y si digo que me gustó el rewine Ah
Well look G and if I say that I liked the
Bueno mira G y si digo que me gustó el
rewind 2024 by Javi Olivas how you
rewind 2024 de Javi Olivas cómo te
stay wow wow wow wow wow it didn't have a
quedas wow wow wow wow wow no tuvo un
mistake in the couple breakups it was missing the one with
error en las rupturas de pareja le faltó
Alana and Barca from there on out
la de alana y barca de ahí en fuera
scrin and guarro but it ends up being good
scrin y guarro pero termina siendo bueno
I thought I would have a bad time watching it but it
creí que lo pasaría mal viéndolo pero me
ended up  liking as Martian would say
terminó gustando como diría marcianita
Sorry chat at least he didn't spend as much
Perdón chat al menos no se gastó tanto
money as the cool one and tried to imitate
dinero como al molón y pretendió imitar
the Marvel movies that the old r
las pelis de Marvel que los r antiguos
seemed made for 3 year olds
parecían hechos para peques de 3 años
nor did he want to grab as much attention
tampoco quiso agarrar tanto protagonismo
as Alex cool who
como Alex molón que cada segundo
appeared on screen every second who had to be Yuki
aparecía en pantalla que tuvo estar yuki
a girl who had a rise too
una chica que tuvo un ascenso demasiado
quickly on multiple platforms and when
rápido en múltiples plataformas y cuando
this is what we are dealing with it is YouTube or TikTok
esto tratamos es de YouTube o tiktok
specifically because of the great beauty that she
específicamente por la gran belleza que
has come to handle and has gained her
ha llegado a manejar y le ha conseguido
many followers specifically if
muchísimos seguidores específicamente si
you notice her physical appearance is
te das cuenta su aspecto físico es
too graceful and by that we
demasiado agraciado y con eso nos
mean fair skin and pink
referimos a una piel Clara y rosacia
blue eyes and unparalleled beauty or
ojos azules y una belleza sin igual o
at least that is what her
por lo menos es lo que dicen sus
followers say as such talking about her origin
seguidores como tal hablar de su origen
is completely simple although it is also
es completamente simple aunque también
necessary to clarify her great fall that Hey
hay que aclarar su gran caída que Oye
but I had put this video here
pero yo tenía puesto aquí Este vídeo
to see it very good my beloved audience
para verlo muy buenas mi amado público
today we have nuclear garbage most of it
hoy tenemos basura nuclear la mayoría
monopolized by Juan and wescol as a person
acaparada por Juan y wescol como persona
because if we don't learn anything [ __ ] I have not
pues si no aprendemos nada [__] No he
seen heo in the end dude I have to
visto heo al final tío me tengo que
catch up on the gossip people
poner al día del salseo las personas
But it does not make us bad I say that if  you
Pero no hace que seamos malos yo digo
were a bad person bro I don't
que si eras mala persona bro yo no lo
believe it yes you were and you didn't know you were and you didn't
creo s lo eras y no sabías lo eras y no
know [ __ ] yeah he doesn't hold back eh
sabías [__] se no se corta un pelo eh
hesc eh he tells it to his face
el hesc eh se lo dice la cara
eh it's that Juan always shields himself or he
eh es que Juan siempre se escuda o él
wants to make it seem like no that and many
quiere como que parezca no que y mucha
people say it and repeat it no that it's
gente lo dice y lo repite no que es una
something that I don't understand why they repeat
cosa que yo no entiendo por qué repiten
that nonsense that he criticized him for
esa tontería que a él lo criticaba por
Ari that the hate that he had was because
Ari que el hate que él tenía era por
of Ari it's like no no no Ari had
culpa de Ari es como no no no Ari tenía
his hate obviously because of the
su hate evidentemente por las cosas
bad things he does or did or whatever you
malas que hace o que hacía o lo que
want to say but Juan Juan
queráis decir pero Juan es que Juan se
brings it Juan brings it and brought it
las trae Juan se las trae y se las traía
and the
y se las trajo el
dude brought it You don't know the damage you caused
colega Usted no sabe el daño que causó
pa You don't have the slightest idea of ​​the
pa Usted no tiene ni la menor idea del
damage you cause Juan was was bad he
daño que usted causa Juan era era malo
has a bad
tiene un mal
heart and neither do you But you know what the
fondo y tú tampoco Pero sabes cuál es el
issue is that I don't know what you did outside of
tema que yo no sé qué hacías fuera de
that what I did outside of what I did
eso yo que hacía fuera de lo que hací
that but one is a bad person without knowing it
eso pero uno es mala persona sin saberlo
the mere fact that when you
el mero hecho de que cuando usted me
threw me at me He had that amount of people
tiró a mí Tenía esa cantidad de gente
bro when you threw me at  You
bro cuando usted me tiró a mí Usted
had like 30,000 people and I had
tenía como 30,000 personas y yo tenía
like 200 but well, they were, but I'll tell you again,
como 200 pero pues ellos ero te repito
not everything has to be one or
algo que no todo tiene que ser o uno o
two, I mean, just because I acted badly, it doesn't
dos o sea no porque yo haya actuado mal
mean that I was a bad
actuado mal significa que yo era mala
person and that you were a bad person,
persona y que tú er as mala persona por
at least in my perception, I didn't like you, I didn't like you, I hated you, I
lo menos a mi percepción me caías mal me
was angry at you, I
caías mal te tenía rabia te tenía rabia
felt that you were a bad person and I
yo siento que si eras mala persona y yo
also feel that I was a bad person,
también siento que yo era mala persona
I see it differently. I thought that this
yo lo veo diferente Yo pensaba que esta
is an expression, not everything has to be one or
es expresión no todo tiene que ser o uno
two, it was that not everything has to be
o dos era que no todo tiene por qué ser
black or white, by the way, a Juan who
blanco o negro por cierto un Juan que se
has won the little heart of Dech Juan
ha ganado el corazoncito de dech Juan
Guarnizo, no no, but if 2024 brought us anything, it
guarnizo no no pero si algo nos trajo
was a different Juan Guarnizo. Look, I do
2024 fue un Juan guarnizo distinto Mire
n't like getting into controversies, there
no me gusta meterme en controversias ya
's too much gossip, but if we
es demasiado chisme pero si en algo
can agree on one thing, it's that Juan
podemos estar de acuerdo es que Juan
Guizo is another person. The last time I saw him, he
guizo es otro yo la última vez que lo vi
was choosing between one, it's that wcol
andaba escogiendo entre una es que wcol
has hate speech, I mean, I don't
tiene discursos que son de odio o sea no
know if he
sé si lo
does it. Look, I see something positive in wcon too.  it's
hace Mira a wcon le veo algo también
that deep down it's not a let's
positivo y es que en el fondo no es una
see how clear em I do
a ver como claro em
n't know if I'm going to be able to explain it well
no sé si voy a saber explicarlo bien
but I think that wcol has things that
pero yo creo que wescol tiene cosas que
are hate speech and
son discursos de odio y comportamientos
hateful behavior okay regarding women
de odio vale respecto a las mujeres
Regarding homosexuals, trans people
Respecto a los homosexuales a las trans
okay but I think he has a good background
vale pero creo que tiene como buen fondo
in which he doesn't want to be bad but rather he
en el que él no quiere ser malo sino que
has normalized certain things based
tiene normalizadas ciertas cosas en base
on his environment in the environment that he was
a su ambiente en el ambiente que se haya
raised or whatever that is what I think
criado o lo que sea eso es lo que pienso
is wcol However, I see Juan
que es de wcol Sin embargo a Juan le veo
as a certain malice in some of
como cierta malicia inquina en alguna de
his attitudes on many
sus actitudes en muchas
occasions a girl and grabbed the Nerf we
ocasiones una morra y agarró la Nerf no
cannot deny that wcol has
podemos negar que wcol tiene discursos
hate speech, I mean it is hate speech that
de odio o sea son discursos de odio que
you say that if you have a gay son you
tú digas que si te sale un hijo gay le
shoot him right in the roof of his
pegas balazos hasta en el cielo de la
mouth you understand me, I mean he does and I have
boca me entiendes o sea lo hace y tengo
a video with a lot of things that
un vídeo con un montón de de cosas que
people applaud that about wcol that I
la gente aplaude que sobre wcol que yo
don't understand how it is applauded I don't know
no entiendo cómo se aplaude Yo no sé
but Juan guarnizo 2024 I
pero el Juan guarnizo 2024 a mí me me
like him very much I like him very much I know
cae muy bien a mí me cae muy bien Yo sé
that I  He doesn't like me I don't give a
que yo a él no le caigo bien Me vale un
damn but I really like seeing
poco [__] pero a mí me cae muy bien ver
Juan Guarnizo's transformation then
la transformación de Juan guarnizo luego
schizophrenia set in and we
ya se sumergió el esquizofrenia y lo
lost him without a chance Why did you forgive
perdimos sin podido Por qué perdonaste
an infidelity what do you know pinch
una infidelidad tú qué vas a saber pinch
Tech if you've never been with a
Tech si tú nunca has estado con una
beautiful woman like me with a woman who
mujer bella como yo con una mujer que
charges for her photos because only a
cobra por sus fotos porque solo una
beautiful woman could charge for her photos
mujer bella podría cobrar por sus fotos
anyway Juanito seems condemned
de todas formas Juanito parece condenado
Eternally
Eternamente todavía se continúan
clips like
haciendo virales clips como
[Music]
[Música]
this I am that these things are things that I do
este yo es que estas cosas son cosas que
n't
no las
understand I these are things that I don't but not
entiendo yo esto son cosas que no pero
this anymore eh Because you can make them
ya no esto eh Porque tú puedes hacer las
with a person or talk about it or who
pase con una persona o hablarlo o vete
knows what they have talked about between them
tú a saber qu habrán hablado entre ellos
eh It's already that your wife being your wife
eh Ya es que tu mujer siendo tu mujer
during the time that she was your wife
durante el tiempo que era tu mujer se
goes to work with Gref to present the
vaya a trabajar con gref a presentar los
eslan and that kind of thing seems to me that
eslan y ese tipo de cosas me parecen que
there you have you the humiliating thing, the
ahí tienes tú la lo humillante lo
criticizable thing to Juan not to Juan and to her
criticable a Juan no a Juan y a ella
evidently to see me and then you
evidentemente a ver a mí ya luego que tú
fix it with him or talk
te arregles con él o que hables las
things over or whatever you want that  whatever they've done you
cosas o lo que quiera que sea que hayan
know bro he's literally talking
hecho sabes bro literal está hablando
to the guy who detonated his wife and
con el tipo que detonó a su esposa y
Juan with a lamb face Oh just as
Juan con cara de corderito Ay igual de
humiliating as using bro in your
humillante que utilizar bro en tu
vocabulary I also tell you on the
vocabulario también te digo en el bando
opposite side we have wescol who of the
opuesto tenemos a wescol que de los
creators
creadores
left Juan's penalty guarn to me to
dejal penalti de Juan guarn a me di
remove that disease it smells like it
quitar esa enfermed huele como si hua
happened chim that those Koreans have the
pasado chim que esos coreanos tengan la
same
misma
face the truth
cara la verdad
truth there is a nationality that escapes
verad hay nacionalidad que se escape
today I'm going to be very positive with wc but it
hoy voy a ser muy positivo con wc pero
's that I also prefer a thousand times the
es que también prefiero mil veces a las
people who are worth it you can be
personas que vale la puedes estar
[ __ ] yourself But he's doing it to your face you can already
[__] Pero te lo está haciendo de cara
see it no no you think the
ya lo estás viendo no no pensáis lo
same no no no you think the fake ones worse
mismo no no no os parece peor los falsos
the civilino the ratillas that you don't
los civilino los ratillas que no te los
see them coming that go from Well I think this I
ve venir que van de Bueno yo pienso esto
have these morals I have this you know
yo tengo esta moral yo tengo esta sabes
what I'm telling you and it's a
lo que te digo y es
lie incorporated I don't understand
mentira incorporado yo no entiendo por
why the woman out of nowhere wants to be better
qué la mujer de la nada quiere ser mejor
than the man brother like of them
que el hombre brother como de elos
exactly Princess Sofia If that
exactamente princesa Sofía Si eso nunca
will never happen Total these two have
va a pasar Total que estos dos han
been talking and they have made It is clear that
estado hablando y han dejado Claro que
they are incompatible Let's see let's be
son incompatibles A ver vamos a ser
honest that I believe  which is something that you
honestos que yo creo que es algo que tú
also think and that I also think
también piensas y que yo también pienso
a friendship between the two of us is something very
una amistad entre los dos es algo muy
complicated difficult but not because of the past
complicado difícil pero no por el pasado
not because of the differences we are
no por las diferencias somos personas
absolutely different people yes yes yes No I have
absolutamente distintas sí s s No yo lo
noticed you have your good things your
notado tú tienes tus cosas buenas tus
bad things I have my good things and
cosas malas yo tengo mis cosas buenas y
my bad things you are a
mis cosas malas usted es un hombre
calm man Well I see you calm calm yes you
tranquilo Pues yo lo veo tranquilo
understand I am more
calmado s me entiende Yo soy más
extroverted and it does not mean that one is
extrovertido y no significa que uno sea
good and the other is bad they
El bueno y el otro el malo simplemente
are simply personalities exactly and I believe
son personalidades exactamente y yo creo
that keeping the party in peace makes me
que llevar la fiesta en paz hace que yo
I believe Gen an m in friendships or not
yo creo Gen un m en las amistades o no
friendships in
las amistades en las relaciones
cordial relationships well Anyway for a
cordiales bien De todas formas para un
boxing match it doesn't matter to me Juan
combate de boxeo igual le da yo le Juan
that when he feels the need to
que cuando él sienta la necesidad de
fight against me I am with me I think that
pelear contra mí yo soy con yo creo que
the best of the people who sign up for
lo mejor de la gente que se inscribe a
those evening fights Stream Fighters It is
esas veladas peleas Stream Fighters Es
the physical change that they do cool I mean
el cambio físico que hacen chimba o sea
but that requires a lot of
pero eso requiere mucho tiempo de
preparation time and a lot of turning around when he
preparación y mucha vuelta cuando él
wants but it's that it gives me a lot of
quiera pero es que a mí me da mucha
cloer when you feel daddy the
cloer cuando usted sienta papi la
need to get your face kicked in let's see
necesidad de que le partan la cara a ver
I am l do you think you have the time
yo esty es l tú crees tener el tiempo
currently like  to dedicate months
actualmente como para dedicar se meses
of your life to preparing for a fight
de tu vida a prepararte para una pelea
I think we could make a p paicos
yo creo que podríamos hacer un p paicos
3 hard months each
3 meses cada
TR hard months that I
uno duros TR meses duros que yo me
imagine TR months of my life dedicated
imagino TR meses de mi vida dedicado
completely to that and no I don't feel that it
completamente eso y no yo no siento que
's completely two hours in the
sea completamente dos horitas en la
morning two hours in the afternoon I'm
mañana dos horitas en la tarde te lo
telling you that I have literally had the moment when
digo yo que he tenido literal el momento
April fights I was married to
en el que pelea abril yo estaba casado
her I knew how much people
con ella yo sabía que tanto la gente le
invest in that I wanted to win totally Well the thing is that
invierte a eso quería ganar totalmente
if you sign up for that it's to
Pues es que si te inscribes a eso es
win yes otherwise I feel like I wouldn't have to
para ganar sí sino que yo siento que no
train much the truth
tendría que entrenar mucho la verdad
who knows eh I could be a surprise
quién sabe eh Yo puedo ser sorpresa
imagine if I get into a waterfall
imagina con que me meta una cascada
daddy [ __ ] everyone seen that
papi una [__] todo el mundo visto que
my physical activity I describe myself like
mi actividad física yo me describo como
Pinocchio I move badly I mean I run and it
Pinocho Yo me muevo feo o sea Yo corro y
seems like I fall apart But why
parece que me desbarato Pero por qué
Natalia I say that that could be it could
Natalia yo digo que que eso puede ser
be a fight for
puede ser una pelea para el año que
next year it depends on how we finish the year
entra depende de como terminemos el año
well find out that Juan doesn't want
puesc entérate que Juan no quiere
friendship with you or to hit you what he does
contigo ni amistad ni dse de [__] lo
want is to make one more strong
que sí que quiere es poner fuerte uno má
Welcome to the club I think  let's see, for
Bienvenido al club creo que a ver yo por
example, one of my goals for this year
ejemplo un propósito que tengo este año
is to get strong, just fine, both
es ponerme fuerte sillo bien ambos
had time to talk, get
tuvieron tiempo para hablar un Ponerme
strong, a little bit about everything, who
fuertecito un poco de todo quién
ever showed up, better said, savagely,
apareció nunca Mejor dicho salvajemente
fagor, fagor, a while ago, in a
fagor fagor hace un tiempo en un partido
soccer game, he destroyed Westcol, they were
de fútbol destrozó a westcol se
claiming by hand. Now I'm on the ground with Fagor,
reclamaba a mano W ahora suelo con fagor
Fagor, who's going down, he says he touched the ball,
fagor que va abajo dice que tocó balón
but he doesn't have the same idea, the school
pero no tiene la misma idea el cole
returned it.
devolvió
If he got a yellow card before, I imagine
Si antes se ha petado amarilla imagino
Latin America says, well, why is this one? No, no,
que latinoamérica dice bueno porque esta
but he says he touched the ball, the son of a
no no pero dice que tocó balón el hijo
[ __ ], after this event,
[__] después de este acontecimiento
Westcol has been through hell and
wescol ha pasado por un infierno y por
the operating room. I'm going to tell you a little bit about
el quirófano les voy a contar un poquito
how the operation went. It's true, it's
cómo me fue en la operación es verdad es
true, he had to have surgery and everything is
verdad se tuvo co operar y todo es
true, how this happened. On the way back, the
verdad cómo esto a la vuelta la
experience that I lived through, but
experiencia que he vivido acord pero
well, let's see, unintentionally, it's an accident. Let
bueno a ver sin querer es un accidente
's tell you a little bit about how the operation went, pill, these are things that happen. Well, here I'm not going to show you what I have here, but
les voy a mostrar lo que tengo aquí pero
basically, uh, they opened my knee,
básicamente Eh me abrieron la rodilla me
they put in a graft from another person,
pusieron un un injerto de otra persona
so I can't do sports or
es pues ya no puede hacer deporte ni
run or train or anything like that,
correr ni entrenar ni nada por el estilo
weird  with orrea The fact is that this
rara con orrea El caso es que esta
operation is a very tedious operation,
operación es una operación muy tediosa
very annoying organizers of the event I
muy fastidiosa organizadores del evento
don't know, I have to sue like that
No sé yo tengo que demandar eso así
thinking but what
pensando pero lo que sí que tiene claro
Wescol is clear about is how he wants to make
wescol es cómo quiere hacer pagar a
Fagor pay for what he did, attention because it is not
fagor lo que hizo atención por qué no
wasted as an anecdote that
tiene desperdicio como anécdota que eso
will last a lifetime Your cruciate ligament
ya para toda la vida Tu ligamento cruzad
has been torn by Fagor who plays Pokémon it
ha sido roto por fagor que juega Pokémon
is quite
es bastante
funny he would have done that in Medin and he
gracioso hubiera hecho eso en medin y le
shoots him pa I would not stay with that
mete un tiro pa yo no me quedaba con esa
egg thank goodness it touched him in Spain to
huevo menos mal le tocó en España para
luo publicly without misery or rather with
luo públicamente sin miseria o sea con
me he did me a lot of damage dude but if
me me hizo un daño huevón pero si lo
Medellín does it he shoots him
hace Medellín le mete un
intentionally not intentionally but a
tiro intencional no intencional pero una
cpa I swear that I would reach the
cpa se lo juro que yo le llegaba a la
royal house I am not talking [ __ ]
casa real yo no estoy hablando caca
you can say that but is that
usted puede deir que pero esra ese
santra it is either
santra es o
a prison sentence around 3 years or
una pena de cárcel por ahí de 3 años o
a shot in the foot we have to return the
un tiro en el pie hay que devolverle la
same he hurt me very hard Ok F Well here
misma me daño durísimo Ok F Pues aquí
is the price a shot in the foot for
tiene el precio un tiro en el pie por
having retired a [ __ ] star from football
haber retirado del fútbol a una jodida
There is something that makes me very
estrella Hay algo que me tiene muy
sad and that is that  obviously I'm
triste y es que obviamente todo
going to spend all of December like this gonorrhea
diciembre lo voy a pasar así gonorrea
Unfortunately but he's
Lamentablemente pero lo está diciendo en
serious eh I mean he's serious eh
serio eh o sea lo dice en serio eh
dude that makes me sad But what
huevón eso me tiene triste Pero lo que
makes me sadder the most is that I think
más me tiene triste es que yo creo que
I'll never play
yo nunca más en la vida volver a jugar
soccer again that's what I think makes me
fútbol eso es lo que yo creo que más me
sadder because eh dog I don't know and they
tiene triste porque eh perro no sé y
caught me I think this was the same
pillaron yo creo que esta fue la misma
injury as Falc the same injuries as
lesión de falc la misma lesiones de
famous soccer players and Ed has
jugadores de fútbol así famosos y Ed ha
caught me that a lot of soccer players get
pillado que muchos jugadores de fútbol
injured dude and they never go back to being the
se lesionan huevón y no vuelven a ser
same actually it's not because their
los mismos en realidad no es porque la
knee isn't completely
rodilla no les haya quedado totalmente
good but rather because of the psychological damage I just
buena sino es por el daño psicológico yo
realized that gonorrhea
me acabo de dar cuenta de eso gorrea
imagine me with everything I've been through
imag yo con todo lo que he vivido
going back to play soccer to get
volverme a poner a jugar fútbol para
injured again you're not going to come in
volver a lesionarme usted no va a volver
that strong again you're not going to come in that crazy again
a entrar así de fuerte usted no va a
you're going to
volver a entrar así a la loca usted va a
play more with fear If you understand me
jugar más con miedo Si me entiendes
So I think dude I'm saying that in
Entonces yo creo que huevón yo digo que
order to never live this again Conan I don't
para yo no volver a vivir esto Conan no
want to play soccer again I swear
quiero volver a jugar fútbol se lo juro
for the icing on the cake of this video
par la guinda del pastel de este vídeo
Changing the subject, my people saying that
cambiando de tema mi gente diciendo que
people have a thing against
la gente le tiene Manía a los streamers
Argentine streamers, it's fashionable to criticize
argentinos está de moda bardear a los
Argentine streamers, it's fashionable to
streamers de Argentina está de moda
criticize streamers, especially here
bardear a los streamers más que nada acá
in Argentina because people. Well,
en Argentina porque la gente Bueno
streamers here in
también los streamers de acá de
Argentina too. Most of them take it easy, I can't, I ca
Argentina La mayoría se las remand no
n't be responsible
puedo yo no me puedo hacer cargo tampoco
for what others do either. I make my own
de lo que hacen los demás yo hago mi
content, I shouldn't be put
contenido a mí no me tendrían que meter
in the same bag.
en la misma bolsa
Eh so if they commit an act, let's
Eh entonces si cometen acto vamos a
call it cancelable. Most of them take it easy, it
llamarlo cancelable la mayoría se las
's justified. People, I don't know if I
remand está justificado gente no sé si
had more things in the title but I'm
tenía más cosillas en el título pero lo
going to leave it here since it's 2,
voy a dejar por aquí que son las 2s las
3, well, 2:30, after 2:30, let's go
3 bueno las 2:30 más de las 2:30 vamos
sleep a little. We haven't had
aí a mimir un poquillo No hemos tenido
a
una noche
very intense night and you guys don't feel like
bastante intensa y ustedes no tenéis
going to bed, so what's happening here? There are
ganas de acostar o sea que pasa aquí hay
2,000 people at almost 3 in the morning,
2000 personas casi a las 3 de la mañana
guys, and let's see if we can come up with some things to
chicos e a ver si salen cositas para
record for the main channel. The truth
grabar para el canal principal la verdad
is that I really want to give
es que tengo muchas ganas de de darle
the main channel a boost, especially this
caña el canal principal sobre todo este
year.  ok And hook a topic that
año vale Y enganchar un tema que nos
seems interesting to us, one of those where
parezca interesante an de estos de los
we start to blow it up, okay, I uploaded a
que nos ponemos a a petarlo vale subí un
video about Great Britain the
vídeo sobre el tema de Gran Bretaña el
other day, so I'm just getting into warming up the
otro día para ahí entrando calentando el
channel. But hey, you have to support it
canal Pero bueno tenéis que apoyarlo
a lot so that the video gets more popular
mucho para que el vídeo se posicione más
because it has done a little bit, it doesn't have
porque ha pinchado un poquillo no tiene
20,000 views. But hey, it's been a long
20.000 visitas Pero bueno lleva mucho
time since I uploaded videos, it's not the
tiempo sin subir vídeos no es la
theme, we'll see, little by little, okay, yeah,
temática veremos a ver poco a poco vale
also, this one will do well, but hey, I really want to
em sí que también que este también
do it too and upload it, but I need
hacerlo también y subirlo pero necesito
everything to download. I already downloaded my
tod habí a descargar Ya descargué mi
phone, I downloaded the camera, I have to
teléfono descargué la la cámara tengo
download Lorena's phone
que descargar el teléfono de Lorena
too, eh, all the videos and everything I
también eh todos los vídeos y todo lo
recorded in New York, okay, I'll make a
que grabé en Nueva York vale haré un
blog, sure, a guide blog, more or less,
blog segur un blog guía más o menos blog
guide blog, tips, no experience, no, from the
guía consejos no experiencia no del
trip to New York, I really want to
viaje a Nueva York tengo muchas ganas de
upload things, okay,
de subir cosas okay
And what's up, Karime, that topic hasn't
Y qué va Karime ese tema no me ha
caught me, Marifer Centeno and Mr.
pillado a mí tema Marifer Centeno y Mr
Doctor. Well, still, they're still talking about
doctor Bueno todavía Ya siguen hablando
that topic, it hasn't died yet, but it has
de ese tema no murió todavía pero a mí
n't caught me, I've already made two videos that are
no me cogió yo ya dos vídeos que hice
quite good about  that topic and the
bastante buenos sobre ese tema y la
truth is they didn't work for me I felt sorry for them I'll do it let's
verdad no me funcionaron me me dio pena
see if tomorrow I can finish
em haré a ver si mañana puedo terminar
doing the one about New York Okay
de hacer el de Nueva York Okay
and and and
y
other things come out that we
y y salen otras cositas de las que
can
podamos
record and other things come out that we
grabar y salen otras cositas de las que
can record okay a kiss I love you
podamos grabar vale un beso os quiero
so much okay I love you so much
muchísimo vale os quiero muchísimo
Thank you very much uh I'm going to report now the
Muchas gracias eh voy a ahora reportar
channel of this crazy guy who has threatened us
el el canal del loquito este que nos ha
em I hope they shut down his [ __ ] channel
em Espero que le cierren el [__] canal
obviously And tomorrow I'll be talking
evidentemente Y mañana estaré hablando
to Juan gopin to see what this is about him
con Juan gopin a ver qué es eso de que
having an agreement with a law firm in Miami
tiene un acuerdo con un bufete de Miami
so that they can
para que le pongan
file a complaint against him
la para que le pongan la la denuncia
there in Miami and what and let's see if let's see
allí en Miami y que y a ver si a ver yo
I think I'm going to look at it now eh I'm going to
yo creo lo voy a mirar ahora eh voy a
look now like this eh more or less how it is
mirar ahora así eh más o menos cómo es
but but I think what's it called r token
pero pero creo que cómo se llama r token
r token okay I'm going to go there now to
r token vale voy a ir para allá ahora a
report it let's go on twitter they're going to shut down
reportarlo vamos en twit lo van a cerrar
the channel but 100% I mean with the
el canal pero 100% o sea con las
atrocities that he has said but but I would
barbaridades que ha dicho pero pero me
like I would like for his
gustaría me gustaría que se le cayera el
balls to fall on the law that I understand that  Yes,
pelete en la ley que entiendo que sí que
something can be done there in the United States,
algo se podrá hac allí en Estados Unidos
guys, a huge kiss, okay, handsome, a
chicos un beso enorme vale guapos un
kiss, I love you all very much. Bye,
beso os quiero mucho Chao
rest, bu
descansad bu